should you keep secrets from your
你是否应该对你的人隐瞒秘密
partner this is big yes and the data
合作伙伴，这很重要，而且数据也很重要。
shows it will help to increase
这表明它将有助于增加
satisfaction and lower conflict in your
满意度和较低的冲突
relationship so give me an example of
关系，请举个例子
something that I shouldn't say to my
有些话我不应该对我的家人说
partner here's a juicy one
伙伴，这可是个劲爆消息！
so what
所以呢
about
关于
oh even when I say out loud I know py
哦，即使我大声说我知道py
Brunson is the world's most influential
布伦森是世界上最具影响力的人。
Matchmaker who Blends groundbreaking
融合了突破性元素的媒人
science research and over 15 years of
科学研究和超过15年的经验
expertise to prove that anyone can
专业知识证明任何人都可以
create shakable foundations for
为……创造不稳固的基础
long-lasting life-changing love I read
我读到过一段关于持久、改变人生的爱情的故事。
about this study that says men are
关于这项研究，它说男性
approximately 624 more likely to
大约有 624 人更有可能
separate if the woman gets terminally
如果该女子患上绝症，则需分开隔离。
ill yes what is going on there typically
是的，那里通常发生了什么事。
it's because there is a low level of
这是因为水平较低
satisfaction in the relationship from
对这段关系的满意度
not having enough sex for example but
例如，性生活不足。
this is a major issue cuz 80% of
这是一个大问题，因为80%的
relationships have a lower level of
人际关系水平较低
satisfaction today than any point in
今天比任何时候都更令人满意
history and part of that is because most
历史，部分原因是因为大多数
of what we know about finding and
我们对发现和的了解
keeping love has unfortunately been fed
不幸的是，维系爱情的手段已经根深蒂固。
to us through lies let's pause there
谎言蒙蔽了我们，让我们先停一下。
because I want to talk about those myths
因为我想谈谈那些迷思。
okay so does having more sex increase
那么，性生活越多，性欲就越强吗？
the happiness in your relationship no
你们关系中的幸福感
what about having doubts in your
如果你对自己的某些方面有所怀疑呢？
relationship is that bad that couldn't
这段关系糟糕到无法维系。
be further from the truth really it's
这与事实相去甚远。
actually healthy to have doubts about
对此抱有怀疑态度其实是健康的。
your relationship and this is why what
你们的关系，这就是为什么
about if someone cheats is that the end
如果有人作弊，那就结束了吗？
of the relationship brilliant question
关于这段关系的绝妙问题
and quite honestly and then what are the
坦白地说，那么接下来又是什么呢？
most important qualities I need in a
我需要的最重要品质
partner okay this BW my mind so these
搭档好的，这是我的想法，所以这些
are the three traits to have a
具备以下三种特质是……
phenomenal relationship number one what
非凡的关系第一名是什么
this has always blown my mind a little
这件事一直让我有点难以置信。
bit 53% of you that listen to the show
53% 的听众收听了该节目
regularly haven't yet subscribed to the
经常还没有订阅
show so could I ask you for a favor
所以，我能请你帮个忙吗？
before we start if you like the show and
在我们开始之前，如果你喜欢这个节目，
you like what we do here and you want to
你喜欢我们在这里做的事情，并且你想……
support us the free simple way that you
您支持我们的方式很简单，而且完全免费。
can do just that is by hitting the
做到这一点的方法就是点击
Subscribe button and my commitment to
订阅按钮以及我对订阅的承诺
you is if you do that then I'll do
如果你那样做，那我也会那样做。
everything in my power me and my team to
我和我的团队将竭尽全力
make sure that this show is better for
确保这个节目对……更好
you every single week we'll listen to
我们每周都会听你的节目。
your feedback we'll find the guest that
您的反馈将帮助我们找到合适的客人
you want me to speak to and we'll
你想让我跟谁谈谈，我们……
continue to do what we do thank you so
请继续做我们正在做的事情，谢谢。
much
很多
[Music]
[音乐]
good to see you again it's awesome to be
很高兴再次见到你，真是太棒了！
here I'm going to ask you a question
接下来我要问你一个问题
that assumes that I don't know who you
那假设我不知道你是谁。
are okay which is quite hard because I
没事，这很难，因为我
know you very well but who are you and
我非常了解你，但你究竟是谁？
who are you to write these two books
你凭什么写这两本书？
that I have in front of me find love and
我面前的一切都是为了找到爱情，
keep
保持
love well who who am I I'm first and
爱，我是谁？我是谁？我是第一，而且
foremost a husband I'm a father uh I'm a
首先，我是一位丈夫，我是一位父亲，呃，我是一位
son I'm a brother I'm a cousin I'm an
儿子，我是兄弟，我是表兄弟，我是……
uncle I'm a mentor I'm a mentee you know
叔叔，我是你的导师，也是你的学员，你知道吗？
I'm all of those things and I feel like
我具备所有这些特质，我觉得
those are the things I am first uh but
这些是我首先考虑的事情，但是
uh I have a longstanding history with
呃，我和……有着很长的渊源。
relationships you know I became a
你知道，我与人之间的关系变得
Matchmaker my wife and I launched a
我和妻子创办了一家婚介公司
matchmaking agency we became one of the
我们成为婚介机构之一
largest agencies in the United States
美国最大的机构
and what's interesting about being a
而作为一名……的有趣之处是什么？
matchmaker is that a lot of people don't
媒人的问题在于，很多人都不认识媒人。
even realize that is a career like
甚至意识到那是一种职业
there's legit matchmakers there's
确实有正规的婚介机构。
probably I'd say roughly a thousand
我估计大概有一千左右吧。
full-time match makers around the world
世界各地的全职婚介师
and what we do is we literally match
我们所做的，就是进行字面匹配。
people together for long-term committed
人们为了长期的承诺而走到一起
relationships but what ends up happening
人际关系，但最终会发生什么？
if you're successful with that is two
如果你成功做到这一点，那就是两个
people enter a long-term committed
人们进入一个长期承诺期。
relationship and because they've built
关系，以及他们建立起来的关系
up a relationship with you they have
他们与你建立了一种关系。
questions about how do they keep that
关于他们如何保持这种状态的问题
relationship how do they keep their love
他们如何维系这段感情？
so my wife and I then began to
于是，我和妻子就开始了
transition into counselors and coaches
转型成为咨询师和教练
for married couples or couples who were
对于已婚夫妇或曾经是夫妻的人来说
in committed relationships so that's
在稳定的恋爱关系中，就是这样。
where that that started and that went on
事情的起因和后续发展
for for over a decade and then on top of
十多年来，而且在此基础上……
that I started uh you know I had
我开始的时候，你知道，我曾经有
research Global Research at Tinder which
在 Tinder 进行全球研究
is a great opportunity for me to look at
对我来说，这是一个很好的机会去了解……
a very large data set and make
一个非常大的数据集，并制作
predictions as to what's happening with
对未来发展趋势的预测
our relationships uh I host television
我们的关系，呃，我主持电视节目
shows uh reality TV shows which for good
真人秀节目，这对……有好处
or for bad I think help to spark
或者说，坏事我认为有助于激发火花
conversation about relationships that
关于人际关系的对话
are needed so doing research there you
需要进行一些研究，所以你在那里做些调查。
know I do podcasts like this you know so
你知道我也会做这种播客。
my life actually is all about
我的生活实际上就是关于
relationships and that's the reason why
人际关系，这就是原因。
I wanted to to write this book and
我想写这本书，
that's the reason why I feel qualified
这就是我觉得自己有资格的原因。
to write this book so how long ago was
写这本书是什么时候的事了？
it that you started doing the
就是你开始做这件事的时候
matchmaking oh my gosh so
配对，我的天哪，真是太糟糕了
2008 is when I officially began
2008年是我正式开始从事这项工作的年份。
matchmaking yeah 17 years it was a long
相亲？是啊，17年了，真是漫长的一段路。
time ago the reason I asked that is a
之前我问这个问题的原因是……
lot has changed in 17 years yes we've
是的，17年来发生了很多变化。
been through this Evol ution of dating
经历过约会方式的这种演变
apps and matchmaking services and things
应用程序、婚介服务等等
like Match.com and my question is where
比如 Match.com，我的问题是哪里
do you think we find ourselves today as
你认为我们今天所处的境地是怎样的？
it relates to relationships like what is
它与人际关系有关，比如……
the macro picture how are people feeling
宏观层面来看，人们的感受如何？
the person that's watching this right
正在观看这段视频的人
now that's either single and looking in
现在要么是单身，要么正在寻找对象
a relationship and maybe struggling can
一段关系，或许还有挣扎，可能会
you give me an overview a synopsis of
请给我一个概述或概要。
how they're feeling in their head sure
他们内心的感受究竟如何，我们拭目以待。
sure and why all right this is a great
当然，这真是太棒了！
one so we're feeling different things
一是我们感受不同。
there's a small percentage of us and
我们当中只有一小部分人是这样，
I'll go to Eli fle research who wrote
我会去找 Eli fle 研究，他写了
phenomenal books but one is called the
非常精彩的书籍，但其中一本叫做……
All or Nothing marriage that I love and
我所爱的那种要么全有要么全无的婚姻
in it he states that if you look at
他在文中指出，如果你观察
marriages committed relationships that
婚姻是承诺的关系。
20% of us have higher satisfaction than
20% 的人比其他人更满意
we ever have in the history of
我们历史上从未有过这样的经历
relationships and you think 20% one is
人际关系，你认为20%是
that's fairly small and do they really
那地方挺小的，他们真的会这么做吗？
have high statisfaction and and I fully
非常满意，而且我完全
believe this and the reason why is
相信这一点，原因如下：
because we have tools you know we have
因为我们有工具，你知道我们有
people watch podcast read books watch
人们观看播客、阅读书籍、观看
television shows we have tools like
我们有类似工具的电视节目
we've never had before more access to
我们从未像现在这样拥有如此多的接触机会
therapy so 20% very satisfied but 80%
治疗效果：20% 非常满意，80% 不满意
more
更多的
dissatisfied more upset more confused
不满、沮丧、困惑
than ever before and I would say that
比以往任何时候都更甚，而且我会这么说。
those who are not in relationships the
那些单身的人
pool reflects that as well I think
我认为泳池也反映了这一点。
there's a 20% of singles who are hopeful
有20%的单身人士抱有希望。
and are developing the tools and
并且正在开发相关工具和
developing the skills and learning
培养技能和学习
active listening and all these things
积极倾听以及所有这些事情
and they will and they believe they'll
他们会的，而且他们相信他们会的
enter strong relationships they're
建立牢固的关系，他们是
they're very hopeful I think there's 80%
他们非常乐观，我认为有80%的可能性。
out there that
外面那个
are perhaps hopeless disgruntled
或许是无可救药的不满者
confused dismayed uh you know and and
困惑、沮丧，你知道的，还有
and I would say that that that's that's
我会说，那就是……
the landscape today that being said the
也就是说，今天的景观
reason for that is because we over the
原因在于我们过度……
years have placed more
多年来，人们已经投入了更多
emphasis on one partner versus having a
强调一个伴侣而不是拥有多个伴侣
village to lean on so so we're we're
村庄可以依靠，所以我们……
leaning more so we're we we're requiring
越来越倾向于，所以我们要求
more from our partners so what that
更多来自我们合作伙伴的信息，那又怎样呢？
means is that if we're requiring more if
这意味着如果我们要求更多的话
we're requiring our partner to be we
我们要求我们的合作伙伴是……
want our partner to be our best friend
我们希望伴侣成为我们最好的朋友
we all want to launch a business and be
我们都想创办自己的企业，并取得成功。
a CEO right so we want our partner to be
首席执行官，对吧？所以我们希望我们的合作伙伴是
co-ceo or coo we want our partner to be
我们希望我们的合作伙伴是联合首席执行官或首席运营官。
a great parent we want our partner to
我们希望伴侣成为一位优秀的父母。
come home at night take their clothes
晚上回家后，他们会带走自己的衣服。
off and do backflips in the bedroom
下楼，然后在卧室里做后空翻。
right this is what we want this is what
对，这就是我们想要的，这就是
we want so we want now more from that
我们想要更多，所以我们现在想要更多。
one person versus 30 years ago 300 years
一个人对比30年前300年前
ago 3,000 years ago
3000年前
300,000 years ago when when humans
30万年前，人类
really began 300,000 years ago so you
实际上，它始于30万年前，所以你
you you look at all this and you say wow
你看着这一切，不禁惊叹：哇！
we want more so therefore for we're
我们想要更多，因此我们是
going to have lower satisfaction so this
满意度会降低，所以这样
is what I believe the the landscape is
这就是我所认为的景观。
today and if we start then with people
今天，如果我们从人开始，那就从今天开始吧。
that are looking for love people that
那些正在寻找爱情的人
are in search of Love um how are the the
正在寻找爱情，嗯，他们怎么样？
current tools
当前工具
because I see so much online about how
因为我在网上看到很多关于如何
people are disenfranchised with like
人们因类似原因而被剥夺了权利
things like dating apps and they've
比如约会软件之类的东西，它们……
tried like social media and I've got so
试过社交媒体，但我感觉很糟糕。
many of my friends who are struggling at
我的很多朋友都在努力……
the moment they're going on 100 dates a
他们开始约会100次的那一刻
year and they're unable to find anybody
一年过去了，他们还是找不到人。
and I I Ponder to myself I go you're
我心想，我去你那里
going on 100 dates a year you're almost
一年约会100次，你几乎就……
a professional data and you still can't
即使拥有专业数据，你仍然无法做到。
find
寻找
somebody it's surely that's not through
肯定有人没通过
lack of options or like the top of the
缺乏选择，或者像顶部一样
funnel there the sort of exposure is
漏斗状的暴露方式是
fine but there's something further down
好吧，但下面还有事。
the funnel as it relates to them being
漏斗与它们之间的关系
able to convert somebody that seems to
能够说服看似
be off right right but but also I would
不对，对，但是，我也想
argue that it could even stem you you
认为它甚至可以阻止你
could go deeper to the root right so you
可以深入到根源，对吧？
think about attachment Styles attachment
思考依恋风格
Styles I know you've talked a lot about
我知道你已经谈了很多关于风格的话题
attachment Styles attachment styles are
附件样式附件样式是
kind of the hot thing the hot Trend that
有点像现在很火的东西，很热门的趋势。
people are talking about rightfully so I
人们都在谈论这件事，这是理所当然的。
like this and if you think about that
就像这样，如果你仔细想想……
there are primarily three right we know
我们知道，主要有三种。
we have secure there's anxious and
我们有安全感，那里很焦虑，而且
there's avoidant there's there are other
有回避型人格，还有其他类型的人。
uh variations but in essence these are
呃，有一些变体，但本质上这些都是
the three now depending on who you talk
现在这三个人，取决于你问的是谁。
to roughly 50 60% of the population are
大约占人口的50%到60%
secure that means the balance are going
这意味着余额正在稳定。
to be anxious or avoidant or or or some
感到焦虑或回避，或者或某些
combination so therefore if you are on a
组合，因此，如果您正在使用
date and you have an anxious attachment
约会对象和你患有焦虑型依恋
style or you have an avoidant attachment
你是那种有回避型依恋的人还是有回避型依恋的人
style and you have someone in front of
风格，你面前有人
you who is the perfect match for you
你，那个最适合你的人
they're they're they're taking off all
他们正在……他们正在……他们正在全部……
the boxes you could be so anxious or so
那些盒子可能会让你非常焦虑，或者
avoidant that you push them away or you
回避型思维，比如你把他们推开或者你
lay blame to a certain character a
将责任归咎于某个特定人物
characteristic or a trait that they have
他们所具有的特征或特性
that means nothing to the relationship
这对这段关系来说毫无意义。
and you dismissed them you you know um
然后你就把他们打发走了，你知道的，嗯
this is going to sound funny but it's
这听起来可能很滑稽，但事实是
sad is do you know what we found when we
令人难过的是，你知道我们发现了什么吗？
were matchmaking what the number one
配对是排名第一的
reason why people did not allow someone
人们不允许某人出现的原因
someone to get a second date with
想和某人进行第二次约会
them they had a velcro
它们都带有魔术贴
wallet velcro wallet are cool though you
魔术贴钱包很酷，虽然你
change no they're not you can't no no
改变？不，他们不是，你不能，不，不
all right so you know what was it was
好了，所以你知道那是什么了。
around attraction so one it was you know
围绕着景点，所以你知道，其中一个就是。
physical attraction but in particular it
生理上的吸引力，尤其是
was cuz they they smelled really they
是因为他们身上真的散发着难闻的气味。
had bad breath halosis right or there
当时就口臭，有雾霾。
was some odor now you can argue that
现在确实有些气味，你可以这么说。
scent plays a strong role in our partner
气味在我们伴侣关系中扮演着重要角色。
selection Dr Tara forart talks about
选择 Tara forart 博士谈到
this quite quite a bit right so there
这相当多，对吧？
there's uh there's a evolutionary
呃，这里有一个进化论
biology that comes with scent yes I
是的，气味相关的生物学特征。
agree but to look across from someone
同意，但要从某人的角度看过去。
and say you know what you you like you
然后说你知道你喜欢什么
like your breath stinks right and I'm
就像你的口气很臭一样，而我
not going to give up the the second date
不会放弃第二次约会
and as a result of your breath stinks
结果就是你的口气很臭
you have long uh fingernails you're
你的指甲很长。
you're you're in a track suit right for
你穿着运动服，对吧？
to to to look at these moments and say
看看这些时刻，然后说
because of this thing I'm going to
因为这件事，我要……
dismiss you as a partner I think for a
我认为，我不应该再把你当成合作伙伴了。
lot of people sounds logical but then
很多人听起来很有道理，但实际上并非如此。
for a lot of people sounds ridiculous
对很多人来说，这听起来很荒谬。
you know what I mean now how you got to
你现在明白我的意思了吧，你是怎么走到这一步的？
that point is the challenge if you think
如果你认为这一点就是挑战所在，那么
it's ridiculous how you got to assuming
你居然会得出这样的假设，真是荒谬至极。
that because someone has a tracksuit on
因为有人穿着运动服
because they have long fingernails it
因为他们留着长指甲
dismisses
解雇
their their um their validity of being a
他们的，他们的，嗯，他们作为……的有效性
great partner that is about you that is
一位以你为中心的好伙伴
about you your attachment that is about
关于你，关于你的依恋
how you've been socialized that is about
你的社会化方式，这才是关键所在。
so I would argue that people who are
所以我认为，那些……
going on lots and lots and lots of dates
约会很多很多次
and they still can't feel like they can
但他们仍然感觉不到自己可以
find the right partner the first place
首先要找到合适的伴侣。
to look at is yourself I do Wonder this
看看你自己，我确实很想知道这一点。
because I think the more dates you go on
因为我觉得约会次数越多，你就会越频繁地约会。
the more reference points of comparison
比较的参考点越多
you then have for the next person so
然后你就可以为下一个人做好准备了。
date 101 if you've been on 100
如果你已经去过100号，那就把日期设为101号。
previously you've now got a 100 guys who
之前你们有100个人，
are maybe all good at one thing and date
也许他们都擅长一件事，然后约会
101 is going to be compared to the
101 将与
previous 100 on all factors so maybe
之前所有因素都达到了100分，所以也许
date 49 had great sense of humor date 53
第49次约会对象很有幽默感。第53次约会对象也很有幽默感。
was rich date 67 was physically
67岁是富有的，身体状况良好
beautiful now date 101 is going to be
现在美丽的约会101即将到来
compared to all previous dates on all of
与之前所有日期相比
those factors and you're always going to
这些因素，你总是会……
find something that is less good at
找一些不太擅长的东西
least one factor that is less good than
至少有一个因素不如……
someone you dat previously and I've
你以前约会过的人，而我
always wondered are you like
一直很好奇你是不是这样的
accidentally expanding your comparison
不小心扩大了比较范围
set by meeting more and more and more
通过不断会面而逐渐形成
and more and more people y so I think
越来越多的人，所以我认为
this reads to uh Barry schwarz's work uh
这读起来像是巴里·施瓦茨的作品。
with the Paradox of choice mhm where you
选择的悖论，嗯，你在哪里？
know what Barry Schwartz did with the
知道巴里·施瓦茨用……做了什么
par Paradox of choice which is brilliant
选择悖论真是妙不可言
is that when we're presented with more
就是当我们面对更多的时候
options which is in essence all of these
选项，本质上就是所有这些选项。
dates when we choose one we have a less
当我们选择一个日期时，我们拥有的就更少了。
level of satisfaction with the choice
对选择的满意度
because we saw that we had a 100 choices
因为我们看到我们有100个选择。
versus if you have three choices and you
相比之下，如果你有三个选择，而你
have to choose between one of those
必须在两者之间做出选择
three there's going to be a higher level
第三，将会有一个更高的层次
of satisfaction as a result a real life
真实生活中的满足感
example is my grandmother so my
例如我的祖母，所以我
grandmother grew up in I say the bush in
祖母在灌木丛中长大，我说的是灌木丛。
the bush in Jamaica okay super super
牙买加的灌木丛，好吧，超级棒！
small town in Jamaica my grandmother
我祖母住在牙买加的一个小镇上。
literally had five or six options as a
实际上，我有五六个选择。
partner now as a result of my
由于我的缘故，我现在成了我的伴侣。
grandmother having those options when
祖母拥有这些选择时
she chooses one person there's going to
她会选择其中一个人
be more value more emphasis even more if
如果更重视，那就更应该重视，甚至更加强调。
you look at the investment Theory more
你更关注投资理论。
investment placed in one of those
投资于其中之一
options versus if she had a hundred
如果她有一百种选择，情况又会如何呢？
options and she makes a a choice that
她有很多选择，并做出了一个决定。
choice with 100 options becomes more
拥有100个选项的选择变得更加困难
disposable right so this is one issue
一次性用品，所以这是其中一个问题。
that we have in terms of giving
我们在给予方面所拥有的
ourselves so many options the other
我们自己有很多选择，其他的
challenge with this is when you watch
挑战在于当你观看的时候
people date they typically date the same
人们约会时通常会和同一个人约会。
person you know it's typically it's
你认识的人通常是这样的
typically the S the same
通常情况下，S 相同
characteristics even physically you know
甚至身体上的特征你也知道
the the the same
相同的
I argue that some of the greatest value
我认为一些最有价值的
that we we can receive in the dating
我们可以在约会中获得
Market if you want to look at as dating
如果你想把市场看作是约会市场的话。
Market is to take ourselves out of
市场是为了让我们摆脱困境。
our uh our our Market if you will and
我们的，呃，我们的，我们的市场，如果你愿意这么称呼的话。
put yourself in someplace different
把自己置身于一个不同的地方。
right I call this the premium effect so
没错，我称之为溢价效应。
so so an example of this is I had a
举个例子，我曾经……
friend who was a white woman roughly 35
一位大约35岁的白人女性朋友
years old who lived in Northern London
居住在伦敦北部的一位年长的女士
and she was like Paul I'm dating all
她就像保罗一样，正在和所有人约会。
these guys you know I can't find the
你知道，我找不到这些人。
right one blah blah blah blah blah blah
右边那个等等等等等等
I said 'l look you love art don't you
我说：“你看，你喜欢艺术，对吧？”
she said yeah yeah I love art I said all
她说，是啊是啊，我喜欢艺术。我说，全部
right I want you to take yourself down
没错，我希望你自降身价。
to the black cultural archives in
到黑人文化档案馆
Brixton and I want you to go to this you
布里克斯顿，我希望你去那里。
know this exhibit that they're having
我知道他们正在举办这个展览。
and she was like
她当时就像
brixon said I said yeah brickton is
布里克斯顿说我说，是的，布里克顿是
brickton is cool I go there all the time
布里克顿很棒，我经常去那里。
right I want you to go there now why did
对，我现在要你去那里，为什么？
I ask you to go I asked her to go
我请你走，我请她走。
because the moment that she goes
因为她离开的那一刻
characteristically she's not going to
她一贯的作风是不会……
look the same these are mostly going to
看起来都一样，这些大多都会……
be black men and women perhaps even a
可能是黑人男性和女性，甚至可能
little bit younger than she is different
比她小一点，性格也不同。
culturally right but yet they have the
文化上正确，但他们却拥有
same value in art and their appreciation
艺术及其鉴赏中具有同等价值
for creativity Etc the moment that she
为了创造力等等，她那一刻
goes there what happens some people in
去那里会发生什么事？有些人会在那里……
the room look at her like what what she
房间里的人都用一种奇怪的眼神看着她，好像在问她什么事。
doing here like why is she here those
她在这里做什么？她为什么会在这里？
are the close-minded people Carol dwick
卡罗尔·德威克是那些思想封闭的人吗？
talks about this in her book mindset we
她在书中谈到了这一点，我们的心态
have closed-minded open-minded those are
思想封闭的人和思想开放的人
the
这
closed-minded but how do the open-minded
思想封闭的人，那么思想开放的人又该如何看待他们呢？
react to to my friend they lean in what
对我的朋友做出反应，他们向我靠过来
are you doing here and they're curious
你在这里做什么？他们很好奇。
and they engage and all of a sudden she
他们开始交谈，突然间她
opens her network to a whole new group
她将自己的关系网拓展到了一个全新的群体。
of people some of those could be
这些人中有些可能是
romantic interest some of those could be
其中一些人可能对浪漫关系感兴趣
platonic they could be friends so when
柏拉图式的友谊，他们可以成为朋友，所以当
we're dating the serial daters
我们正在和那些频繁约会的人约会
especially the hundred people is it's
尤其是那一百个人……
important for you to step outside of
对你来说，走出去很重要
your sphere if you will I want to pick
如果你愿意的话，我想选择你的领域
up on something there you said that
你刚才说你好像发现了什么。
white woman went into a black space and
一位白人女子走进了一个黑色空间，
in that black space you wouldd be
在那片黑暗空间里，你会……
considered a premium because basically
被视为溢价，因为基本上
her characteristics make her rare yes
她的特质使她成为罕见的人物。
right I was just doing some research
对，我刚才在做一些研究。
then and it says that studies and
然后，它说研究和
surveys in indicate that ethnic
调查显示，种族
minorities particularly Asian men and
少数族裔，特别是亚裔男性和
black women often face unique challenges
黑人女性常常面临独特的挑战
in dating in both the UK and the US and
在英国和美国的约会中
these challenges stem from a combination
这些挑战源于多种因素的综合作用。
of social stereotypes cultural biases
社会刻板印象和文化偏见
and the preference expressed on dating
以及在约会中表达的偏好
platforms and the reason I'm asking this
平台以及我问这个问题的原因
question is to it's not a lived
问题是，这不是一种生活体验。
experience I have because I'm not an
我之所以有这些经验，是因为我不是……
Asian man although sometimes people
虽然有时人们是亚洲人
think I am there are a group group of
我想我在那里有一群人
people where I don't have a shared lived
那些我没有共同居住的地方的人们
experience who are struggling in ways in
有经验的人在某些方面正在挣扎
the western world that like maybe me and
西方世界，也许就像我一样，
you don't understand yeah it no it
你不明白，是啊，不，是啊
definitely definitely you know we we
当然，你肯定知道我们
have to understand that we exist in a
必须明白我们存在于一个
highly racist society and a lot of
种族歧视严重的社会，以及很多
people don't like to acknowledge it
人们不愿承认这一点。
don't like to talk about it like to
不喜欢谈论这件事，喜欢
sweep it under the rug but when it comes
先把它掩盖起来，但当它出现时……
to dating it shows up like in this in
约会中，它就像这样出现
this statistic that you're talking about
你提到的这个统计数据
now now let's think about this if you
现在，让我们来思考一下，如果你
are someone who is not black and you are
你不是黑人，而你
interested in a black I'm sorry you're
对黑色感兴趣？抱歉，你
interested in a partner and then you're
如果你对伴侣感兴趣，那么你
and you've had no experiences with black
而且你之前没有任何与黑人接触的经验。
people other than maybe watching some
除了可能在看一些节目的人之外，其他人可能也会有这样的经历。
black people on on television and your
电视上的黑人，还有你的
parents in your community have said all
你们社区的家长们已经说了所有
kinds of crazy things about about black
关于黑人的各种疯狂事
people and you have all types of
人，而且种类繁多
negative belief structures around black
围绕黑人的负面信念结构
people and then and you're a man you're
人们，然后，你是一个男人，你是
say a white man and you're presented
比如说一个白人男性，你就会看到这样的画面。
with a black woman on a dating app are
在约会软件上和黑人女性交往是
you going to swipe on this person no
你会给这个人点赞吗？不会。
you're you're you're not because you
你不是因为你
don't understand how incredible she is
不明白她有多么了不起。
how smart she is how beautiful she is
她多么聪明，她多么美丽！
like you don't you have no appreciation
就像你一样，你毫无欣赏之心。
so the reason why they're Swip they're
所以他们之所以使用Swip，是因为
not swiping is their ignorance that's
不滑动屏幕是他们的无知，仅此而已。
that's that's what it is and that's this
就是这样，就是这样。
is the reason why one of the most
这就是为什么其中之一最……
important things we can do is widen our
我们可以做的重要事情是拓宽我们的
social groups this is the most important
社会群体，这是最重要的。
thing I mean it positively impacts our
我的意思是，它对我们产生了积极的影响。
romantic relationships it positively
浪漫关系对此有积极影响
impacts our life is that we need to have
对我们生活产生影响的是，我们需要拥有
a diverse set of people that we interact
我们互动的对象形形色色。
with and truly understand how beautiful
与……真正理解它的美好
how beautiful people who are different
多么美丽，不同的人
than us actually are is there a bit of a
比我们实际拥有的更多，这其中是否有些……
systemic issue here as well because when
这里也存在系统性问题，因为当
I was thinking about your grandmother
我在想你的祖母
growing up in that Village in Jamaica
在牙买加的那个村庄长大
that you referenced she
你提到的她
would spend a lot of time because of the
会因为这个原因花费大量时间
nature of how she would meet that person
她会以何种方式与那个人相遇
in the vill that other man in the
村子里还有另一个人
village getting to know him Beyond his
村民们逐渐了解他，超越了他
surface level appearance yes so if he
表面上看是的，所以如果他
lived across the street she would
她住在街对面
interact with him see his behavior he
与他互动，观察他的行为。
might have long fingernails you know but
你可能留着长指甲，但
she she gets to learn that he's a kind
她逐渐了解到他是个善良的人。
generous person and he's got a good
他是个慷慨大方的人，而且人品很好。
sense of humor so she can look past the
她很有幽默感，所以能够忽略这一点。
velcro wallet and the long fingernails
魔术贴钱包和长指甲
but in the way that we've designed
但按照我们设计的方式来说
dating in the modern world where most
在现代社会，约会变得越来越普遍。
people now I believe are meeting online
我相信现在人们都是在网上见面。
in some form whether it's social media
以某种形式，无论是社交媒体
or other we're actually purely judging
或者我们实际上只是在评判其他方面
someone in the fingernails we have we
我们指甲里有人
make a decision in a couple of seconds
在几秒钟内做出决定
whether this person is comp compatible
此人是否与公司兼容
or not and obviously that's not possible
或者不，显然这是不可能的。
um and I just see I just feel this real
嗯，我只是觉得这很真实
strong sense
强烈的感觉
of
的
um dissatisfaction
嗯，不满
frustration and uh desperation yes from
是的，沮丧和绝望。
people at the moment as it relates to
目前人们对此的看法
finding someone yes and I just think the
是的，我找到了合适的人，我只是觉得
systems that we've built social
我们构建的社会系统
networking the screens have have only
网络屏幕只有
exacerbated this frustration and
这加剧了这种挫败感，
Desperation my question which is
绝望之下，我的问题是……
somewhat linked to this is really around
与此有些关联的其实就在附近
the old ways of doing things like you
像你这样的老方法
were talking about your grandmother and
我们在谈论你的祖母。
I was really curious about one subject
我对某个主题非常感兴趣。
in particular and wondered if you you
特别是，我想知道你是否
had any data on this which is arranged
是否有关于这方面的任何数据，这些数据是如何安排的？
marriages yes yes are arranged
是的，婚姻是包办的。
marriages as successful as the
婚姻像……一样成功
relationships we form today via social
我们今天通过社交建立的关系
media screens etc etc
媒体屏幕等等
because you know back in the day we were
因为你知道，以前我们是
kind of put together um with somebody
有点像和某人一起凑到一起。
based on I don't know family or economic
基于我不了解的家庭或经济状况
reasons did those marriages succeed many
这些婚姻成功的原因有很多。
of us don't want to acknowledge how
我们中的许多人都不愿承认这一点
successful arranged marriages actually
成功的包办婚姻实际上
have been and continue to be really
一直是，而且现在仍然是真正的
continue to be but we have to look at
继续下去，但我们必须考虑……
the why right now when people hear this
为什么人们现在听到这句话会这么想
they immediately say oh well what about
他们立刻说，哦，那又怎样呢？
all the abuse and the dissatis action
所有的虐待和不满行为
that happens in these relationships does
这种情况确实会发生在这些关系中。
it happen absolutely but it also happens
这绝对会发生，但也有可能发生
in non arranged marriages at
在非包办婚姻中
significantly High rates so why are
利率显著偏高，那么为什么会这样呢？
arranged marriages so successful to some
包办婚姻对某些人来说非常成功
researchers they have a higher level of
研究人员，他们拥有更高水平的
satisfaction than non- arranged
与未安排的相比，满意度更高
marriages and here's the reason why the
婚姻，原因如下：
reason why is because you have families
原因在于你有家人。
coming together and negotiating and
齐聚一堂，进行谈判和
determin in whether or not this
决定是否如此
particular person fits within their
特定的人适合他们的
family structure and what does that mean
家庭结构及其意义
that means that you have literally a
这意味着你实际上拥有一个
mother a father a grandmother
母亲、父亲、祖母
grandfather a brother a sister who come
祖父、兄弟、姐妹，他们来了
together and they discuss and debate the
他们一起讨论和辩论
characteristics they discuss and debate
他们讨论和辩论的特征
whether or not this person is an
无论这个人是否是
upstanding you know is this an
正直的你知道这是吗
upstanding human being you know is is
你知道，他是一位正直的人。
this person open-minded is this person
这个人思想开放，他就是这个人。
going to be resourceful right are they
他们会想方设法解决问题，对吧？
resilient they debate these
他们对此争论不休，态度坚韧。
characteristics and the reason why it's
特点及其原因
so beneficial is because the person
之所以如此有益，是因为这个人
getting married is not involved and
结婚与此无关
they're not involved because they would
他们没有参与，因为他们会
be entirely biased what happens today is
今天发生的事情完全带有偏见。
incredibly dangerous what happens today
今天发生的事情极其危险
is when we meet someone we typically do
就是当我们遇到某人时，我们通常会做什么
not involve any friends and family we
不牵连任何朋友和家人
are already infatuated with the person
已经迷恋上这个人了
so we're obsessed with them therefore we
所以我们对它们着迷，因此我们
can't even
甚至都做不到
determine whether or not they have any
确定他们是否拥有任何
of the traits that we want we are living
我们正在拥有我们想要的那些特质。
through our own
通过我们自己的
trauma and we're not even selecting them
创伤，而我们甚至都没有选择他们。
typically they are selecting us so we
通常情况下，他们会选择我们，所以我们
end up sliding if you will into a
最后，如果你愿意的话，会滑入一个
relationship that was never right for us
那段关系从来都不适合我们。
to begin with whereas in arranged
首先，在安排好的
marriages you have a true debate
婚姻中存在着真正的争论
happening around whether or not someone
事情的起因似乎与某人有关。
will fit within that with within the
将会符合这个要求。
life of that individual another example
那个人的生活的另一个例子
is why my wife and I in a matchmaking
这就是为什么我和妻子参加相亲的原因
agency we pioneered something that had
我们开创了一种机构模式，这种模式曾经……
never been done at least to our
至少对我们来说，这从未发生过。
knowledge in
知识
matchmaking like Stephen if you were a
如果你像斯蒂芬一样擅长牵线搭桥，那你就是……
client of ours you came you would be the
我们的客户，你来了，你会是……
perfect client at that time right
当时的完美客户，对吧？
because we had many men who were uh
因为我们有很多男人，呃……
incredibly successful professionally and
在专业领域取得了巨大的成功，
felt as if okay what I'm missing is I'm
感觉好像我缺少的就是……
missing love I'm missing partnership so
我怀念爱情，我怀念伴侣关系。
if you came to us as a client instead of
如果您是以客户的身份而不是……的身份来找我们
me saying all right Stephen tell me what
我说，好吧，斯蒂芬，告诉我什么
you want right and you give me this long
你想要正确，你给了我这么长时间
list I know you'd give me a list of like
我知道你会给我一份清单，比如
150 things that you
150件你
want right instead I would say no no no
我想要的是对的，但我会说不不不
you go sit over there I'm not I'm not
你去那边坐，我不坐，我不坐。
even going to talk to you instead let me
甚至想跟你谈谈，而不是让我……
talk to your
和你的
brother let me talk to your
兄弟，让我跟你谈谈。
co-workers let me talk to your exes yes
同事们，让我跟你们的前任聊聊吧，好的。
let me talk to your exes let me get a
让我跟你的前任们聊聊，让我……
360 perspective of who you you are from
360度全方位视角，了解你是谁
the people who you are closest to and I
你最亲近的人和我
would then build out a profile based on
然后根据以下内容建立个人资料
the consensus of what they're telling me
他们告诉我的共识
this is so
这真是太
true I've got a one of my best friends
没错，我有一个最好的朋友
in the world has struggled with a few of
世界上已经与一些……作斗争
my best friends but there's two I'm
我最好的朋友，但有两个，我是
thinking about in particular but one I
特别想到的是我
really want to focus on he's struggled
真的想重点关注他所经历的挣扎
in relationships for the last I'd say 15
在过去的15年里，我一直处于恋爱关系中。
years and every single time he gets in a
多年来，他每次都能进入
relationship as his friend I get that's
我能理解他作为朋友的关系。
not that's not it that's not it and
不，不是那样，不是那样。
every single time he gets with somebody
每次他和别人在一起
else I go that's not it either and I
否则我就只能说那也不是原因，而且我
after this last relationship failed I
上一段感情失败后，我
sat with him and I I'm trying not to
和他坐在一起，我尽量不去想……
like you know intervene too much but I
就像你知道的，干预太多了，但我
said bro I will know I feel like the
兄弟说我会知道我的感觉是
same way that he knew when I'd found the
就像他知道我何时找到了……一样
right one and he would lit if I was to
没错，如果我要的话，他会点燃的。
dump my current partner he would
甩掉我现在的伴侣，他会……
literally reverse the decision yes he
确实，他推翻了之前的决定。
would write an executive order to
会撰写一份行政命令
reverse the decision because he knows
推翻这个决定，因为他知道
that person is exactly what was right
那个人完全正确
for me in the same way I could literally
对我来说，同样的方式，我完全可以
draw a picture I could tell you the
画一幅画，我就可以告诉你
occup ATI the age of the the right
占据 ATI 的年龄，右
person for him based on knowing him and
根据对他的了解，我认为他是一个很棒的人。
him being my best friend for 10 15 years
他是我最好的朋友，我们做了10到15年。
but for some reason he goes for
但不知为何他选择了
everything opposite than that right and
与此相反的一切，没错。
I've always wondered this I've always
我一直都很想知道这个问题。
wondered like should we be picking our
我想知道我们应该如何选择我们的
friends partners for them no I if if as
朋友和伴侣，如果他们没有，我如果如果作为
a society we went back to our nearest
我们回到了离家最近的社会
and dearest family and Social Circle
以及我最亲爱的家人和社交圈
yeah and I want to emphasize the people
是的，我想强调的是人民。
who we TR truly love cuz like not all
我们TR真正爱的人，因为并非所有人
family's family yeah so if we had that
家人，家人，是的，所以如果我们有那个
Circle making the decision for us we
Circle 为我们做出决定
would have much higher satisfaction
满意度会高得多。
rates in marriages without question or
婚姻中的无疑问率或
much higher satisfaction rates in in
满意度要高得多
Partnerships it's because of precisely
正是因为合作关系，才有了现在的局面。
what you
你
said reading a study here it says a 2012
有人说，他读了这里的一份研究报告，报告显示2012年……
study published in the Journal of
发表在《期刊》上的研究
comparative family studies found that
比较家庭研究发现
couples and arranged marriages in
情侣和包办婚姻
collectivist cultures reported similar
集体主义文化也报告了类似情况。
or higher levels of satisfaction over
或更高的满意度
the long term compared to those in love
从长远来看，与恋爱中的人相比
marriages yes yes go back Eli 80% of our
婚姻，是的，回去吧，伊莱，我们80%的人
marriages have a lower level of
婚姻的程度较低
satisfaction today than than than any
今天比以往任何时候都更令人满意
point in in history and and you think
历史上的一个节点，你认为
about even what we were uh you think
关于我们当时的情况，呃，你觉得呢？
about the emphasis that we place on the
关于我们对以下方面的重视
individual this this is something that
这是个人的事情
needs to really be emphasized because
这一点确实需要强调，因为
the the more that we require our partner
我们对合作伙伴的要求越高
to deliver everything to us the higher
把一切都送到我们这里，更高的
their bar becomes the expectation and
他们的酒吧成了人们的期望，
the moment that they're not meeting that
当他们未能满足这一要求时
expectation we're we're not satisfied
我们并不满意。
now they could be delivering on nine out
现在他们有可能在九个出局的情况下兑现承诺。
of 10 things but because our expectation
十件事，但因为我们的期望
is 10 we have low satisfaction because
如果评分为10，我们的满意度会很低，因为……
ultimately that's what satisfaction is
归根结底，这就是满足感。
is satisfaction is really based on our
满意度真的取决于我们
expectation so what do we do about that
那么，我们该如何应对这种期望呢？
because a lot of people will be able to
因为很多人都能
relate to this idea that their partner
这与他们的伴侣的想法有关
is multiple things in their life or that
他们生活中有很多事情，或者说，
they feel like they are expected to be
他们觉得自己应该……
their Partners therapist maybe
他们的伴侣治疗师可能
financier um best
金融家嗯最好
friend uh Sports uh buddy on the weekend
朋友，呃，运动​​，呃，周末的伙伴
to play paddle with um I don't know life
和……一起打板球，我不知道生活
coach Etc some people will feel that
教练等等，有些人会觉得
pressure while they're also trying to
压力之下，他们也在努力
run their own life what' you do about it
他们自己掌控自己的生活，你能怎么办？
because you can't come home and say babe
因为你不能回家说“宝贝”
listen it's over I'm only going to be
听着，一切都结束了，我只会……
your boyfriend from now
从现在起，你的男朋友
on a lot of people people won't like
很多人不喜欢
this but we have to lower our
但我们必须降低我们的
expectation of our partners we really do
我们确实期望我们的合作伙伴这样做。
and and and what I mean by this is first
我的意思是，首先
we have to be begin with determining
我们必须首先确定
what do we want out of our partnership
我们希望从合作关系中获得什么
because if we go back and we don't have
因为如果我们回到过去，而我们却没有
to go back thousands of years we can
我们可以追溯到几千年前。
literally go back to my
真的要回到我的
grandparents the decisions were not am I
祖父母的决定不是我做的。
going to get all 10 things from my
我打算从我那里得到全部10样东西
partner it is three of the the 10 things
合作伙伴，这是十件事中的三件。
and I'll be satisfied with the three of
我会对这三个感到满意。
the 10 things why because I have a full
因为我拥有完整的10个原因
community that I can go to of friends
我可以去的朋友社区
co-workers colleagues people who you
同事、同行、你身边的人
know in my running club that I can go to
我知道在我的跑步俱乐部里，我可以去
for uh for for other facets of my life
至于我生活的其他方面
confidence intellectual stimulation
自信和智力刺激
whatever it may be so that's where it
不管它是什么，所以它就在那里。
begins what what do you want from your
首先要问的是，你想要从你的……中获得什么？
marriage then the next step becomes all
结婚之后，下一步就变成了所有
right are you then prepared to do the
那么，你准备好做这件事了吗？
work required to sustain that
维持这种状态所需的工作
relationship you know uh the the Gans
你知道，这和甘斯的关系有关。
who I know you you've had on the podcast
我知道你之前邀请过你上播客节目。
and are really the foremost experts in
他们是这方面的真正顶尖专家
the world around couples therapy right
夫妻治疗的世界
John and Julie gotman they said
他们说，约翰和朱莉·戈特曼
something to me that was profound when I
对我来说，那件事意义非凡。
was talking to them and that is we're
当时我们正在和他们交谈，那就是我们
all compatible with each
所有部件都与彼此兼容
other and and let that sit in for a
其他的，让它静置一段时间。
second it's like okay what does that
其次，这就好比是“好吧，那是什么意思？”
really mean what it means is
它的真正含义是
that if I were to drop you with another
如果我把你和另一个人一起丢掉的话
human being on a desolate Island and say
一个人被困在荒岛上，然后说
that's it it's just the two of you for
就这样，只有你们两个人了。
the rest of your lives you were going to
你们余生都将……
form a very strong emotional bond and
形成非常牢固的情感纽带
chances are you're going to form a very
你很有可能会形成一个非常
strong physical and sexual Bond right
强大的身体和性纽带
why because you are required there's no
为什么？因为这是必须的，没有。
other outlet but to make it work with
其他出口，但要让它工作起来
them look at
他们看着
today we don't feel like we have to make
今天我们觉得我们不必非得做出什么。
it work there's countless options we can
这样做行得通，我们有无数种选择。
just leave right and and so the this
就这么离开右边，就这样。
notion that we are compatible with
我们与……相容的观念
everyone I think is profound because
我认为每个人都很有深度，因为
what it means is that you can get
这意味着你可以获得
through that you can you can increase
通过这种方式，你可以增加
your satisfaction by putting in the
您的满意是通过投入而实现的
work I um I can totally relate to that I
工作方面，嗯，我完全能理解。
remember working in a call center once
记得曾经在呼叫中心工作过。
upon a time and I was broke and lonely
从前，我身无分文，孤苦伶仃。
and as I worked in this call center it
当我在这家呼叫中心工作时
was late rooms call center in cheet Mill
奇特米尔的晚间客房呼叫中心
in man Chester um I basically like fell
在切斯特，嗯，我基本上喜欢坠落
in love with the girl sat next to me in
我爱上了坐在我旁边的那个女孩。
the call center now listen um I've seen
呼叫中心现在听着，嗯，我已经看到了
her since I think 10 10 years later she
自从我想10年后她就一直和她在一起。
came to one of my meetting greets which
来参加我的一次见面会，
is she's called Rosie I literally she's
她叫罗西，我字面上就是她
probably the first time she realized I
大概是她第一次意识到我
fell in love with her but in the context
我爱上了她，但在那种情况下……
of there not being many options and me
选择不多，而我
being a guy that basically had no other
作为一个基本上别无选择的人
options I wasn't going out to my clubs I
我没有选择去夜店。
couldn't afford it I just fell in love
我买不起，我只是爱上了它
with someone who was in close proximity
与近距离接触的人
and I just was really really into her
我当时真的非常非常喜欢她。
and it shocked me because
这让我很震惊，因为
objectively speaking had I written down
客观地说，我是否写下了
what my type was at that period of my
我那段时间喜欢的类型是什么？
life I wouldn't have written that but
如果是在生活中，我不会写那样的话，但是
just because we were held in close
仅仅因为我们被严密监视
proximity for long enough I found the
长时间的接近让我发现了
the the attraction yes it the attraction
是的，这就是景点。
came to be unfortunately that's not the
可惜的是，事实并非如此。
world we live in and in fact one of my
我们生活的世界，事实上，我的
friends who's struggling the most in
朋友们中谁最艰难
relationships her job is literally to
她的工作就是维系人际关系。
meet people that's like the the base
结识像基地一样的人
premise of her job and she can't find
她的工作前提是她找不到。
anyone MH and I think part of what we're
任何人 MH，我认为我们的一部分是
what what I'm seeing there is we've
我看到的是，我们已经
described with having too many options
形容为选择太多
but what does someone do about that do
但对此人们又能做些什么呢？
they like what's the what's the
他们喜欢什么？什么？
actionable thing to do if you live in
如果你住在……，可以采取的行动
the modern world and you're struggling
现代社会，你却在苦苦挣扎。
to find somebody even though you realize
即使你意识到这一点，也要去找某个人。
that if you were held in a room with
如果你被关在一个房间里，
five total strangers you'd probably fall
五个完全陌生的人，你很可能会爱上他们
in love with one of them yeah it's it's
爱上其中一个，是的，是的
tough right but it always begins with
很难，对吧？但一切都始于……
self and self-awareness and I would
自我和自我意识，以及我会
literally start at well what is my
实际上，一切都从“我的是什么”开始。
attachment that will inform an
附件将告知
incredible amount if she goes back and
如果她回去，那将是一笔巨款。
does the work and realizes that she is
她做了工作，然后意识到自己是
avoidant that will begin to fill in the
回避型人格将开始填补空缺
gaps as to why maybe she's been
关于她为何一直如此，仍存在一些疑问。
emotionally distant relationships why
为什么会出现情感疏离的关系
she feels like she doesn't need anyone
她觉得自己不需要任何人
right why people need to jump an even
这就是为什么人们需要跳跃的原因
higher bar to be in a relationship with
与……建立恋爱关系需要更高的标准
her start with your attachment and
她从你依恋她开始
realize that if you are avoidant or you
意识到如果你是回避型人格或者你
are anxious you can earn a secure
担心自己无法获得一份稳定的收入
attachment and there's work that's
依恋，还有工作是
involved but you can do that and by by
虽然有点复杂，但你可以做到，而且……
the way you can do that without a
你可以不用……就能做到这一点
therapist it's always advisable to go
去看心理咨询师总是明智之举。
with therapist but let's face it the
虽然有治疗师，但说实话……
wait times for therapists the uh the
治疗师的等待时间呃
cost for a therapist they're they're not
治疗师的费用是……他们不是
and also the number of therapists on a
以及治疗师的数量
per capita basis is is decreasing so
按人均计算，这一数字正在下降。
they're not as accessible as often it we
它们不像我们通常认为的那样容易获取。
we make it at the mount to see so that's
我们爬到山顶去看，就是这样。
one is you want to start with self
一是你想从自身做起。
that's one secondly is really get
其次，这真的让人很兴奋。
grounded on the type of relationship
基于关系类型
that you want and the reason why this is
你想要的以及原因如下
important is because therefore you can
重要的是，因此你可以
make it clear what your boundaries are
明确你的底线是什么
when you begin to engage with people
当你开始与人交往时
because I always say that if you don't
因为我总是说，如果你不
assert your boundaries you can take
坚持你的界限，你可以做到
well-intentioned people and turn them
把好心人变成坏人
into bullies just as a result of not
仅仅因为没有……就变成了欺凌者
asserting your boundaries so in order to
划清界限，以便……
know your in order to assert your
了解你才能主张你的
boundaries you have to know your
你必须了解自己的界限
boundaries so that's the second piece is
边界，所以这是第二部分。
beginning to know okay what do I want
开始明白我想要什么
what do I want for example there are
例如，我想要什么？
hundreds of variations of relationships
数百种关系变体
that you could have today my grandmother
今天你本可以拥有我的祖母
right there was one it was committed
就在那里，它被犯下了罪行。
relationship committed marriage until
恋爱关系已定，直至结婚
you die that was it now you don't have
你死了，一切就结束了，你现在什么都没有了。
to be married you could live apart but
结婚后，你们可以分居两地，但是
be together see each other on weekends
周末见面，在一起。
you can decide I want we we don't want
你可以决定我想要我们我们不想要
to have children you can decide like
想要孩子，你可以自己决定。
there are hundreds of variations
有数百种变体
be very clear on what your what you want
务必清楚自己想要什么。
and when I say assert your boundaries is
我说要坚持你的界限，是指
assert what you are interested in right
正确地表达你的兴趣所在。
from the
从
beginning the the these three steps are
首先要完成这三个步骤。
incredibly important I want to talk
非常重要的一点是，我想谈谈
about the different variations of
关于不同变体
relationships and a lot of the sort of
人际关系以及很多其他类型的
myths that keep us held
那些让我们深陷其中的神话
in the the sort of modern idea of what a
在现代观念中，什么是
relationship looks like okay but you
这段关系看起来还不错，但是你
said something there which I which
我在那里说了些什么，
sparked a thought that I had read in
这让我想到我曾经读到过的一件事。
your book um
你的书嗯
when you said till death do us part yes
当你说至死不渝时，是的
I read about this study that says that
我读过一篇关于这项研究的文章，文章说：
cancer research on heterosexual couples
异性恋夫妇的癌症研究
found that if a man becomes terminally
研究发现，如果一名男子患上绝症
ill and his wife becomes the caretaker
他生病了，他的妻子成了他的照护者。
there was a 2.9% separation rate if the
如果分离率为2.9%，
woman is terminally ill and their male
这位女士身患绝症，而他们的男性
partner becomes the caretaker they leave
伴侣成了他们离开时的照顾者。
at a 21% rate which basically means that
利率为21%，这基本上意味着
men are approximately 64% more likely to
男性患病的可能性比女性高约 64%。
separate from a woman woman if the woman
与女人分开，如果女人
gets sick yes and that was on page 48 of
是的，她生病了，那件事发生在第48页。
your new book keep love yes what the
你的新书《保持爱》是的，什么？
[__] is going on there that is alarming
那里到底发生了什么？太可怕了。
shocking and it was so alarming and
太令人震惊了，也太令人担忧了。
shocking I had to include the study in
令人震惊的是，我不得不把这项研究也纳入其中。
the book for for me and and I wrote this
这本书对我来说意义非凡，我写了这本书。
in the in the chapter around love is
在关于爱情的章节中是
conditional and we have to understand
条件性的，我们需要理解
that the myth that presents itself is
所呈现的神话是
that love is unconditional it is you
那份爱是无条件的，那就是你。
know if you find the right person
知道你是否找到了合适的人
there's no condition
没有条件
that could be true with your children
你的孩子也可能出现这种情况。
right your child could go do something
你的孩子可以去做点什么了。
heinous and I believe there could or
令人发指，而且我相信可能或
would still be love for them but that's
对他们来说，那依然是爱，但那只是……
not the case with our partners and for
我们的合作伙伴并非如此，而且
us to be aware that there are conditions
我们需要意识到存在一些条件。
when we go into these relationships
当我们进入这些关系时
that's the most important so it's almost
这是最重要的，所以几乎
a warning sign in particular to women in
这对女性来说尤其是一个警示信号
that chapter to say there there are
那一章要说明的是，有
conditions and unfortunately when people
情况，不幸的是，当人们
have gone through and interviewed these
已经审阅并采访了这些人
men who have left the the the women at
离开的女人们
at at on on their deathbed and even the
在临终之际，甚至在临终前
women because it's 2.9% of women leave
因为女性离职率仅为2.9%。
men even the women who've left the men
男人，甚至包括那些离开男人的女人
what they will say is that they're no
他们会说，他们不是。
longer getting fill in the blank they're
不再填空
no longer getting the emotional intimacy
不再获得情感上的亲密感
they're no longer getting the physical
他们不再接受体检
intimacy they're no longer getting the
他们不再拥有亲密关系了
you know you fill in the blank and as a
你知道你要填空，而且作为一个
result of no longer getting this thing
不再收到这东西的结果
and the thing is the
问题是……
condition they're out so why men though
条件是他们出局了，所以为什么男人要出局呢？
600 they're over 600% more likely to
他们发生这种情况的可能性高出600%以上
leave a termin Le old partner than women
留下一个终结者 Le 老伴侣比女人
are yeah you know there's a
是的，你知道，那里有一个
disproportionate amount of the
不成比例的
relationship that's placed on the
建立在……之上的关系
physical side of the relationship right
这段关系中的生理层面是正确的
sex sex yeah you're like Paul say
性，性，是啊，你就像保罗说的那样。
actually what it is well it's it's not
实际上它是什么？嗯，它不是。
all about sex right it's not all about
一切都与性有关，对吧？但并非一切都与性有关。
sex but what it typically means is that
性，但它通常意味着
there is a low level of satisfaction in
满意度较低
the relationship and as a result of
这种关系以及由此产生的
and the low level of satisfaction could
而低满意度可能是
come
来
from not having enough sex or not having
性生活不足或缺乏
the sex that they like it could have
他们喜欢的性爱方式可能
could be from there's a you know there's
可能是因为你知道那里有
no respect they don't feel like there's
他们不尊重人，他们感觉不到被尊重。
equity in the relationship whatever it
无论如何，关系中的公平性
may be but because there's already a low
或许如此，但因为目前已经很低了。
level of satisfaction when they go into
他们进入时的满意度
a place where the the the the partner is
伴侣所在的地方
terminally ill they're more ready to
身患绝症的人更容易……
leave right this is normally what you
向右走，这通常是你应该做的。
see what you see happen when you see um
看看你看到什么之后会发生什么
a partner leave another partner where
一位合伙人离开另一位合伙人
you see infidelity happening is you see
你看到不忠行为发生，就是你看到
that there was already a low level of
已经存在较低水平的
satisfaction the level of satisfaction
满意度
in the relationships not only dictate
在人际关系中，不仅决定着
the survivability of the relationship it
这段关系的存续能力
dictates the survivability of us there
这决定了我们在那里的生存能力。
was a study done James coin this this
詹姆斯·科因做过一项研究
one blew my
一个炸了我的
mind he pulled 200 patients who had
记住，他抽调了200名病人。
congenital heart disease right so not
先天性心脏病，所以不是
terminally ill but as close as you get
身患绝症，但已接近极限
to terminally ill and he was able to
他身患绝症，却依然能够
look at the 200 and he broke down the
看看那200，他把一切都分解开了。
group based on those who have a high
根据那些拥有高……的人群划分的群体
level of satisfaction and those who have
满意度以及那些拥有
a low level of satisfaction in their
对他们的满意度较低
relationship two years later the couples
两年后，这对情侣的恋情告一段落。
who had a high level of satisfaction the
那些对现状感到高度满意的人
person in that partnership who had
该合伙关系中的某人
congenital heart failure you know what
先天性心脏衰竭，你知道吗？
they died about 11% of the time so 11%
他们的死亡率约为11%，所以是11%。
they died but those who had a low level
他们死了，但那些低水平的人也死了。
of satisfaction two years later
两年后的满意度
45% of them had
其中45%的人有
died think about that little greater
死了，想想那一点点更大
than three times the likelihood of death
死亡可能性是原来的三倍以上
because of the low level of satisfaction
由于满意度低
in the relationship so the satisfaction
在恋爱关系中，满意度
in the relationship is the key and this
关系的关键在于这一点。
is part of what I've been trying to
这是我一直试图做的事情的一部分
drive in this book and a lot of my
这本书的驱动力以及我的很多其他想法
messaging is that we place too much
传递的信息是，我们投入了太多。
value on
价值
longevity it's ridiculous when I sit
寿命长短简直荒谬，我坐着的时候就觉得不可思议。
down for interviews typically the top
面试时通常会优先考虑顶尖的面试官。
see and thank you for not asking me this
谢谢你没问我这个问题
the typically the first two or third
通常是前两个或第三个
question is Paul how so you've been
问题是保罗，你最近怎么样？
married for how long how long have you
结婚多久了？
married and the idea is that because
已婚，而且这个想法是因为
I've been married for 23 plus years that
我结婚已经超过23年了。
I'm successful in my marriage it's
我的婚姻很成功。
ridiculous it's ridiculous the question
这个问题太荒谬了。
should be how satisfied are you in your
你对你的工作/生活有多满意？
marriage or in your partnership and so
婚姻或伴侣关系等等
we can't we have to stop putting
我们不能停止这样做
emphasis U on on the longevity and
重点在于U的寿命和
really focus on the satisfaction how
真正关注满意度如何
satisfied are you in your marriage
你对你的婚姻满意吗？
Stephen
史蒂芬
this
这
[Music]
[音乐]
[Laughter]
[笑声]
is I hate you fing this question no no I
我讨厌你问这个问题，不不，我
am so the reason why I your wife and we
我就是你妻子和我们在一起的原因。
got her answer before so we'll just
之前已经得到她的答复了，所以我们就……
compare yeah you tell me what she said
对比一下，你告诉我她说了什么
you sure you want to know on on
你确定你想知道吗？
air what the reason why I hate trying to
空气是什么？我讨厌尝试的原因是什么？
answer a question like this is because
回答这类问题的原因
so many people are say oh I don't
很多人都说，哦，我不。
believe I don't believe what this guy
我不相信这家伙说的话
say
说
truly hand on my heart word to my
我发自内心地向我保证
children I have the highest level of
我的孩子拥有最高水平的
satisfaction with Jill you know with my
我对吉尔很满意，你知道我的
best friend today than ever ever ever
今天比以往任何时候都更像最好的朋友
ever ever ever and I think the reason
永远永远永远，而且我认为原因
for this is because of the enormous
这是因为巨大的
amount of work that we put in you know a
你知道，我们投入了大量的工作。
lot of people don't realize is that when
很多人没有意识到的是，当
I read a
我读了一篇
stat Jill is typically right next to me
统计员吉尔通常就在我旁边。
last night literally last night we're in
昨晚，真的是昨晚，我们……
the bed and we are talking about the
床，我们正在谈论的是
history of marriage and we're debating
婚姻史，我们正在辩论
Clovis the first of Franks and how he
克洛维一世，法兰克国王，以及他如何
made an impact in relationships we're
对我们的人际关系产生了影响
always discussing these topics and as a
总是讨论这些话题，而且
result of having the conversation around
围绕这个话题展开的讨论的结果
these topics it helps us to be open it
谈论这些话题有助于我们保持开放的态度。
helps us to dialogue it helps us to
它有助于我们进行对话，它有助于我们……
debate it helps us to have doubt it
辩论有助于我们产生怀疑。
helps to have trust and autonomy and
有助于建立信任和自主权，
therefore it helps us to have this
因此，拥有这个对我们很有帮助。
strong level of communication and
较强的沟通能力和
emotional intimacy that then feeds into
情感上的亲密感，进而促进
all aspects of our life into our sex
我们将生活的方方面面都融入到我们的性生活中。
life right into our ability to parent
生命直至我们为人父母的能力
our our our children into our work right
我们的孩子也应该参与到我们的工作中来。
all of this feeds from having the strong
这一切都源于拥有强大的力量。
connection so the satisfaction is Sky
连接，所以满意度是天空
High and this is a topic that it was
高，这是一个值得探讨的话题。
funny because I was like I know Stephen
真搞笑，因为我当时就想，我认识史蒂芬。
does the research so he could have asked
他做了调查，所以他本来可以问的。
Jill I am very confident Jill would say
吉尔，我很有信心吉尔会这么说。
the same the reason why is because we
原因相同，因为我们
always check in with each with each
务必与每个人进行确认。
other we're always check how are you
我们总是会关心你的情况。
feeling right now right are do we feel
此刻的感觉，我们感觉如何？
like we're going in the right direction
感觉我们正朝着正确的方向前进。
you know when I think about do you have
你知道，当我想到你是否拥有……的时候，我就知道了。
strong satisfaction in your relationship
对你们的关系感到非常满意
the questions that always come to mind
脑海中总是浮现出这些问题。
is do you feel safe with your partner do
你觉得和伴侣在一起安全吗？
you feel safe do you feel like you can
你觉得安全吗？你觉得你能做到吗？
express your true vulnerability to them
向他们袒露你内心真正的脆弱
right that's one secondly is do you feel
对，这是第一点。第二点是，你觉得呢？
respected you know with John gottman's
你知道，约翰·戈特曼很受人尊敬
research number one you know he saw he
第一项研究你知道他看到了他
could predict divorce at 99 plus perc or
可以预测离婚率达到99%以上，或者
90 plus perc because of contempt or
因蔑视或
disrespect in the relationship so do you
在这段关系中，不尊重也是如此。
feel like you have
感觉你拥有
respect another one are you optimistic
尊重他人，你乐观吗？
about where the relationship is going
关于这段关系的走向
which suggests how much effort and work
这表明需要付出多少努力和工作
your part is placing in the relationship
你在这段关系中扮演的角色是付出。
so many of us are hopeless about the the
我们当中许多人对……感到绝望
future is because we know our our our
未来在于我们了解我们的未来
partner's not doing anything to to to to
伴侣什么也没做
further the relationship so are you
进一步发展这段关系，你也是如此。
nurturing the
培育
relationship many of us are quick to
我们许多人很快就能建立关系
focus on self-love now and nurturing
现在专注于自爱和滋养
ourselves but the question is how much
我们自己，但问题是，我们能做到什么程度？
nurture are you giving to the
你给予了什么关爱？
relationship because that's a separate
因为那是另一种关系。
entity you talking there about sort of
你刚才说的实体是指某种东西
the pillow talk with Jill about
与吉尔的枕边细语
relationships and constantly it being
关系以及持续不断的关系
part of the conversation in your
对话的一部分
household one of the things that I was I
家庭是我当时所做的事情之一
was pondering as you said that is should
我一直在思考，正如你所说，这应该
we spend more time talking about the
我们花更多时间谈论……
relationship with our partner because if
与伴侣的关系，因为如果
I think about the relationship I'm in
我会思考我目前的这段感情。
now we spend a lot of time talking about
现在我们花了很多时间谈论……
the relationship um whereas in previous
这种关系，嗯，而在以前
relationships it was kind of the
关系就是这样
elephant in the room all the time so we
房间里的大象一直都那么显而易见，所以我们
never really had an opportunity or a
从未真正有过机会或
forum
论坛
to ask those questions right about unmet
要问清楚那些关于未满足需求的问题。
needs or are you happy etc etc and I
需要什么，或者你是否快乐等等等等，而我
just think that probably the missing
想想看，那可能就是缺失的部分。
piece for a lot of people in
很多人认为这是一首……
relationships is they just don't have a
关系就是他们之间没有……
a space in their week where they sit and
他们每周都会抽出一些时间坐下来，
talk about the relationship itself yes
谈谈这段关系本身吧，是的。
so so yes should we be speaking more
所以，是的，我们应该多谈谈吗？
absolutely would it save many
当然可以节省很多钱
Partnerships absolutely would it
合作关系绝对会如此。
increase the satisfaction absolutely do
提高满意度绝对没错
we not have enough time I would say this
我觉得我们时间不够。
becomes our copout like we're so busy
成了我们的借口，好像我们很忙似的。
with life think about this I'm so busy
想想生活，我太忙了。
with life that I can't give the person
我无法给予那个人的生命
that I plan to spend the rest of my life
我计划度过余生
with time right we have to
时机成熟时，我们必须
prioritize our relationship with our
优先考虑我们与客户的关系
partner we have to prioritize this we
合作伙伴，我们必须优先考虑这件事。
have to figure out when we can build in
我们得想想什么时候可以开始建设。
time to talk and we have to actually
是时候谈谈了，我们必须认真谈谈。
talk about the real things you know I'm
谈谈真正的事情，你知道我是
willing to bet that most men don't even
我敢打赌，大多数男人甚至都不知道。
realize especially in in in in
尤其是在……中意识到
heterosexual relationships
异性恋关系
heteronormative uh relationships most
异性恋规范的呃关系最
men don't even realize that their
男人们甚至没有意识到他们的
partner doesn't even orgasm when they
伴侣甚至在性交时都没有达到高潮
have sex like you look at the orgasm Gap
做爱就像你看着高潮一样。
and you say oh my God you have men
然后你说，哦我的天哪，你有男人
orgasming at 95% and women at roughly
男性性高潮发生率为95%，女性性高潮发生率约为
65% maybe a little bit higher in in
65% 或许还要更高一些
these committed relationships that means
这些承诺关系意味着
that there's a significant percentage
有相当一部分人
that never orgasm I bet you their
我敢打赌他们永远不会达到性高潮
partner has no idea no noide idea why
伴侣完全不知道为什么
because there's there hasn't been a
因为一直没有
conversation around it now the issue is
现在围绕这个问题的讨论是……
a two-way street it's not only the man's
这是双向的，不仅仅是男人的事。
issue that he needs to be aware and have
他需要意识到并了解的问题
the conversation but she also needs to
对话，但她也需要
be able to tell him but you know why she
能告诉他，但你知道为什么她
probably doesn't tell him
可能不会告诉他。
because she doesn't want herur his
因为她不想要他的
feelings she has not she's not been
她没有那种感觉，她一直没有
having an orgasm for the last 10 years
过去十年一直有性高潮
so she feels like if she brings it up
所以她觉得如果她提起这件事
now it's going to be detrimental to the
现在这将对……造成不利影响
relationship so she's trying to protect
所以她想保护这段关系
him right right and or she's embarrassed
他是对的，或者她感到尴尬。
or whatever it may be he is completely
或者不管是什么，他完全
oblivious and unaware and they never
他们浑然不觉，毫无察觉，而且他们从未
talk about their sex life a matter of
谈论他们的性生活是件很平常的事
fact their sex life is a script which is
事实上，他们的性生活就像一部剧本。
typically most people's sex life it's
通常来说，大多数人的性生活是这样的
just a script it's two or three moves
只是一个脚本，两三个步骤而已。
that are done man orgasms women woman
男人高潮女人
doesn't that's
难道不是吗？
it think of how powerful it would be if
想想如果……那该有多强大
they could just simply have dialogue and
他们完全可以进行对话，
discussion it's hard to start that
讨论很难开始。
behavior though I imagine in your Rel
虽然我猜想你的关系中会有这种行为
reltionship with Jill you guys are
你们和吉尔的关系
pretty Advanced right so if you're level
相当高级了吧，所以如果你是这个级别的话
one what's level one in karate is it
一、空手道一级是什么？
like a white belt oh yeah white belt if
就像白带一样，哦，对，白带。
you're like a white belt in this stuff
你在这方面就像个新手。
where there been 10 years you and your
过去十年里，你和你的
partner just really don't talk about
伴侣真的不怎么谈论这件事。
these things it's kind of always been
这些事情一直以来都是如此。
the elephant in the room loads of words
房间里的大象，一堆废话
have been unsa what would you suggest as
我一直不太清楚，你有什么建议吗？
like a good starting point to to get the
就像一个好的起点，可以……
ball rolling in this Direction all right
球正朝着这个方向滚动，一切正常。
I like this so baby steps so in the book
我喜欢这种方式，所以要循序渐进，就像书里写的那样。
I talk about how we have to normalize
我谈到了我们如何必须正常化。
the fact that we will be attracted to
我们会被吸引的事实
people other than our partner no one
除了我们的合作伙伴之外，没有人
wants to talk about that no one wants to
想谈谈没人想谈的事
talk about you know it's just my partner
你知道，就说说我的伴侣吧
that's it I'm not looking at anyone else
就这样，我没再看其他人了。
right are you attracted to other people
你是否会被其他人吸引？
oh my Sten come on man are
哦，我的天哪，斯坦，拜托，伙计们
you AB but but absolutely absolutely and
你AB，但是绝对绝对和
not only that and there are different
不仅如此，还有不同的
forms of Attraction you know there's
你知道，吸引力有很多种形式。
physical there's there's sexual
生理上的，有性方面的
attraction there's there's emotional
吸引力，有情感上的。
attraction but to your question of what
吸引力，但对于你提出的“什么”这个问题，我不太确定。
do you do if you're level one in your
如果你是一级玩家，你会怎么做？
relationship is you start with these
关系始于这些
baby steps so Jill and myself we had to
循序渐进，所以吉尔和我不得不
start around this topic of Attraction
就从吸引力这个话题开始吧。
because I had a very hard
因为我经历了一段非常艰难的时期。
time just thinking about my wife being
只是静静地想着我的妻子
attracted to someone else I couldn't
因为喜欢上了别人，我无法……
fathom it the jealousy the anxiety the
领悟其中的嫉妒和焦虑
anxiousness I have an anxious attachment
我患有焦虑型依恋障碍。
style so so it just it was just fear
风格就是这样，所以，它只是，只是恐惧
right and there there many different
对，那里有很多不同的
things that that that that you can do
你可以做的事情
but I'll give two one is that you just
但我会给出两点，第一点是你刚刚
have to normalize that these behaviors
必须将这些行为正常化。
are a part of our Human Experience well
是我们人类体验的重要组成部分
all have physical attraction some of us
我们中的一些人都有生理吸引力。
will have sexual attraction some of us
我们中的一些人会产生性吸引力。
will have emotional attraction to people
会对人产生情感上的吸引
who are not our partners if anyone
如果有人不是我们的合作伙伴，请告知。
denies it they are lying okay this is
他们否认，他们在撒谎，好吧，这是
one we have to normalize this we
我们必须将这一点正常化。
normalize it then we begin having
将其规范化，然后我们就开始拥有
conversations around it so what my wife
围绕这件事的讨论，所以我的妻子
and I used to or did around this and she
我过去常常或曾经这样做过，而她
uh will hate me for saying this but I
呃，你们可能会因为我说这话而讨厌我，但是……
wrote I wrote this in the book so it's
我在书里写了，所以是这样的。
it's it's cool is um we started talking
这很酷，嗯，我们开始聊天了。
about celebrities easy low-level way
关于名人的简单低级方法
people who are arm length distance who
与自己保持一定距离的人
do you find attracted blah blah blah I
你觉得……吸引你吗？
saw that my wife as does I think
我看到我妻子也这么认为。
99.999% of uh women and Men loves Idris
99.999%的女性和男性都喜欢伊德里斯
Elba she's like Idris is is is is it to
艾尔巴就像伊德里斯一样，是的，是的，是的
the point where I was like will you
我当时就想，你愿意吗？
leave me for I think she will leave me
离开我吧，因为我觉得她会离开我。
for it's like she will definitely leave
因为她好像肯定会离开。
me for this man but we begin having
我为这个男人感到高兴，但我们开始……
conversations around it it becomes a bit
围绕它的讨论变得有点
of a joke right it is embedded in our in
一个笑话，对吧？它就蕴含在我们的内心深处。
in the normalization of it and then I
在规范化过程中，然后我
begin to do what I call taking my
开始做我所谓的“拿走我的”
thought to court take your thoughts to
考虑将你的想法带到法庭
court right whereas I would identify
法庭权利，而我会认同
okay what is the issue what's the
好的，问题是什么？
emotion it's actually fear if Jill's
如果吉尔的情绪实际上是恐惧，那
talking about someone else she was with
谈论着和她在一起的其他人。
it was it was fear but then I and then
那是一种恐惧，但后来我，然后
then I then I draw on that fear what am
然后我，然后我利用那种恐惧，我是什么？
I in fear of I'm in fear of her of her
我害怕她，我害怕她
leaving me she's just going to leave me
她要离开我了，她就要离开我了。
right but then take that thought to
没错，但请把这个想法……
court what are the facts that can that
法庭可以依据哪些事实来做出判决？
that what are the facts that I have to
我掌握的事实是什么？
support or discredit those feelings well
支持或否定这些感受
I've been with Jill for 20 plus years
我和吉尔在一起超过20年了。
right she has never we have a high level
对，她从来没有，我们有一个很高的水平
of satisfaction it's normal to have
感到满意是正常的。
attraction right so you take your
吸引力对吧，所以你采取你的
thoughts to court and then you could
考虑上法庭，然后你就可以
begin to recalibrate your perspective on
开始重新调整你对……的看法
the thing so it gets to the point where
事情发展到这个地步……
do you know that every
你知道吗，每一个
anniversary Jill gets the biggest
周年纪念日，吉尔得到了最大的
bouquet of flowers
一束鲜花
from Idris
来自伊德里斯
Elba I write love Idis Elba so I I'm I'm
埃尔巴，我写爱伊迪斯·埃尔巴，所以我，我是，我是
writing so I've now it's now it's moved
写完之后，现在它已经移动了。
to a point where I couldn't even stand
到了我甚至都站不起来的地步。
this idea to now it's it's so normalized
这个想法现在已经非常普遍了。
I'm I'm it's jokes about it so so it's
我，我，这是关于它的笑话，所以，就是这样。
very important for us to normalize have
对我们来说，实现正常化非常重要。
these conversations take our thoughts to
这些对话引导我们思考
court and if we are and we have to
法庭，如果我们是，而且我们必须……
realize this and I wrote about this in
我意识到了这一点，并且我写过关于这一点的文章。
the book is that it is also
这本书也是
healthy to have doubts about your
对你的某些方面抱有怀疑是健康的
relationship we're told that if you're
我们被告知，如果你是这种关系，
in the greatest
在最
relationship if you found your soulmate
如果你找到了灵魂伴侣，你们的关系会如何发展？
you should never have doubts myth myth
你不应该对神话产生怀疑。
right it's healthy to have doubts but
没错，有疑虑是健康的，但是
there are healthy doubts and there's
既有健康的怀疑，也有……
unhealthy doubts if it is a doubt that
如果怀疑本身就是一种不健康的怀疑，那么这种怀疑就是
is
是
about uh the growth of your
关于你的成长
relationship that's healthy to express
表达健康的恋爱关系
that if it is a doubt that is predicated
如果这是一个基于前提的疑问
in your own fear or your anxieties your
在你自身的恐惧或焦虑中，你的
traumas that's that's that's unhealthy
创伤，那就是，那就是，那是不健康的。
so to know that informs you know how how
所以，了解这一点就能让你知道如何操作。
how how how Jill and I have have tackled
我和吉尔是如何应对的
that idea of let's normalize a
那种“让我们把……正常化”的想法
conversation is this a healthy doubt it
这段对话是否健康，我对此表示怀疑。
is let's build this into to to our
让我们把这个融入到我们的
relationship so Jill so uh I know jills
关系，所以吉尔，所以呃，我认识吉尔
adors ID Ela and she knows I would leave
爱拉 ID，她知道我会离开
her for Beyonce yeah I mean that's
她是为了碧昂斯，是的，我的意思是，那就是
fair yeah I I just I can just imagine
好吧，我简直可以想象。
that I've got a certain type of listener
我拥有特定类型的听众
who is
谁是
more how would you word
你会怎么措辞？
it advanced in terms of the like belt
它在类似腰带方面取得了进步
you know when I talked about white belts
你知道，我之前谈到白带的时候
and black belts more advanced in their
以及更高级的黑带选手
curiosity their um Intrigue their
他们的好奇心，嗯，他们的兴趣
willingness to like develop and evolve
乐于发展和演变
in the relationship I would bet and this
在这段关系中，我敢打赌，而且
is stereotyping I understand that it's
我理解这是刻板印象。
typically women more than men that are
通常情况下，女性比男性更容易出现这种情况。
like more open-minded to like learn to
更开放包容，乐于学习
grow to deepen the bond I think it's t
我认为这会加深彼此的联系。
typically women more than men I would
通常情况下，女性比男性更倾向于这样做。
Hazard a guess that it's more women
我猜想女性比较多。
buying your books than men yes and and
是的，而且
I'd Hazard a guess that when I make
我大胆猜测，当我……
conversations about love and
关于爱情和对话
relationship it's typically not always
关系通常并非总是如此
because I can kind of see the numbers
因为我大概能看到这些数字。
but typically more women that are trying
但通常情况下，尝试的女性更多。
to learn to deepen their relationships
学习如何加深彼此的关系
so I imagine there's a certain person in
所以我认为其中肯定有某个人
my audience that sat there thinking I
我的听众坐在那里想着我
want to do this I want to have these
我想做这件事，我想要这些
conversations with my partner I want to
我想和我的伴侣进行一些对话
take down some of these walles and start
拆掉一些墙，然后开始
talking about the lack of orgasms I've
谈到我缺乏性高潮的问题
had in the last couple of years I want
过去几年里，我想要
to talk about x y and Zed but I know if
谈谈x、y和Zed，但我知道如果
I bring this conversation up to Dave
我把这件事跟戴夫提起了。
Dave's gonna like think I'm weird he's
戴夫肯定会觉得我很奇怪，他
gonna like roll his eyes and like put
他会翻个白眼，然后……
the football back on and um and I feel a
足球比赛重新开始了，嗯，我感觉……
sense of dissatisfaction in this
这种不满情绪
relationship but because we just don't
关系，但因为我们就是不……
have a bridge of communication I feel
我觉得我们之间有沟通的桥梁。
like I'm faced with a choice now do I
我现在面临一个选择，对吗？
just leave this guy or do I just stick
我该离开这个人，还是继续待下去？
tolerate it and put up with this and
容忍它，忍受它。
that like first step to Bridging the Gap
那就像是弥合差距的第一步
what is it do I turn the football off
怎么关掉足球？
and scream at him do I do I send him the
然后对他大喊大叫，我该怎么做？我该怎么把他送走？
link to this podcast I think that's
我想这就是这个播客的链接。
probably the best option I think it's
我觉得这可能是最好的选择。
just keep sharing the podcast I think I
我觉得只要继续分享播客就行了。
think sharing the podcast with everyone
想想如何与大家分享播客
you know I think is probably the I'm
你知道，我觉得可能是我
joking no no no no no no
开玩笑的，不不不不不不
no laughing I was like I was with you I
别笑，我当时就像和你在一起一样。
was like this is this is it but I
当时的感觉就像，就是这样，就是这样，但是我
thought it's really pushing this yeah
我觉得这真的有点过头了。
yeah he said it five times the
是的，他说了五遍。
link
关联
truly this is the first step uh so say
这确实是第一步，所以这么说吧。
it's uh it's uh it's lah and Dave yeah
呃，呃，呃，啦，还有戴夫，是的
okay L's listening to us right now and
好的，L现在正在听我们说话。
she wants to deepen her emotional
她想加深自己的情感
connection with her partner Dave what
她与伴侣戴夫的关系是什么
does she do she sends Dave a link to
她会给戴夫发链接吗？
this podcast and she says let's listen
这个播客，她说，我们来听听吧。
to this together let's have a date night
为了共同实现这个目标，让我们一起度过一个约会之夜吧。
let's listen to this together and let's
我们一起来听听吧。
just talk about what's happening you
你就说说你正在经历的事情吧。
know what I've noticed with um with one
我知道我注意到他和一个人之间有什么关系。
of the shows that I co-host mared at
我共同主持的节目都失败了
First Sight UK what I'm so proud about
First Sight UK 让我感到无比自豪
is I'm stopped all the time by men and
我总是被男人拦住，
they'll say Paul I watch your show with
他们会说：“保罗，我和你一起看你的节目。”
my partner and our kids watch it as well
我的伴侣和孩子们也看。
and we debate what you're saying and
我们会就你所说的话进行辩论，
sometimes we disagree with you but
有时我们可能会和你意见不一致，但是
sometimes we agree with you and I think
有时我们同意你的观点，我认为
this is what we need because just
这就是我们需要的，因为仅仅
talking about it and having the
谈论它并拥有
conversation around it helps to
围绕这个话题的讨论很有帮助
contribute to awareness which puts you
有助于提高人们的意识，这会让你……
on the path to developing skills which
在发展技能的道路上，
then allows you to begin to heal and
然后让你开始疗愈，
ultimately that's what therapy is
归根结底，这就是治疗的本质。
therapy is healing and so having the
治疗具有疗愈作用，因此接受治疗是有益的。
dialogue based on this podcast based on
基于本播客的对话
a book based on a television show is
一本根据电视节目改编的书
truly not just a first step that's a a
这不仅仅是第一步，而是一个
significant step towards your black belt
迈向黑带的重要一步
I am thinking about the history of
我正在思考历史……
relationships I often wonder how many of
我常常想知道，我究竟有多少段关系……
the rules of relationships that we've
我们所遵循的关系规则
been handed by Society are now invalid
由社会移交的现已失效
or maybe we're never valid so you know
或许我们永远都不算有效，你知道的。
we have these sort of constructs of like
我们有这类结构，比如
marriage and monogamy and um even like
婚姻、一夫一妻制，甚至还有……
heterosexuality all these things that
异性恋以及所有这些事情
have been passed to us through religion
通过宗教传承给我们的
and through history I was looking at
纵观历史，我一直在观察
some stats about marriage and it says
一些关于婚姻的统计数据显示：
that in 2019 marriage rates for opposite
2019年异性婚姻率
sex couples fell to their lowest on
性生活夫妻数量降至最低点
record since
自创纪录以来
1862 that's in the UK and in the US
1862年，英国和美国都是如此。
marriage rates have been declining since
自那以后，结婚率一直在下降。
the early
早期
1970s I I'm not married but I spend a
1970年代 我还没结婚，但我花了很多时间
lot of time thinking about whether I
我花了很多时间思考我是否
should be or not I actually had a
应该还是不应该？我其实有过
conversation recently with my partner
最近和我的伴侣进行了一次谈话
where I said do you want to get married
我问你，你想结婚吗？
and it was abundantly clear that she
很明显，她
does want to get married but then I
确实想结婚，但是后来我
asked why and really it seems like it
问为什么，看起来确实如此。
was really just more for the wedding
其实主要是为了婚礼
than
比
then for some kind of legal contract
然后，就某种法律合同而言
that we sign with the government so I'm
我们与政府签署了协议，所以我
I'm I'm I'm really wondering based on
我真的很想知道基于
everything we know about history and the
我们所知道的关于历史的一切
tradeoffs of marriage should I be
婚姻的权衡取舍我应该如何看待？
getting married yes because your partner
是的，因为你的伴侣会结婚
wants to is that reing enough but but
想要的是，这样就足够了吗？但是
here all right so um I think the
好的，嗯，我想
institution of
机构
marriage what you're going to see this
婚姻，你会看到这个
is my my my prediction is is that
我的预测是……
because nuclear families what do you
因为核心家庭怎么办？
mean by nuclear family so having um to
所谓核心家庭，就是有……
well it's interesting there's there's
嗯，这很有意思。
different perspectives now on nuclear
现在人们对核能的看法有所不同。
family but I look at it as you have two
家人，但我认为你有两个。
partners and children and that creates
伴侣和孩子，这造成了
the nuclear
核能
family that becomes an economic unit
家庭成为经济单位
which drives a
这驱动着
society and as that has disappeared
社会，以及随之消失的这一切
there's been less of a base
基本面有所减弱。
to drive Society per many researchers so
许多研究人员认为，推动社会发展至关重要。
as a result what I believe is going to
因此，我认为将会发生
happen as we see right now in Singapore
就像我们现在在新加坡看到的那样。
as we see right now in China as we see
正如我们现在在中国看到的那样，我们看到
right now in Japan you're going to see
现在在日本，你会看到
government heavily involved in
政府深度参与
incentivizing marriage and marriage is
鼓励婚姻和婚姻是
already incentivized right now in terms
目前已经获得了激励。
of uh you know tax benefits uh being
你知道，税收优惠……
able to um uh you know leave assets
能够留下资产
to your partner leave assets to family
让你的伴侣把资产留给家人
members so as a result of the decrease
成员数量因此减少
of marriage and decrease of of nuclear
婚姻和核能的减少
families you will see government step up
家庭方面，你会看到政府介入。
even more to incentivize so you're going
为了激励你，我们还要做更多。
to see all types of benefits being
看到各种类型的好处
thrown at people to to to to get married
扔给人们是为了让他们结婚
you know especially as you not only see
你知道，尤其当你不仅看到
marriage rates decline but as you also
结婚率下降，但正如你所说
see birth rates declining as they as
看到出生率下降，因为它们
they are now your question around what
现在，你的问题是关于什么？
what what should you do is that um this
你应该怎么做呢？嗯……
is a question around
这是一个关于……的问题
values and this is a question that I
价值观，而这正是我要问的问题。
believe is very important to have early
相信这一点在早期非常重要。
on now I was saying you know when you
刚才我正说你知道当你
meet someone you should lay out exactly
遇到你应该明确说明的人。
what you want this is a very important
你想要什么？这非常重要。
question to have early early on now in
现在就应该尽早提出这个问题
terms of where you where you are with
就你目前所处的位置而言
your partner I would say that if she is
我会说，如果你的伴侣是
for if she is Pro Pro
如果她是 Pro Pro
this and you were indifferent sounds
这和你漠不关心的声音
like it feels like you're indifferent
感觉就像你漠不关心一样
not anti but indifferent yeah I think
不是反对，而是漠不关心，是的，我想。
I'm I'm somewhat agnostic um to it
我对此持某种程度的不可知论态度。
however I can call out a bunch of
然而，我可以列举出一大堆
downsides to getting married really like
结婚的缺点真的很有意思
uh well again I don't know because I'm
呃，好吧，我还是不知道，因为我……
not married so all the married people
未婚人士，所以所有已婚人士
are like screaming at me right now I
他们现在就像在对我大喊大叫一样。
know this because they DM me they've
我知道这一点是因为他们私信告诉我他们已经……
been dming me for many many years since
多年来一直有人私信我
I started the D Co because in some of
我创办D公司是因为在某些情况下
those early episodes I was really like
在最初的几集里，我真的很喜欢
not I was really quite against it but um
不，我其实很反对，但是……
over time I've kind of developed my
随着时间的推移，我逐渐发展出了我的
thinking here I just wonder I can't
我在想，我怎么可能做不到呢？
understand the first principles as to
理解关于以下方面的基本原理
why having a like government or
为什么需要一个类似的政府？
religious contract with somebody is
与某人签订的宗教契约是
going to increase the probability of
这将增加以下概率：
success in the union of Love um there's
在爱情的结合中取得成功，嗯，有
obviously the issue with the prenup
显然，婚前协议存在问题。
situation I actually don't have this
我实际上并没有这种情况。
concern with my my partner so I think
担心我的伴侣，所以我认为
she's um I think you've met her you
她……嗯，我想你见过她吧？
you've met her yeah yeah uh yeah from a
你见过她，是啊是啊，嗯是啊，从一个
distance yes from a distance yeah I I
距离，是的，从远处看，是的，我
don't a concern that she's going to try
别担心她会尝试
and bankrupt me or that I might try and
让我破产，或者我可能会尝试……
bankrupt her um so that's not really a
让她破产，嗯，所以这并不是真正的……
concern um the whole charade of like
担心整个闹剧，就像
doing a massive wedding I think is a
我认为举办一场盛大的婚礼是件好事。
little bit weird I think why can't we
我觉得有点奇怪，为什么我们不能
just have lots of events over the next
接下来会有很多活动。
50 years where we bring our friends and
50年来，我们带着朋友们一起来到这里。
family versus like one I've also watched
家庭与像我一样的人，我也看过
a couple of my friends at the moment who
我目前有几个朋友
are getting married the the like two
即将结婚的两人
years of pain in heart a can like
多年来，心脏一直承受着巨大的痛苦，就像……
canceling date nights so that they can
取消约会之夜，以便他们可以
afford this one wedding day yeah feels
负担得起这一个婚礼日的感觉
like highly logical to me I've got one
对我来说，这非常合乎逻辑，我有一个。
particular friend who is having to
一位特别的朋友不得不
cancel so much of their like everyday
取消他们很多日常活动
joy to save up for this one big event
为这场盛事攒钱的喜悦
which is stressing them both out and I
这让他们俩都压力很大，而且
don't think they're going to have well I
我觉得他们不会有好结果的。
don't think he's going to have a great
我觉得他不会有好结果。
time at the wedding anyway because he
反正他有时间参加婚礼，因为他
seems so stressed by it all I just I
看起来我压力好大，我简直……
sometimes hear that people can't like
有时听到有人不喜欢
get out of their marriage without having
他们无需付出任何代价就能摆脱婚姻。
to like file a divorce um thing with
比如，提交离婚申请之类的。
like the with through lawyers and going
就像通过律师和前往一样
to court and battling out in court I
上法庭，在法庭上据理力争
just think you should be free to leave
我觉得你应该有离开的自由。
if you want to leave
如果你想离开
I don't know I just
我不知道，我只是
think this is a terrible analogy and
我觉得这个比喻很糟糕。
completely unrelated but like in
完全无关，但就像在
football many of the problems we see
足球存在着我们看到的许多问题。
with my favorite Club Manchester United
我最喜欢的俱乐部是曼联。
at the moment is we've got people on
目前我们已经有人在……
fiveyear contracts who we just can't get
我们就是找不到能签五年合同的球员。
rid of and like they want to go we want
摆脱他们，就像他们想走一样，我们也想走。
them to go but because we sign these
他们要走，但因为我们签了这些协议。
long contracts with them it's like
和他们签长期合同就像
incredibly difficult and you now these
极其困难，而你现在也知道了这些
players have been like thrown in the
球员们就像被扔进了游戏里一样。
back room and they're not playing
后台，他们没在玩。
football and we're like just completely
足球，我们简直太投入了。
ignoring them because we can't get out
我们无视他们，因为我们无法离开
the contract yes so I I just think yeah
是的，合同里有相关条款，所以我就想，嗯。
I hear you I hear you all right can we
我听到了，我听到了，好的，我们可以吗？
talk about this yes all right there are
谈谈这个，好的，有
many secular marriages so you don't have
许多世俗婚姻，所以你没有
to do anything religious
做任何宗教活动
related and it sounds like a big
相关，听起来像个大问题
difficulty that you have could could be
你遇到的困难可能是
the the number one is the
第一名是
wedding because but the wedding to me
婚礼，因为但对我来说，婚礼就是如此。
the premise of it is a public
它的前提是公共的
Declaration of your love and to your
向你表达你的爱意
point it could be a small as you want it
这一点可以根据你的需要做得非常小。
could be as big as you want you could
可以像你想要的那样大
have as many as you want right that
你想拥有多少就拥有多少，对吧？
public declaration Could Happen 50 times
公开声明可能发生50次
over 50 years it is up to you so that is
超过50年的时间，这完全取决于你，就是这样。
you and your partner navigating that
你和你的伴侣正在经历这一切
space with regard to getting out of it
就摆脱困境而言，空间至关重要
this is the single biggest change that
这是最大的变化。
we need in marriages marriages in my
我们需要婚姻，我的婚姻。
opinion should be much harder to get
应该更难获得意见。
into you shouldn't be able like
你不应该能够像这样
literally you and your partner could go
实际上，你和你的伴侣可以去
to Vegas Drive up so a drive-thru you
去拉斯维加斯开车，所以你可以开车去。
could have an Elvis Presley impersonator
可以请一位猫王模仿者
marry you you pay
嫁给你，你付钱
$25 and you're married it's ridiculous I
25美元就能结婚，太荒谬了！
think that there needs to be there needs
认为需要有这些需求
to be hurdles in place there needs to be
要设置障碍，就必须有
some type of vetting some type of
某种审查 某种
premarital coaching counseling so
婚前辅导咨询
everyone is aware of the commitment that
每个人都清楚这一承诺。
is about to be made and you have the
即将制作完成，而你拥有
tools you have skills around Conflict
你拥有应对冲突的技能和工具
Management Etc needs to be
管理等需要是
hard but then if you want out you should
很难，但如果你想退出，你应该
be able to get out in an hour it should
应该一小时内就能出来。
be easy drive up Elvis Presley says it's
开车上去很容易，猫王埃尔维斯·普雷斯利说就是这样。
over
超过
$25 it's free yeah yeah free right
25美元？免费！对对对，免费！对吧？
that's the way it should be but it is
本来就应该这样，但事实并非如此。
the the the the the reverse now you're
现在反过来了，你是
right marriage is hard to get out of
一段好的婚姻很难结束。
that's changing there's now the
情况正在改变，现在有了
introduction especially in the UK of the
尤其是在英国的介绍
no fault right but but that still takes
没错，这并没有错，但这仍然需要时间。
it still could take 6 months or so there
那里可能还需要六个月左右的时间。
still is a lot of haggle so so I I agree
仍然有很多讨价还价的环节，所以我同意。
with you there is that it should be much
与你在一起，应该会很有帮助。
easier to get out but
更容易脱身，但是
ultimately what marriage is is marriage
归根结底，婚姻的本质就是婚姻。
is a declaration of commitment done in a
这是在……中作出的承诺声明
formal way can you not do that without
正式的方式不行吗？没有正式的方式就做不到。
the marriage like can you not do a
婚姻就像你不能做……
declaration of commitment without having
在没有……的情况下做出承诺声明
to go to like a church or whatever else
去教堂之类的地方
and sign documents and stuff I don't
还要签文件什么的，我不签。
know is it not possible I it is you know
我知道这不可能，但你知道这是可能的。
it is it is so I think I just have
就是这样，我想我只是有
commitment issues I think that's
我觉得这是承诺方面的问题。
probably what it is yeah I think that's
大概就是这样吧，我觉得是。
the core of it because you know what's
关键在于，你知道什么是……
so interesting to me is that you're
让我感兴趣的是，你是
already going to well how do I get out
已经到了该如何脱身的地步
of this yeah right and it almost feels
没错，这几乎让人感觉
as if there is a
仿佛存在着
fear of
害怕
committing to someone for the rest of
承诺与某人共度余生
your life because that that's a massive
你的生活，因为那是一件大事。
I mean think about this you're going to
我的意思是，想想你接下来要做的事……
commit to someone for the rest of your
承诺与某人共度余生
life for the rest of your days and what
你余生的生活以及什么
we feel because I've been there because
我们之所以有这种感觉，是因为我曾亲身经历过，因为
when I I'm getting anxiety as you say it
正如你所说，当我感到焦虑时
I'm like [__] know the rest of my
我他妈知道我剩下的部分
life the rest of your
余生
life but think about this the anxiety is
生活，但想想焦虑是
the fear of what is not even come yet so
对尚未到来之事的恐惧
that means that you can now interrogate
这意味着你现在可以进行审问
your
你的
thoughts okay you have fear over what
想法很好，你害怕什么？
what's the
是什么
fear but isn't it just a terrible idea
害怕，但这难道不是一个糟糕的想法吗？
to commit to someone till death do you
至死不渝地忠于某人，你愿意吗？
part because like imagine if I said to
部分原因是，想象一下如果我说
you you got to pick a job and then you
你得选一份工作，然后你
got to do it forever yes you would the
必须永远这样做，是的，你会的。
amount of procrastination that would
拖延的程度会
occur because of the significance of
发生的原因在于其重要性
that decision would would basically stop
这项决定基本上会阻止……
you picking any job at all because you'd
你随便选一份工作，因为你会……
be like I can know I got to pick one and
就像我知道我必须选择一个一样
do it forever and you know you'd be
如果一直这样做，你知道你会……
you'd become a perfectionist you know
你知道，那样你会变成一个完美主义者。
you'd be looking for perfection in every
你会追求方方面面的完美。
single job and maybe this is in part the
一份工作，也许部分原因在于此
issue is that because we see marriage as
问题在于，因为我们把婚姻视为
being such a final thing that we really
因为这是如此最终的事情，我们真的
have to make sure the pick is perfect is
必须确保选择完美。
perfect I agree this is one of the myths
完全同意，这是个误区。
right this whole notion of till death do
没错，这种“至死不渝”的概念真是荒谬至极。
us part which really was handed to us in
我们这部分实际上是交给我们的
religion if you look through
如果你仔细观察宗教的话
Christianity Hinduism even a lot of the
基督教、印度教，甚至很多……
modern day Islamic marriage ceremonies
现代伊斯兰婚礼仪式
there's some formation of you will be
你会形成某种形态
with this partner for the rest of your
余生都和这位伴侣在一起
life and I think what that does is it
生活，我认为它的作用是
actually sets us up for a lower level of
实际上，这会让我们处于一个较低的水平。
satisfaction it sets us up for
它带给我们的满足感
complacency oh this is all we get right
自满，哦，这就是我们唯一做对的事情吗？
it instead they can't leave me they
相反，他们却不能离开我。
can't leave me so therefore I don't have
不能离开我，所以我没有
to try as hard I don't even have to talk
尽我所能，我甚至不必开口说话。
to them now yeah I don't have to get to
现在对他们来说，是的，我不需要去……
the gym no I can just sit here like
健身房？不，我就可以像这样坐在这里
so that is a myth though because we know
所以那其实是个谬论，因为我们知道
where where divorce rates are separation
离婚率和分居率在哪里
rates are we know that there are you can
利率是我们知道的，你可以
get a divorce so you can get out she can
离婚，这样你就能离开她了。
get out we have to we have to put that
出去，我们必须，我们必须把那件事放下。
to the side but the key is is to think
放在一边，但关键在于思考
about when I always like interrogate the
每当我喜欢审问的时候
fears is well what's the
恐惧究竟是什么？
upside what's the upside of having a
好处是什么？
partner for Life what what would you say
人生伴侣，你会怎么说？
upsides I mean I could also name the
好处，我的意思是，我也可以列举出来
upsides I think so there's a certain
我认为也有好处，比如……
sense of stability and focus that comes
随之而来的稳定感和专注感
when you know that home is kind of
当你意识到家是一种
locked down so as an entrepreneur in
疫情封锁期间，作为一名企业家……
particular I I advise anybody that's
特别是，我建议任何人……
going to pursue a big grueling
去追求一项艰巨的
tumultuous uncertain challenge like
动荡不安的挑战，例如
building a business business to have a
建立一家企业，以便拥有
partner at home um and and I know Sir
家里的伴侣，嗯，而且我知道先生
Alex Ferguson was big on this when he
亚历克斯·弗格森非常重视这一点。
was selecting players for Manchester
正在为曼彻斯特挑选球员
United he would often inquire about
他经常会询问有关联合方面的事情。
whether they were in a relationship
他们是否处于恋爱关系中
because if they had a stable home life
因为如果他们拥有稳定的家庭生活
then they would be much more focused on
那么他们就会更加专注于
a training ground and I see that with
一个训练场，我看到了这一点
myself you need a stable base um if
我自己需要一个稳定的基础，嗯，如果
you're single I think as an entrepreneur
我认为你单身，而且你还是个创业者。
it can become an immense distraction an
它会成为极大的干扰因素。
immense distraction because on one hand
极大的干扰，因为一方面
you're trying to build something over
你试图在原有基础上构建一些东西。
here and you're trying to build
在这里，你正试图建造
something over here I think marriage is
我觉得婚姻这边是这样的
useful as well because when you know
这也很有用，因为当你了解它的时候。
that it's hard to get out of it means
难以摆脱的意思是
that exiting isn't the path of least
退出并非最不明智的选择
resistance which means that you you
抵抗意味着你你
probably will go to therapy first and
可能先会接受心理治疗，
you probably will see if you can fix it
你大概会看看能不能修好它。
and figure it out versus just throwing
想办法解决，而不是直接扔出去。
it away yes so it becomes less
是的，把它拿走，这样它就变得不那么
disposable yes which means that you're
一次性的，是的，这意味着你是
more likely to fight to fix the thing um
更有可能努力解决这个问题。
and what are the other upsides
还有哪些其他优点？
um I mean the stats right so the stats
嗯，我是说统计数据，对吧？所以，统计数据……
around health and wealth all suggest
关于健康和财富，所有这些都表明
that if you're in a good productive
如果你处于一个良好且高效的状态，那么
healthy relationship you're going to
你将会拥有一段健康的恋爱关系
earn more money I think it's 4% more a
我觉得赚更多钱应该能多赚4%。
year in a productive uh marriage both
在一段富有成效的婚姻中度过一年
Partners net earn 4% more a year and
合伙人每年净收入增加 4%，
according to Robert waldinger who came
根据罗伯特·瓦尔丁格的说法，他来了
on the show you're going to live longer
在节目中，你会活得更久。
so I get it yeah and you're going be
所以我明白了，是的，你会的
healthier you're going to be healthier
身体越健康，你就会越健康。
yeah yeah L less disas come on Stephen I
是的，是的，少些麻烦，来吧，斯蒂芬。
know you know do you know what it is I'm
你知道，你知道，你知道我是什么吗？
not trying to throw the marriage out I'm
我不是想破坏婚姻，我是
wondering if there's an alternative
想知道是否有其他替代方案
which do you know what it is part of me
你知道这是什么吗？这是我的一部分。
as well if you look at the way I've live
如果你看看我的生活方式，也会明白这一点。
my life I've always tried to test the
我一生都在尝试检验……
system so school like not going to
学校系统就像不去上学一样
school dropping out of University being
辍学
an entrepreneur there's always been a
企业家总是会遇到这种情况
bit of a [__] you and me to the system
有点儿像是对体制的蔑视。
and a real pause in questioning what I'm
以及一段真正停下来质疑我究竟是什么的思考。
being handed as the right answer to
被认为是正确答案
interrogate whether it's still valid now
询问它现在是否仍然有效
okay so like many of the answers I was
好的，就像我回答的很多问题一样……
given you go to university then you go
如果你上大学，那么你就会
get a job and then you hand out your CV
找到工作后，你就可以开始投递简历了。
all of these things proved in my life to
所有这些都在我的生活中得到了证明。
just be BS there was a better way so
你就胡说八道，肯定有更好的办法。
when I I'm approached with a
当我被问到这个问题时
conventional system like marriage
婚姻等传统制度
immediately I go hm let's interrogate
我立刻说道：“嗯，我们来审问一下。”
this thing and I would say I'm with you
这件事，我同意你的看法。
throw the system out think about just
抛弃这套体系，好好想想吧。
one thing and you you said this and
一件事，你说过这句话
there's research behind this it's the
这背后是有研究支持的。
investment model Right theory so the
投资模式正确的理论是
more you
你越多
invest in the preparation of your
投资于你的准备工作
partnership in the actual partnership
实际合伙关系中的合伙关系
the more that you're investing time res
你投入的时间越多
all resources the higher satisfaction
所有资源都能带来更高的满意度
you have that's fact right that's that's
你说的没错，事实就是这样。
that's research that's in essence what
那项研究本质上是什么？
you're saying right so that's the way I
你说得对，就是这样。
that I would approach it is how can I
我会采取的方法是：我该如何做？
invest as much as I can in this
我会尽我所能投资于此。
partnership with this person that I love
与我爱的人建立伙伴关系
what is it that predicts a successful
什么因素可以预测成功
marriage in your view well once again
你认为婚姻再次成为你眼中的一部分
what is success is it to to me success
对我而言，成功是什么？成功又是什么？
is high satisfaction High satisfaction
满意度高
is has a strong correlation around
它与周围环境有很强的相关性。
well-being uh Dr Carol riff I think is
健康，呃，卡罗尔博士的即兴演讲，我认为是
the OG of well-being she doesn't get
她没能获得幸福感的元老级人物。
enough credit she created a model called
她凭借足够的功劳创建了一个模型，名为
The Six Dimensions of psychological
心理的六个维度
well-being and in essence if we are
幸福感，以及本质上，如果我们是
working to increase each one of these
努力提高这些方面的每一项。
Dimensions so for example one is having
尺寸，例如，一个有
a vision of your life like what is that
你对人生的愿景是什么样的呢？
Vision that you have for life and the
你对生活和事业的愿景
question though is do you feel like you
但问题是，你觉得自己怎么样？
are actively in pursuit of that Vision
正在积极追求这一愿景
if you don't feel like you know what
如果你觉得自己不知道该怎么做
your vision is or you're not in pursuit
你的愿景是否在追求？你是否在追求？
of it you're going to have lower
其中你的收入将会降低
well-being right so the higher
幸福感越高越好
well-being that you have
你所拥有的幸福感
individually the higher satisfaction you
个人满意度越高，你
have in your
在你的
relationship the more successful your
你们的关系越成功，你们的关系就越好。
relationship is all that like
关系就是这样。
fundamental qualities that I should be
我应该具备的基本品质
looking for in a good partner oh yeah I
寻找一个好伴侣，哦耶！
mean there's a million but the the core
意思是说有百万个，但核心
the core that I I like to write about is
我喜欢写的核心内容是
and and I'll actually I I'll even uh
而且我实际上我甚至会呃
synthesize it you want to have a partner
综合起来，你想找个伴侣。
who is aware of their well-being and who
谁了解自己的健康状况，谁
is focused on their well-being this this
关注他们的福祉
is this is incredibly important because
这一点极其重要，因为
one of the most profound re uh bits of
最深刻的……片段之一
research that I I feel like I included
我感觉我纳入的研究包括
in the book is that most of us believe
书中提到，我们大多数人都相信
that having
拥有
alignment in the values of our partner
我们与合作伙伴的价值观一致
is the most successful or is the high is
是最成功的，还是最高的？
the number one determinant of having a
拥有……的首要决定因素
successful partnership we think it's
我们认为这是一次成功的合作。
about values we're told it's about
关于我们被告知的价值观
values we're fed values which by the way
我们被灌输的价值观，顺便说一句
goes back to you know where that goes
回到你知道的那个地方
back
后退
to religion you know how have you heard
你知道，你听说过宗教吗？
of you need to be equally yolked no oh
你们需要同质化吗？不，哦
you haven't heard this you're not
你没听说过这件事，你不是
reading your
读你的
Bibles exp me all right
圣经让我明白了。
so the
所以
Bible talks about you have to have a
圣经谈到你必须拥有一个
partner you have to find a partner who's
你必须找到一个合适的伴侣。
equ equally yolked what does that really
等同于等同的蛋黄，那到底是什么意思？
mean equally yolked comes from oxen
意思是“蛋黄大小相等”来自牛
right so two you have one Ox here one Ox
对，所以这里有两头牛，一头是牛。
here they're tethered together they're
在这里，它们被拴在一起。
plowing the land if they're walking lock
如果他们步行锁着，就耕地。
step they can plow the land if you have
步骤，如果你有的话，他们可以耕地。
one going off this way one going off
一个朝这边走，一个朝那边走
this way you can't plow the land you
这样你就无法耕种土地了。
can't produce so the Bible says you need
无法生产，所以圣经说你需要
to have a partner who is equally
拥有一个同样优秀的伴侣
yolked pastors then interpreted that
那些被束缚的牧师们随后解释说：
over the years to be what values you
多年来，你所珍视的价值观
need to have a partner who shares your
需要一个与你分享你需求的伴侣
value vales has the same religion has
价值观与宗教有相同的属性
the same accent this is how we became
我们就是这样变成了同样的口音。
regimented in class this happened
课堂上，这种严格的纪律导致了这件事的发生。
Century after Century after Century
一个世纪又一个世纪
right we get to today you ask anyone on
好了，我们今天就说到这儿，你可以问问任何人。
the street we grab 10 people nine out of
我们在街上抓了10个人，其中9个……
10 would say and and we said how
10 会说，然后我们说如何
important are values nine out of 10
重要性体现在9/10的价值观上
would say values is
会说价值观是
everything
一切
what values change they change I value
价值观会改变，它们会改变我所珍视的价值观。
things much differently today than I did
今天的情况与我以前大不相同了。
10 years ago our values change they're
十年前我们的价值观发生了改变，它们是
not constant we need to throw away
并非恒定不变，我们需要抛弃它
values are they important yes are they
价值观很重要吗？是的，它们很重要。
the most important no so therefore let's
最重要的不是，所以我们……
deemphasize the focusing on finding
弱化对寻找的关注
someone who matches all of our values
符合我们所有价值观的人。
instead well-being key are they focus on
相反，他们更关注的是福祉。
their well-being that's one two yeah
他们的福祉，这当然是第一点和第二点。
values is important but you know what
价值观固然重要，但你知道吗？
what's what's what's equally if not
如果不是这样，那又怎样呢？
more is you know what how open-minded
更重要的是，你知道，要多么开放包容。
are they like H how how how much do they
他们像H吗？他们多少钱？
lean in how how curious are they and
深入了解他们的好奇心有多强。
then the third is how resilient are they
第三点是他们的韧性如何。
because having a relationship with
因为与……建立关系
anyone means tough times so are they
任何人都意味着艰难时期，他们也是如此。
able to bounce back or when things get
能够迅速恢复，或者当事情变得
tough do they just lay on their back so
但它们就是仰面躺着，这很不容易。
if you have a partner who's resilient
如果你有一个适应能力强的伴侣。
you have a partner who's open-minded you
你有一个思想开放的伴侣。
have a partner who's focused and
找一个专注的伴侣
nurturing their well-being you have a
培养他们的福祉，你拥有
great partner what about ambition does
优秀的合作伙伴，那么雄心壮志呢？
that matter I I think ambition is a
就这件事而言，我认为野心是一种
value set okay
值设置正常
e yeah I just wonder because a lot of
嗯，我只是好奇，因为很多
people would say that they want that in
人们会说他们想要那个。
a partner but just by I mean like
一个伴侣，但我的意思是，就像
running the mental numbers not everybody
并非每个人都能做到心算。
can be ambitious and people that aren't
有些人雄心勃勃，有些人则不然。
necessarily hugely ambitious also find
必然雄心勃勃，也发现
love and keep love but when you ask them
爱并保持爱，但当你问他们时
on what they're looking for they'll tend
根据他们寻找的东西，他们会倾向于
to have a preference towards someone
对某人有偏好
who's ambitious or goal
谁有雄心壮志或目标
orientated one of the things we talked
我们讨论的内容之一，它指向了某个方向。
about kind of in between the lines was
大概就是字里行间那种感觉吧
how Society has changed and one of the
社会发生了怎样的变化，以及其中之一
ongoing conversations in dating at the
在约会中持续进行的对话
moment is around how women are
此刻的焦点在于女性是如何……
struggling to find compatible men
难以找到合适的男人
because women are more educated I think
因为我认为女性受教育程度更高。
there's more women graduating with
越来越多的女性毕业
college degrees now the top 10% of men
大学学位现在是男性中排名前 10% 的人的专属。
seem to be having all of the sex
似乎他们拥有所有的性生活
According to some studies that I read a
根据我读过的一些研究……
lot of the sex and then there's this
很多性爱场面，然后还有这个
bottom 50% of men that are somewhat
处于男性群体后50%的男性，他们在某种程度上
disenfranchised because they they're not
他们被剥夺了选举权，因为他们不是
getting the attention they're probably
他们很可能获得了关注
turning to things like pornography women
转向诸如色情作品之类的东西
are dating up into the right I'm told so
据说他们正在约会，而且约会对象也相当不错。
women I did read a study that said the
我读过一篇关于女性的研究，其中提到……
majority of women are still looking for
大多数女性仍在寻找
a man who's earning more than them but
一个收入比他们高的男人，
in a world of equality which we all
在一个我们所有人都平等的世界里
agree is a good thing where women are
在女性群体中，同意是一件好事。
more educated now there's there isn't
现在受过更多教育的人没有了
enough men up and to the right anymore
右边上方的人已经够多了。
so there's this sort of disparity
所以这里存在这种差距。
between you know what women are looking
你知道女人在看什么吗？
for but actually what's available in the
但实际上有哪些东西是可用的
market
市场
potentially these these these are all
这些可能都是
facts however we have to in we have to
然而，事实是我们必须……
interrogate the this this this data but
查询这些数据，但是
more so I think we have to interrogate
更何况我认为我们必须进行质询
The Narrative that's being handed to us
我们被灌输的叙事方式
so I feel like the The Narrative that's
所以我感觉这就是叙事方式。
being handed us today is that you know
今天我们得到的答案是，你知道
what the top 20% of men or 10% of men
前20%的男性或前10%的男性是什么？
they're good but the bottom 80% you
他们不错，但底层的80%……
suck that couldn't be further from the
糟糕透了，简直离谱。
truth and I think we have to acknowledge
事实如此，我认为我们必须承认这一点。
and this is where uh you know two things
而在这里，你知道两件事。
could be true one we live in a
这可能是真的，在我们生活的这个世界里。
patriarchal society absolutely
绝对的父权社会
absolutely
绝对地
but do we need to extend more grace to
但我们是否需要给予更多宽容呢？
our men absolutely we do are men lonlier
我们的男人确实更孤独。
than they ever have been absolutely are
比以往任何时候都更加如此。
men confused absolutely right are men
男人完全搞错了，他们是男人
being misled absolutely let's extend
被误导是绝对的，让我们继续下去。
more grace to our men what does that
对我们的男人多一些恩典，这是什么意思？
mean that means being aware that we do
这意味着要意识到我们确实
live in a loneliness epidemic
生活在孤独的流行病中
being aware that less than 27% of men
意识到只有不到 27% 的男性
have a friend that they can feel is a
找一个可以让他们感到亲切的朋友
confidant that 0% of them now feel like
确信他们中现在没有 0% 的人有这种感觉
they have someone who they can go to at
他们有可以求助的人。
3:00 a.m. in the morning it's being
凌晨3点，事情正在发生
aware of these things it is saying you
它意识到这些事情，就等于在告诉你
know what I um can appreciate other
我知道我能欣赏其他的东西
traits and characteristics outside of
特征和特性之外
how much you earn or how tall you are
你的收入多少，或者你的身高
right these are it's important to be
没错，这些都是很重要的。
able to understand and and you just
能够理解，而且你只是
asked me you said where are the most I
你问我，你说哪里最多，我
said nothing about how much money
只字未提金额多少。
someone makes nothing about how tall
有人根本不在乎身高
they are right but at the same time what
他们说得对，但同时又是什么呢？
we have to understand is the narrative
我们必须理解的是叙事方式。
that is handed to about women is that
人们普遍认为女性应该这样看待这件事。
all women are looking for the six foot
所有女性都在寻找身高六英尺的男人
plus CEO right who's making over 100,000
还有那位年薪超过10万美元的CEO
pounds or dollars a year and that is
每年英镑或美元，就是这样。
also not the case this study here says
这项研究也表明情况并非如此。
despite advancements in gender equality
尽管性别平等方面取得了进展
resarch indicates that better educated
研究表明，受过良好教育的人
women still tend to prefer husbands who
女性仍然倾向于选择这样的丈夫：
earn more than they do that's from The
他们赚的比他们多，那是来自……
Institute for family studies an analysis
家庭研究所的一项分析
of online dating behaviors across 24
24 年间在线约会行为
countries found that women are more
各国发现女性更
selective than men showing a marked
比男性更具选择性，表现出明显的
preference for men um with high incomes
偏爱高收入男性
and education levels which which again
以及教育水平，这又如何呢？
proves this up and to the right thing
这证明了这一点，并且是正确的做法。
but there's just not enough men up and
但是人手严重不足，
to the right so there's going to be a
向右走，所以会有一个
lot of women that are somewhat
很多女性都有些
dissatisfied according to this all right
根据这一点，我对一切都感到不满
so the challenge if if I'm really
所以，如果我真的……那么挑战就来了
interrogating this is one is it's
质疑这一点就是其中之一。
talking about High educated women so we
谈到受过高等教育的女性，所以我们
know that Highly Educated women are on
要知道，受过高等教育的女性都在
average dating hypergamous right which
平均而言，约会对象都是高嫁，对吧？
is what you're talking about up so
这就是你说的那个意思吗？
someone who's dating someone who has the
正在和拥有……的人约会的人
same or higher level of Education the
相同或更高教育水平
same or higher level of financial
相同或更高水平的财务状况
resources and why is that because that's
资源，以及为什么会这样，因为那是……
the script that Society handed to women
社会赋予女性的剧本
to say the only way you can survive is
可以说，你生存的唯一途径是
by finding a man who can deliver this to
找到一个能把这个送过去的人
you right right that's and and I think
你说得对，就是这样，而且我认为
we have to accept where it came from it
我们必须接受它的来源。
was this terrible Society of you know
你知道，这就是那个可怕的社会吗？
what you're not going to be safe unless
除非你这样做，否则你不会安全。
you find a man who could provide but you
你找到一个能养家糊口的男人，但是你
fast forward to to
快进到
today a large percentage of high Highly
今天，很大一部分高……
Educated women are dating this way but
受过良好教育的女性也会这样约会，但
that's not all women the other part is
那并不是所有女性的全部，另一部分是
yes are women beginning to out earn men
是的，女性的收入开始超过男性了。
and outeducate men absolutely in certain
并且在某些方面绝对超越男性的教育水平
cities
城市
not in every everywhere of the world men
并非世界各地所有地方都有男人
on average still earn more income so so
平均而言，收入仍然更高，所以……
so if you look at at at at the The
所以如果你看一下那个
Narrative that's handed to us you could
别人交给我们的叙述可能
say well you know what men on average
比如说，你知道男人平均水平是多少吗？
Still Still earn more but my point is
虽然收入仍然更高，但我的重点是
this my point is that I think we all
我的意思是，我认为我们所有人都
need to
需要
re-evaluate what it is that we want no
重新评估我们真正想要的是什么
longer do we need to have a partner for
我们还需要合作伙伴多久？
most of us or should I say this is me
我们大多数人，或者应该说，这说的就是我。
speaking out of privilege for many of us
对我们许多人来说，发声是出于特权。
in the west no longer do we need to have
在西方，我们不再需要拥有
a partner for pragmatic reasons if you
出于务实原因，如果你是合作伙伴的话
think about maso's hierarchy of needs
思考一下马索的需求层次理论
and you just divided it into three
你把它分成了三份。
categories you would say the bottom the
你会说，类别底部
bottom kind of rung is all of our
最底层的阶梯就是我们所有人的。
psychological and physical needs food
心理和生理需求 食物
shelter right then that kind of middle
当时的庇护所就在那种中间地带
rung is belonging and connection and the
阶梯代表归属感和联系。
top rung is selfish evolved self you
最高境界是自私的、进化的自我。
know we want to be you know we you know
知道我们想成为你知道我们你知道
well self- evolved living our best self
完善自我，不断进化，活出最好的自己
contributing the most that we ever could
我们尽了全力。
to this
对此
world marriage and partnership and
世界婚姻和伙伴关系
selecting a partner was largely based on
选择伴侣主要基于
that lower rung all the way through to
从最低层一直到最高层
the 1960s that's like yesterday if you
如果你觉得1960年代就像昨天一样，那你就会明白。
think about how long we've lived but
想想我们已经活了多久，但是
it's that Evolution as well because you
这也是进化的一部分，因为你
see the same thing in the animal kingdom
在动物王国中也能看到同样的现象。
with like the orangutang which has like
就像猩猩一样，它就像
98% the same DNA as us they still select
98% 的基因和我们相同，他们仍然会选择。
for survival
为了生存
factors so I think what's interesting
因素有很多，所以我觉得有趣的是……
when you look at uh different
当你观察不同的东西时
mammals and the uh the The evolutionary
哺乳动物和呃，进化
biology is that there's lots of
生物学就是有很多……
similarities but then there's also lots
相似之处很多，但也有很多不同之处。
of traits that are different you know so
你知道，有些特征是不同的。
it's it's one of those where we have to
这是我们必须……的情况之一
appreciate that as Homo
欣赏这一点，作为人类
sapiens we are unique and we live in a
智人是独一无二的，我们生活在一个
structure that we have largely created
我们已基本构建的结构
ourselves
我们自己
we're talking we're debating about the
我们正在谈论，我们正在辩论……
institution of marriage I mean marriage
我指的是婚姻制度
didn't exist for the vast majority of
对绝大多数人来说，它并不存在。
our existence but this Golden Rule thing
我们的存在，但这条黄金法则却并非如此。
you told me about this yeah and you told
你跟我说过这件事，是的，你还说过
me that it's cross-cultural yes so so it
对我来说，它是跨文化的，是的，就是这样。
is and this Golden Rule thing please
是，还有这条黄金法则，请
explain it for people but for me that is
要向别人解释清楚，但对我来说就是这样。
evidence that there's still an
有证据表明仍然存在
evolutionary component to selection for
进化成分对选择的影响
men and women and I read I was reading
男人和女人，我读着，我在读着
this study that said women um almost 50%
这项研究表明，女性的患病率接近50%。
of women prefer to date only men that
大多数女性更喜欢只和男性约会。
are taller than themselves while only
比他们自己高，而只有
13% of men prefer to date only women
13%的男性更喜欢只和女性约会。
that are shorter than themselves and
比他们自身矮的
another study revealed that women are
另一项研究表明，女性
most satisfied when they're partner is
当伴侣是……时，他们最满意。
approximately 8 Ines taller whereas men
大约高出8英寸，而男性
are most satisfied with a height
最满意的身高
difference of about 8 centimeters taller
身高相差约 8 厘米
than their partner so women clearly have
比她们的伴侣更甚，所以女性显然有
a preference here significant amount of
这里偏好大量的
them to dating a man that is bigger than
她们和比她们高大的男人约会
they are yes but all right yes this is
是的，好吧，是的，这是
so good all right couple things here M
好的，这里有几件事 M
do we have these preferences absolutely
我们绝对有这些偏好
it's a lot of this handed us through
很多东西都是别人交给我们的。
evolutionary and our biology
进化与我们的生物学
absolutely is most of it handed to us
大部分确实是别人拱手相让的。
through
通过
socialization definitely do we change as
社会化肯定会改变我们。
we increase our
我们增加了我们的
well-being yes so here's my point if you
是的，幸福感很重要，所以我的观点是，如果你
were to go back and say Zena look you go
回去跟泽娜说，你看，你走吧
back 10 years say Z look would you
十年前，你觉得Z会怎么样？
prefer to date a man that is taller than
更喜欢和比自己高的男人约会
you
你
I would say there's a there's a good
我觉得这很好。
chance she would say I would prefer it
她可能会说我更喜欢这样
yes has that been her result no does she
是的，那是她的结果吗？不，不是。
appear to be incredibly happy and
他们看起来非常开心，
satisfied yes right with Tom Holland
满意吗？是的，汤姆·霍兰德
that's from my op from from my outside
那是我从外部视角看到的。
looking in yes why could that have been
是的，我看了看，为什么会这样呢？
the case because she grew up being
因为她从小就……
handed to script she grew up the disn
她拿着剧本长大，迪士尼
ification of relationships she saw the
她看到了人际关系的形成
The Prince and how large the prince
王子以及王子的体型有多大
always was in comparison to the princess
总是和公主作比较。
she saw that the prince was able to pick
她看到王子能够挑选
up the princess like she saw all these
公主好像看到了这一切。
things she believed all of these things
她相信所有这些事情
and then as she became more mature as
然后随着她逐渐成熟
she realized that she doesn't need
她意识到自己不需要
anyone's validation as she understood
她理解任何人的认可。
the things and the traits that she loved
她所爱的事物和特质
she was like this Tom Holland guy is hot
她当时就觉得汤姆·霍兰德这个男的真帅。
yeah but is it that is an exception not
是的，但这算例外吗？
because Al Tom Holland's got 30 million
因为艾尔·汤姆·霍兰德有3000万美元
in the bank so
存入银行
yeah but but but this does happen you
是啊，但是，但是，但是，这种情况确实会发生。
hear happens but it's it's the exception
这种情况确实会发生，但这只是个例外。
isn't it it's not the rule it is and you
不是吗？这不是规则，但这就是规则，而且你
know why also that's the exception and I
我知道为什么这是个例外，而且我
agree I'm with you it's the exception
同意，我同意你的看法，这只是个例外。
because most of us have poor
因为我们大多数人都很穷。
well-being most of us have low
我们大多数人的幸福感都很低。
self-esteem most of us do I would argue
我认为，我们大多数人都有自尊心。
most adults have low self-esteem mid to
大多数成年人的自尊心都比较低。
low self-esteem and what does that mean
低自尊意味着什么
it means that we need the validation of
这意味着我们需要验证
others right and this is the reason why
其他人是对的，这就是原因。
I always say it goes back to us do you
我总是说，这最终还是取决于我们自己，对吧？
really think this is the answer to this
我真的觉得这就是答案。
do do you not believe that there's a big
你难道不相信存在一个很大的
evolutionary component to attraction
吸引力的进化成分
selection preferences like
选择偏好
because I I'm struggling to believe that
因为我很难相信这一点。
Society is the only reason why we're why
社会是我们存在的唯一原因。
we pick certain people and I I do part
我们挑选一些人，而我负责其中一部分。
of me wonders and slightly worries that
我心中充满疑惑和些许担忧。
we've we've almost accidentally
我们几乎是无意中
inadvertently designed design Society in
无意中设计了设计社会
such a way where what we're looking for
这样我们就能找到我们想要的东西了
no longer exists necessarily so we have
不再一定存在，所以我们有
to confront this new reality that in
面对这一新的现实，
fact we're going to have to adjust some
事实上，我们必须做出一些调整。
of our preferences if we are going to be
如果我们打算这样做，就要考虑我们的偏好。
happy and find what we're looking for
开心，并且找到了我们想要的东西
yes I do believe that a large percentage
是的，我相信很大一部分人
of the decisions that we make have been
我们所做的决定一直是
handed to us genetically so I'm I'm I'm
这是我与生俱来的基因，所以我……
with that uh and I think the research
有了那项研究，我认为……
suggests that so if you have for example
这表明，例如，如果你有
um you know uh I was talking to to Dr
嗯，你知道，呃，我当时在和医生说话。
taros wart and talking about you know a
塔罗牌疣，还有关于你知道的谈话
woman in the club if she's ovulating or
如果俱乐部里的女人正处于排卵期，或者
not ovulating just based on that men are
仅仅因为男性不排卵是不合理的
going to be attracted or or or or or or
将会被吸引，或者或者或者或者或者
not attracted or you think about scent
没有被吸引，或者你想到了气味
right really what we're trying to do
对，我们真正想做的就是这个。
with scent the reason why we're turned
气味是我们着迷的原因
off with scent is that it's genetic it's
气味消失是因为这是基因决定的。
that if we end up mating with someone
如果我们最终和某人交配了
who has too close of a a genetic mirror
谁与基因镜像过于接近
to ours the child won't be as
对我们来说，孩子不会像
so we need
所以我们需要
diversification in our in our genetics
我们基因的多样性
and we don't realize this but we can
我们可能没有意识到这一点，但我们可以
determine that through our scent by
通过我们的气味来确定
being turned off it's it's it's a whole
被关掉，它就完全是……
sniff test so does Do genetics play a
嗅觉测试也是如此吗？基因在其中扮演什么角色？
role absolutely golden mean we talked
角色绝对黄金法则我们谈到了
about Golden mean where in essence this
关于黄金分割，其本质是……
is women on average loving to see wide
女性平均而言是否喜欢看广阔的视野
shoulders and a thinner waist and Men on
肩膀更宽，腰部更细，男人
average loving to see smaller hips uh
一般人都喜欢看小一点的臀部。
smaller waist wider hips now can people
腰围变小，臀部变宽，现在人们可以
debate these Concepts absolutely do they
辩论这些概念绝对没错
stand up um I mean are there uh
站起来，嗯，我的意思是，有……
evolutionary reasons for these yes
进化原因可以解释这些现象。
because it speaks to being fertile for
因为它象征着生育能力。
women or it speaks to being uh strong to
这表明女性要坚强。
protect right for a man all of this does
这一切都是为了保护男性的权利。
play a role and sometimes we don't
扮演某种角色，有时我们则不扮演。
realize
意识到
how much of a role
扮演多大的角色
Evolution has played in why and how we
进化在为什么以及如何……方面发挥了作用。
make decisions which is why it's also
做出决定，这也是它的原因。
important though to understand how the
但重要的是要理解……
society that we have created as human
我们人类所创造的社会
beings also plays a role how we were
生命体也对我们过去的经历起着一定的作用。
handed you should you need to have a
如果您需要的话，可以递给您一个
partner who's the same class as you you
和你同班的伙伴
need to when you find your partner
当你找到伴侣时，就需要这样做。
that's person that completes you when
那个人会让你的人生变得完整
you find a partner that's till death do
你找到一个至死不渝的伴侣
you part those pieces were handed to us
你把那些碎片交给了我们。
so there's no wonder why we're confused
所以，我们感到困惑也就不足为奇了。
we have all this
我们拥有这一切
evolutionary uh uh decision-making
进化论的决策
happening that we're not even aware of
我们甚至没有意识到的事情正在发生
and then on this side we have Society
然后，这边是社会。
telling us this is the person that we
告诉我们这就是我们要找的人
that we should have and this is this is
我们应该拥有的，而这就是，这就是
the reason why and I go back to why
原因是什么？我又回到了为什么这个问题。
awareness is key and understanding how
意识是关键，了解如何
and why we are gives us a power it gives
我们存在的意义赋予我们力量，它赋予我们
us a t autonomy over our decisions so
我们拥有对自己决定的自主权，所以
that when you are making that decision
当你做出那个决定的时候
on your partner you can ask yourself you
你可以问问自己，关于你的伴侣，你
know yeah I would love to have a partner
是的，我很想有个伴侣。
who's over six feet but how important is
谁身高超过六英尺？但这有多重要？
that really to me why why do I think I I
对我来说，这真的就是为什么，为什么我认为我
feel this way yeah and once you begin to
是的，有这种感觉，一旦你开始
have those debates with yourself that
和自己进行这些辩论
puts you on the path to making a
让你走上创造之路
decision that you're going to be more
你决定要更加
satisfied with in the Long Haul I think
从长远来看，我对结果很满意。
that's the key and I think the awareness
这是关键，我认为这种意识也很重要。
comes from confronting both realities
源于直面两种现实
which is on one hand there are some
一方面有一些
evolutionary things that are going to
进化论即将发生的事情
make me have a bias towards a certain
这让我对某事产生偏见。
type of person that has certain
具有某种特质的人
attributes even if those attributes
即使这些属性
actually um not going to lead to a
实际上，嗯，不会导致……
long-term healthy relationship like [__]
长期健康的恋爱关系就像操
boys yes like Charisma and bravado and
是的，男孩喜欢魅力和虚张声势。
confidence is like somewhat attractive
自信就像某种吸引力。
but it might not be a great husband and
但他可能不是个好丈夫
then on the other hand there is tons of
另一方面，也有很多
things Society has handed me through
社会赋予我的东西
magazines and media that have portrayed
杂志和媒体曾对……进行过报道
an image of what beauty looks like that
一张展现美的图片
are also just [__] I think
我觉得那些也都是胡说八道。
understanding both is the key to that
理解这两者是关键。
sort of autonomy being able to say
某种程度上的自主权，能够说
actually I understand where that's
其实我明白那是什么意思。
coming from in me but I will make a
虽然这想法源于我内心，但我会努力实现。
rational prefrontal cortex decision to
理性的前额叶皮层决策
select something else some evidence of
选择其他一些证据
this The evolutionary basis of
这是进化的基础
Attraction comes in this idea that
吸引力源于这种想法：
people who have symmetrical faces are
拥有对称面部的人
more beautiful and more attractive
更美丽，更有吸引力
across cultures is that true yes so
跨文化来看，情况确实如此吗？是的，如此。
there are many scientists that will say
有很多科学家会说
absolutely but here's what one thing I
当然，但有一点我想说的是……
know definitively about attraction is
确切地了解吸引力是
attraction to someone else is largely
对另一个人的吸引力很大程度上
based on your
根据你的
self-esteem and this is what I mean is
自尊，这就是我的意思：
that the lower your self-esteem the more
自尊心越低，就越容易……
dependent you are on the validation of
这取决于你的验证
the public so therefore you will want to
因此，公众会希望
have a partner who is considered to be
有一个被认为是
attractive so if Society if the script
如果剧本对社会有吸引力，那么它就具有吸引力。
is is that symmetry is it or if the
那就是对称性吗？还是说……
script is um
脚本是嗯
wearing this type of trainer is it if
穿这种运动鞋怎么样？
that's what Society is saying then if
这就是社会当时所表达的意思。
you have low self-esteem you want a
你缺乏自信，你想要一个
partner to look like that because you
你的伴侣看起来是那样，因为你
need the validation of the partner
需要合作伙伴的验证
however whenever you see this is what I
但是每当你看到这个的时候，这就是我
this is what I say whenever you see
每当你看到我，我都会这么说。
someone who's walking around with a
一个带着……四处走动的人
partner and you think how did those two
你的伴侣，你会想，这两个人是怎么走到一起的？
get together right chances are there's
聚在一起的机会很大
an element and remember I'm not talking
一个元素，记住我不是在说话。
about one has super high income or one
大约有一个人收入非常高，或者一个
has super high status I'm just talking
地位超级高，我只是说说而已。
about you look at at at at a couple and
关于你，看看一对夫妇，
you say they look odd right one of them
你说它们其中一个看起来很奇怪，对吧？
could be traditionally attractive one of
传统上，这可能是一个有吸引力的人。
them might not normally what's happened
他们可能通常不会知道发生了什么。
is that you have someone with high
就是你身边有位高学历的人
self-esteem who has no need for the
自尊心强的人不需要
Public's validation of their partner at
公众对其合作伙伴的认可
all I don't think people talk about this
我觉得人们很少谈论这件事。
enough but it's so unbelievable true in
够了，但这真是难以置信，却又如此真实。
fact I know an individual who has a
事实上，我认识一个人，他有
historically low self-esteem and went
历史上一直很低的自尊心，并且
through a lot of stuff when they were
他们经历了很多事情
younger and I remember when they got
年轻的时候，我还记得他们什么时候……
into a relationship I remember exactly
我清楚地记得那段感情。
where I was stood in London I remember
我记得当时我站在伦敦的哪个位置。
the time of day when they turned to me
他们转向我的时候是什么时候？
they just got into a relationship
他们刚开始谈恋爱。
someone with historic low self-esteem
长期以来自卑的人
and they said to me Steve I really like
他们对我说：“史蒂夫，我真的很喜欢你。”
her but I'm kind of worried this is an
但她，但我有点担心这是个……
exact quote I'm kind of worried like if
原话：我有点担心，如果
I walk into a restaurant with her on my
我和她一起走进一家餐厅。
arm is it going to be a good look
手臂看起来会很好看吗？
and I remember saying to this person
我记得我对这个人说过……
like if that's the way you're assessing
如果你是这样评估的话
this person based on how they'll look on
这个人是根据他们的外貌来判断的
your own when you walk into a
当你走进一个地方时，你自己的
relationship my God this relationship is
我的上帝，这段关系是
[__] because you're overlooking the
搞砸了，因为你忽略了……
actual things that matter the most
真正重要的事情
important things and this person has
重要的事情，而这个人有
gone from one relationship to the next
从一段感情走向下一段感情
to the next to the next all of them
到下一个到下一个，他们所有人
failing as the more time I've spent with
随着我与他相处时间的增加，失败的程度也越来越深。
them I thought to myself like it's
我心想，就好像……
because their selection is being made
因为正在进行选择。
through insecurity and low self-esteem
由于缺乏安全感和自卑
yes just back to back to back to back to
是的，就这样，一个接一个地重复着。
back yes it's not being made based on
是的，它不是根据……制作的
the like the essence of the person the
就像这个人的本质一样
the other areas of compatibility that
其他兼容性方面
matter more over the long term it's that
从长远来看，更重要的是这一点。
constant like surface level connection
像表面层连接一样恒定
yes and and I think most of us are
是的，而且我认为我们大多数人都是
making decisions based on our
根据我们的决策做出决定
self-esteem did you see this as a
自尊心，你认为这是……
Matchmaker you know yes cuz you saying
媒人，你知道的，因为你说
Rich guys right yeah exactly I you know
有钱人，对吧？没错，你知道的。
uh I distinctly remember when I was on
呃，我清楚地记得我当时在……
previously and and You' ask about like
之前，你问的是类似的事情
what was one of the most profound things
其中最深刻的事情之一是什么？
that that you saw and I never had
你看到了，而我从未见过。
thought about that question until you
思考这个问题直到你
asked it and it was uh these men who
问了这个问题，结果是这些人……
were coming who had incredibly low
那些人来了，他们的水平低得惊人
self-esteem and what it was is these
自尊以及它究竟是什么，就是这些
were what I call Lake
我称之为湖
Bloomers you know it was the the the the
你知道，布鲁默斯就是那个那个
guy who always felt like no one liked
一个总觉得自己不被人喜欢的人
you know no one liked how they appeared
你知道，没人喜欢他们的样子。
they were the quote unquote ugly
他们是所谓的“丑陋的”。
duckling they they then found the gym
小鸭子们，然后它们找到了健身房
later in life right they they they they
后来，他们，他们，他们
found their Mojo later in life they were
他们晚年才找到自己的魅力。
always studious um they were a bit
他们总是很用功，嗯，他们有点
introverted maybe shy at the same time
内向，或许同时又有点害羞
um and here they are and when people
嗯，他们就在这里，当人们
walk past them they're like oh my God
走过他们身边时，他们会惊呼：“我的天哪！”
this guy's a stud like look at look at
这家伙真是个帅哥，瞧瞧他！
this guy he's a stud but he never
这家伙是个帅哥，但他从来没
thought he was a stud nor does he think
他既不认为自己很厉害，也不这么认为。
he's a stud today which is why I say go
他今天状态极佳，所以我才说加油！
back to doing the inner work we would
回到我们原本计划的内在功课上来。
take a CL like that and oppos just
拿这样的CL，然后反对就
saying let's put you on a date we can't
说我们安排你约会吧，我们不能
do that we have to begin to work with
要做到这一点，我们必须开始与……合作
you so that you realize how incredible
让你意识到这有多么不可思议
you actually are why can't you just
你其实就是，为什么你不能……
check them on a date if they've got low
如果它们含量低，请按日期检查。
self-esteem be because
自尊心可能源于
okay we can sit them across from the
好的，我们可以让他们坐在对面。
most incredible match but they won't
最精彩的比赛，但他们不会赢
recognize it because they're making
认出它，因为他们正在制作
decisions based on their self-esteem so
他们基于自尊心做出的决定
they're making the decision that your
他们正在做出决定，你的
friend made right how will this person
朋友交对了，这个人会怎么做？
look on my arm when I bring them to the
当我把它们带到……时，看看我的手臂。
Christmas party opposed
反对圣诞派对
to what's their well-being look like or
他们的健康状况如何？
do we do do we share any values Etc so
我们之间有共同的价值观吗？等等。
you can end up taking someone who could
你最终可能会带走一个可能
be great for you and push them away or
对你来说可能很好，然后把他们推开，或者
dismiss them or worse you can invite
解雇他们，或者更糟的是，你可以邀请他们
someone into your life who's not the
生活中出现一个并非你想象中的人
best placed for you because of a result
由于这一结果，最适合您的职位。
of your insecurities like a narcissist
像自恋者一样展现你的不安全感
like like like a narcissist like a SST
就像自恋狂一样，就像SST
like a psychopath like a mellian right
就像精神病患者一样，就像梅利安人一样
you know there's a distinct group of bad
你知道有一群特别糟糕的人。
people in the world David bus writes
世界上的人们，大卫·巴斯写道
about this that we have to realize they
关于这一点，我们必须意识到他们
play on our fears they understand when
利用我们的恐惧，他们就能理解。
someone has low self-esteem low
某人自尊心低
well-being they're attracted to that
他们被那种幸福感所吸引。
person why because they're better able
这个人之所以能做到这一点，是因为他们更有能力。
to manipulate them what's our best
操纵他们，我们最好的做法是什么？
defense the best defense in any
最好的防御就是任何情况下最好的防御
relationship in life is our
生活中的关系是我们
well-being it acts as a wall
它对健康起到了屏障的作用。
against all of the bad people in the
对抗所有坏人
world and what it also does is it acts
世界，以及它所做的，就是它的行为
as a magnet for the great people in the
作为吸引优秀人才的磁石
world because people with high
世界因为高学历的人
well-being and high self-esteem tend to
幸福感和高度自尊往往
surround themselves and and and
他们包围着自己，并且
understand and even attract people with
了解甚至吸引拥有以下特质的人
high well-being and high self-esteem
高度幸福感和高度自尊
okay so two personal case studies popped
好的，现在出现了两个个人案例研究。
to mind in my friendship group that I
在我的朋友圈里，我想记住我
that I'm aware of people that I'm aware
我知道我认识的这些人
of um they are approaching their 40s
他们都快40岁了。
okay they would both probably say say
好吧，他们俩可能都会这么说。
that they had low self-esteem they don't
他们缺乏自信，他们不
feel like they got the time pull to
感觉他们得到了时间的拉力
figure out their self-esteem because in
弄清楚他们的自尊心，因为在
both situations they're like I need to
两种情况下，他们都说我需要……
find someone and they're in a bit of a
找到某人，他们有点……
rush I'd say one of them is a male one
拉什，我觉得其中一个是男性。
of them is a female now what would you
其中一位是女性，你会怎么做？
say to both of those people approaching
对走过来的那两个人说
their 40s feel like they're in a bit of
他们感觉自己40多岁的时候有点……
a rush one's sort of contending with a
匆忙之中，人们似乎正在应对某种情况
biological clock MH um the other just is
生物钟 MH 嗯，另一个只是
contending with like social comparison
应对类似社会比较
all of his friends are in relationships
他所有的朋友都在谈恋爱。
and settling down and he's still single
他安定下来了，但仍然单身。
both fundamentally have low self-esteem
两人本质上都缺乏自信。
so the way that they're trying to solve
所以他们试图解决的方法是
this problem is they're trying
这个问题在于他们正在尝试
to get blow Dres to make themselves look
为了让自己看起来更漂亮，去吹嘘
pretty on the external to attract people
外表漂亮，能吸引人
in and dating as many people as they
尽可能多地与人交往和约会
possibly can to try and find someone as
或许可以尝试找找其他人
soon as possible yes I would tell them
是的，我会尽快告诉他们。
you haven't even lived half your life
你甚至还没活过人生的一半。
yet you have plenty of time period but
但你还有充足的时间，
I've got a biological clock over here
我这儿有个生物钟呢。
you know what I understand that but you
你知道，我明白这一点，但是你
know what's worse you know you know you
你知道更糟糕的是什么吗？你知道，你知道你
know what what is what is incredibly sad
知道什么是令人难以置信的悲伤
is that I've seen a large percentage of
我看到很大一部分
people say I have a biological clck I
人们说我有生物学上的缺陷
want to have a child so therefore I'm
想要个孩子，所以我……
just going to have a child with with
就打算和……生个孩子
with with
与
anyone what happens what happens what
任何人，发生了什么事？发生了什么事？
ends up happening is it ends up becoming
最终发生的事情就是它最终变成了
a incredibly difficult scenario to
这是一个极其困难的局面
manage because you now are in a
因为你现在处于……之中，所以要学会管理。
partnership with someone who you don't
与你不认识的人建立合作关系
like you don't feel safe with there's no
就像你觉得没有安全感一样
emotional connection they create stress
情感联系会造成压力
on you they end up not being apparent to
在你身上，它们最终变得不那么明显了。
the child that stress leads to other
压力导致的孩子会面临其他问题
issues that you may have like autoimmune
您可能存在的问题，例如自身免疫性疾病
disease you end up not being able to
患上这种疾病后，你最终无法……
show up as your best self for the child
以最好的自己出现在孩子面前
the child sees this and they they have a
孩子看到了这个，他们就有了
myriad of issues as a result of you
你引发了无数问题。
wanting to beat your biological clock I
想战胜你的生物钟吗？
say this I understand the desire to have
这么说吧，我理解这种渴望。
children I get it I wanted my wife and I
孩子们，我明白了，我想要的是我和我妻子
tried for eight years a lot of people we
我们尝试了八年，很多人都尝试过。
we we went through IVF you know I get it
我们做了试管婴儿，你知道，我明白。
to this day we still pay for our embryos
时至今日，我们仍然需要为胚胎付费。
to be frozen it's like it's one of those
被冷冻起来就像是……
where I understand the desire to have
我理解这种渴望。
children what age were you oh my God it
孩子们，你们当时几岁？我的天哪！
was probably 16 years ago when we
大概是16年前，我们
started IVF we were early to to to IVF
我们很早就开始了试管婴儿治疗。
we
我们
um and by the way even before the 16
嗯，顺便说一句，甚至在16号之前
years we had tried like naturally to to
多年来，我们一直尝试像自然而然地……
have a child we went through one year of
我们生了孩子，经历了一年的时间。
Cycles
循环
unsuccessful we end up we ended up
失败了，我们最终……
losing one of our losing a child right
失去我们中的一员，失去一个孩子的权利
um devastating absolutely devastating
嗯，毁灭性的，绝对的毁灭性
and then we then have a cycle that that
然后我们就进入了一个循环。
works which which is our first son
作品，也就是我们的长子
Kingston and then we have a cycle that
金斯顿，然后我们有一个周期……
works fairly close after our Second Son
紧随我们的第二个儿子之后。
uh Liam but one of the unold stories
呃，利亚姆，但那是一个不为人知的故事
about IVF and I and I wish people talked
关于试管婴儿，我和我希望人们能谈论这件事。
about this more is that you may still
关于这一点，更重要的是，你可能仍然
have eight embryos six embryos that are
有八个胚胎，其中六个是
still viable we have nine embryos that
我们还有九个仍然存活的胚胎。
are still viable and so what do you do
它们仍然可行，那么你该怎么办？
some people will donate them to science
有些人会将它们捐赠给科学研究。
some people will have them destroyed but
有些人会下令销毁它们，但
there's other folks like my wife and I
还有其他像我和我妻子一样的人。
that are thinking know these are lives
那些思考的人要知道，这些都是生命
that we've created like what are we
我们创造了什么？我们是什么？
going to do and so we have paid to store
打算这么做，所以我们付了钱去存储。
them so every month since we began our
所以自从我们开始以来，每个月我们都会这样做
Cycles we have paid to store them now
我们已经付费存放的自行车
from what I uh uh some people have told
据我所知，有些人告诉我……
me that there there limitations in
对我来说，存在一些局限性
certain countries around how many years
某些国家大约有多少年
you can actually uh store your embryos
你其实可以储存你的胚胎。
but it's such a grueling decision to
但这是一个如此艰难的决定
have to make um and um and it's it's
得做嗯嗯嗯，而且是，是的
it's it's it's one that that we made
这是我们制作的。
so I understand the desire to be a
所以我理解想要成为……的愿望
parent I fully do how old were you and
家长，我完全明白你当时几岁了？
Jill when you decided to do IVF I say
吉尔，当你决定做试管婴儿的时候，我说
this because you said 16 years ago you
这是因为你16年前说过你
look about 30 yeah yeah I mean yeah I
看起来大概30岁，是啊是啊，我的意思是，是啊，我
mean this is the thing is everyone's
意思是说，这就是每个人都面临的问题
like well how old are you what a lot of
比如，你多大了？很多
people don't realize is I this year 50
人们没意识到，我今年50岁了。
so you were about 34 35 yeah uh I would
所以你当时大概34、35岁吧？嗯，我会的。
say I was about 30 yeah I was mid-30s
比如说我当时大概30岁，对，我30多岁了。
and Jill was same mid-30s okay yep and
吉尔也差不多30多岁，好吧，是的。
you've been training for eight years so
你已经训练了八年了，所以
quite honestly we had been trying so we
说实话，我们一直在努力，所以我们
got married uh when I was
我结婚的时候……
25 right uh we started trying shortly
25 对，呃，我们很快就开始尝试了
thereafter because I've always wanted to
此后，因为我一直想……
be a father always and so very quickly
永远做一个父亲，而且要很快。
after we got married we thought you know
我们结婚后就想，你知道
children as us will have it and it just
像我们这样的孩子也会有，而且它就
doesn't happen that way and what we
事情并非如此，而我们
began to see is that one of the
开始意识到，其中一个
challenges was around the
挑战围绕着
stress that we had in our lives and how
我们生活中所承受的压力以及我们如何应对这些压力。
we were unhealthy as a result of the
由于以下原因，我们的身体状况不佳：
stress and and the impact that was
压力及其影响
having on our inability to have
因为我们无法拥有
children did it cause a strain on your
孩子们是否给你造成了压力？
relationship when you went through these
当你经历这些事情时，你们的关系如何？
struggles with fertility absolutely you
绝对的生育困难
feel like you know the script that I
感觉你好像知道我写的剧本。
felt was handed to me and this was a
有人递给我一块毡布，这就是……
script is
脚本是
that you're a
你是
man and if you can't have a child you're
男人，如果你不能生育孩子，你就是
not a man that was the script that was
剧本里写的不是男人。
literally I remember being at the barber
我记得很清楚，当时我在理发店。
shop right when I had hair when I used
我刚买东西的时候，头发还没干透。
to go to the barber shop um and that was
去理发店，嗯，就是这样。
that was the idea you know you'd have
这就是你肯定会想到的主意。
the guy who was like I've got eight kids
那个人说，我有八个孩子
you know and and as a result I'm the
你知道，结果我就是
manliest man in the room and I would
房间里最有男子气概的男人，而我
leave thinking my God I can't I can't
离开时心里想着，我的天哪，我不能，我不能
even have a child like what what's
甚至有个孩子，就像……什么是什么
what's the issue and then you begin to
问题是什么？然后你开始……
think okay you know
想想，好吧，你知道
um
嗯
um what are all the factors and you
嗯，所有因素是什么？你
begin to go through the test and you
开始进行测试，然后你
begin to your point and you've already
你的观点开始了，而且你已经……
done this is you see there's a multitude
这样就完成了，你看，这里有很多……
of issues and for some
问题以及一些
people they're incredibly fertile and it
这些人生育能力非常强，而且
takes boom eight times but for others
爆炸发生八次，但对其他人来说却并非如此。
and I'm in the others it
我在其他几部里。
takes
需要
years you know um but I will say this
你知道，这些年了，嗯，但我还是要说……
and this goes back to the investment
而这又回到了投资的问题上。
Theory the more that we invested in the
理论方面，我们投入的越多……
pursuit of having children the more the
越是追求生育子女
desire increase and then now the level
欲望增强，然后现在水平
of cherishing our our boys is on a whole
珍惜我们的男孩们是整体而言的
another I think because of that
我觉得另一个原因是因为这个。
experience is on a whole another Lev
经验完全是另一个层次的。
I can imagine it really tears
我能想象到那真的会让人泪流满面。
relationships apart this issue of
除了这个问题之外，人际关系也存在问题。
fertility in children especially if the
儿童的生育能力，尤其是如果
results come back I was super scared
结果出来后，我超级害怕
when them sperm analysis came in and
当他们的精液分析结果出来时
they like sent me the email with
他们好像给我发了封邮件。
password on it I was like oh my God if
我当时想，天哪，如果密码是……
imagine if I open this document now and
想象一下，如果我现在打开这份文件……
it says that my spam are like not not
它说我的垃圾邮件就像不是不是
good like she's going to leave me you
好极了，她好像要离开我了。
know that's what you kind of think yeah
我知道你大概就是这么想的，是的。
and I'm sure she she might have felt the
我相信她可能也感觉到了。
same way she might have there might have
就像她可能在那里一样，她可能也有
been a doubt in her that said if if her
她心中一直有个疑问，那就是如果她
results came back and it was bad then
结果出来了，情况很糟糕。
maybe I would leave or something OB I
也许我会离开或者做点别的什么。
wouldn't but um I'm sure it tears a lot
不会，但是嗯，我确定它会撕裂很多东西。
of families apart a lot of relationships
家庭成员分离，许多关系
apart this these issues of fertility yes
除了生育问题之外，是的
and and and that's why it's so important
所以，这就是它如此重要的原因。
for us
对我们来说
to spend more
花费更多
time in determining whether or not we
确定我们是否需要时间
feel like we have the right
感觉我们有权
partner before we decide to commit to
在决定做出承诺之前，先与合作伙伴沟通。
them before we decided to have to have
在我们决定必须拥有它们之前，
children with them which is a massive
他们带着孩子，这真是太棒了。
decision before we decide to move house
在决定搬家之前，我们需要先做出决定。
or move into a
或者搬进
house our
我们家
partner our our partner is often life or
伴侣，我们的伴侣通常是生活或
death for us the selection of our
死亡对我们来说，是我们的选择。
partner the selection of our partner is
合作伙伴的选择是
I truly believe the most important
我真心相信最重要的
decision that we will have because of
我们将因为以下原因而做出决定
all these things that it that it
所有这些事情，它就是它
dictates that we've talked about so
这表明我们已经讨论过这个问题了。
having
拥有
more emphasis on who that partner is and
更注重合作伙伴是谁
the dialogue upfront is so incredibly
开头的对话真是太棒了
important you know you think about this
重要的是你要明白这一点。
is like the top uh the
就像顶部的呃
Gans you know they talk about how
你知道，甘斯会谈到如何
69%
69%
of problems in a relationship will never
恋爱关系中的问题永远不会
be resolved 69% never be resolved that's
69%的问题会得到解决，但永远无法解决。
scary that's scary what does that mean
可怕，真可怕，这是什么意思？
that means that you have to learn how to
这意味着你必须学会​​如何
manage it so that means that you have to
管理好它，这意味着你必须……
have a partner who has Superior conflict
有一个伴侣，他有严重的冲突
management skills and so do you if you
你也需要具备管理技能，如果你
can't if your partner doesn't have that
如果你的伴侣没有那种能力，那就不行。
you are in for a world of hurt wouldn't
你等着瞧吧，你会非常痛苦的。
it be great to have determined that
如果能确定这一点就太好了。
before you decide to have a child with
在你决定要孩子之前
someone because once you have a child
因为一旦你有了孩子，就会有人……
the level of conflict is going through
冲突程度正在经历
the
这
roof I umum I had some stats that show
屋顶我嗯嗯我有一些统计数据显示
that in terms of mental health a study
就心理健康而言，一项研究
published in nature showed that
发表在《自然》杂志上的文章表明
unmarried individuals have a 79% high
未婚人士中，高患病率高达79%。
risk of developing depression compared
与……相比，患抑郁症的风险
to their married counterparts maybe I
或许对已婚人士来说，我
should get married but also Research
应该结婚，但也要做研究
indicates that strong social connections
表明强大的社会联系
like a romantic relationship can
就像恋爱关系一样
increase longevity significantly and a
显著延长寿命
comprehensive study analyzing 43 data
一项综合研究分析了43个数据
sets revealed that the quality of one's
数据集揭示了一个人的品质
romantic relationship is a significant
恋爱关系是一件非常重要的事。
predictor of overall life satisfaction
总体生活满意度的预测因素
High relationship satisfaction
高度的关系满意度
correlates with increased happiness and
与幸福感的提升呈正相关
well-being um and the stats go on and on
幸福感，嗯，还有各种统计数据，不胜枚举。
and on and on even financial
以及金融方面的问题，不胜枚举。
implications which is quite quite
这其中的含义相当……
staggering yeah I I this is a bit of a
令人震惊，是的，这有点……
different question but um we talked a
另一个问题，但是我们聊了聊……
second ago about self-esteem and how if
刚才谈到了自尊以及如果
someone came to you in your matchmaking
有人在你的婚介过程中主动联系了你。
days and they were like Keen to form and
日子里，他们就像渴望形成一样。
find love one of the first things you'd
找到爱情是你最先要做的事情之一。
say is like we need to work on the
可以说，我们需要努力改进……
self-esteem but if a man comes to you
自尊心，但如果一个男人来找你
and they are let's say you're one of
假设你是其中之一
your sons okay Kingston is that your
你儿子们还好吗，金斯顿？那是你的
oldest yes that's my oldest Kingston
是的，那是我最老的金斯顿
goes that listen what what should I be
那我该听着，我应该是什么？
doing to increase the probability now
现在这样做是为了增加概率。
that I find and keep a partner what work
找到并留住一个伴侣，这对我来说很重要。
can I do on my own now like do I need to
我现在可以自己做了吗？我需要做什么？
hit the gym do I need to read a book
去健身房锻炼，我需要看书吗？
what do I need to do do I need to go out
我需要做什么？我需要出去吗？
and earn money and I want the honest
我想赚钱，而且我想要诚实。
answer that you would say to Kingston
你会如何回答金斯顿
when no one's looking you know what's
当没人注意的时候，你知道发生了什么。
Wild is I've already started talking to
真是不可思议，我已经开始和……说话了
Kingston about this okay because we work
金斯顿对此表示同意，因为我们工作
out together on the weekends uh and I'm
周末一起出去玩，嗯，我是
shocked at how strong he's getting he's
他对自己变得如此强大感到震惊。
14 uh all the time I tell him King
14 嗯，我一直都告诉他国王
Kingson King surround yourself with
金斯顿国王将自己包围起来
great people
伟大的人们
that's it surround yourself put yourself
就是这样，让自己置身其中。
in proximity to people who have healthy
靠近健康的人
relationships to people who have high
与那些拥有高……的人建立关系
satisfaction in their relationships it's
他们对彼此关系的满意度是
no different than in business you want
和你在商业领域想要的东西没什么不同。
to succeed surround yourself with folks
要想成功，就要和那些志同道合的人在一起。
who are succeeding in business you
那些在商业上取得成功的人
surround yourself with those people and
多和这些人在一起
what you begin to do is you begin to
你开始做的就是你开始
observe their habits you see their
观察他们的习惯，你就会发现他们的
skills you adopt their habits you adopt
你习得的技能和习惯
their skills you understand where the
他们的技能你明白在哪里
boundaries should be what is a healthy
界限应该体现健康状态。
doubt what is an unhealthy doubt you
怀疑什么是不健康的怀疑？
learn all of these behaviors by simply
只需简单地学习这些行为即可。
surrounding yourself with good people
多和优秀的人在一起
this is the
这是
key as you guys know whoop is one of my
你们都知道，Whoop 是我的一个关键技能。
show sponsors it's also a company that I
节目赞助商，它也是一家我所在的公司。
have invested in and it's one that you
已经投资了，而且是你
guys asked me about a lot the biggest
大家问了我很多问题，其中最大的一个。
question I get asked is why I use whoop
经常有人问我为什么使用 Whoop
over other wearable technology options
优于其他可穿戴技术选项
and there is a bunch of reasons but I
原因有很多，但我
think it really comes down to the most
我认为这最终取决于最……
overlooked yet crucial feature it's
一个被忽视但至关重要的特性是
noninvasive nature when everything in
非侵入性，一切都在
life seems to be competing for my
生活似乎在争夺我的……
attention I turned to whoop because it
我转而关注欢呼声，因为它
doesn't have a screen and will armed the
没有屏幕，并且会启动
CEO who came on this podcast told me the
来参加这个播客节目的CEO告诉我……
reason that there's no screen because
原因在于没有屏幕
screens equal distraction so when I'm in
屏幕会分散注意力，所以当我在……的时候
meetings or I'm at the gym my whoop
开会或者我在健身房，我的呼呼
doesn't demand my attention it's there
它并不引人注目，它只是在那里而已。
in the background constantly pulling
背景中不断拉扯
data and insights from my body that are
来自我身体的数据和见解是
ready for when I need them if you've
如果你已经准备好了，随时可以给我。
been thinking about joining woop you can
我一直在考虑加入Woop，你可以
head to join. whoop.com
前往加入。 whoop.com
CEO and try whoop for 30 days risk-free
CEO 和 Whoop 用户可免费试用 30 天。
and zero commitment that's join.
无需任何承诺即可加入。
whoop.com
whoop.com
CEO let me know how you get
CEO，请告诉我你是如何获得
on myths yes we talked about a lot of
关于神话，是的，我们谈了很多。
myths today and your book contains 21
如今的种种迷思，你的书中包含了21个。
different myths um I won't go through
各种各样的神话，嗯，我就不一一赘述了。
them all because I think people should
所有这些都是因为我认为人们应该
buy the book and read them all and we
买下这本书，把它们全部读完，然后我们
don't have enough time to go through all
没有足够的时间全部看完。
of them but just picking out some of the
但他们中只有一部分是……
ones that really stood out to me okay uh
那些真正让我印象深刻的，嗯……
one of the myths that you say in your
你在文章中提到的一个神话
book is that more sex equals a happier
这本书认为，性生活越多，就越幸福。
relationship is that true
这段关系是真的吗？
does having more sex increase the
性生活增多会增加什么症状？
happiness in your relationship
你们关系中的幸福
no no
不不
now here's the investigation of
现在，让我们来调查一下……
that studies show that couples who have
研究表明，夫妻双方
a high level of satisfaction in their
对他们的工作和生活有很高的满意度
relationship they have a high amount of
他们之间的关系非常密切
sex but it's not as a result of the sex
性，但这不是性的结果
that gives them the high satisfaction
这让他们感到非常满意。
it's the high satisfaction that gives
正是这种高度的满足感赋予了它意义。
them the high amount of sex so the
他们性生活频繁，所以
challenge is that we have to reframe and
挑战在于我们必须重新构建和
we have to stop thinking that just
我们必须停止这样想：仅仅
because we're having a lot of sex it
因为我们性生活很频繁
doesn't mean that we have a great
但这并不意味着我们拥有一个伟大的
relationship I see this happen all the
我看到这种事在恋爱关系中屡见不鲜。
time especially I'm Married at First
尤其是我一见钟情的时候
Sight a couple sits down the first thing
看到一对夫妇坐了下来，第一件事就是
they say is oh Paul I don't need any
他们说，哦，保罗，我不需要任何
help we're having sex like
救命，我们正在做爱
rabbits first of all lions have much
首先是兔子，狮子有很多
more sex than rabbits secondly is that
其次，比兔子性欲更强的是……
doesn't mean you have a great
这并不意味着你拥有一个很棒的
relationship the fact that you're having
你们之间的关系，以及你们正在经历的这种关系。
lots of sex it tells me nothing
性生活很多，但这并不能说明什么。
so the the the myth is that if you have
所以，这个误区是，如果你有
lots of sex it means you have a healthy
性生活频繁意味着你拥有健康的性生活。
relationship but could you be in a
但你可能处于一段恋爱关系中
sexless relationship and also be
无性关系，而且也是
extremely happy you can many people many
非常高兴你能帮助很多人。
people are in that space you've met
你在那个空间里遇到的人都在那里。
people that are like this yes there are
是的，确实有这样的人。
a significant percentage of people that
相当一部分人
are like that especially as we get older
尤其随着年龄增长，这种情况就更加明显了。
you have couples in their 80s
你们这里有八十多岁的夫妇
who've now reached a point where the
他们现在已经到了这样一个阶段：
desire for sex is not there maybe it's
可能没有性欲
once a
曾经
year and I know everyone in their 20s
今年，我认识所有二十多岁的人。
30s 40s even 50s like oh my gosh once a
30多岁、40多岁，甚至50多岁，我的天哪，曾经……
year this is crazy but if you have a
今年真是太疯狂了，但如果你有一个
couple you know you know uh there are
你知道，你知道，呃，有一对夫妇
two different desires here there's one
这里有两种不同的欲望，其中一种是……
is called a spontaneous desire and one
被称为自发的欲望，而
is called a responsive desire now there
现在这被称为回应性欲望。
is a gender difference here most men
这里是否存在性别差异？大多数男性
even if if you look through the ages all
即使你纵观历史长河，所有
the way up to' 60s '70s they have what's
直到 60 年代、70 年代，他们拥有的是什么
called a spontaneous desire which means
被称为自发性欲望，这意味着
that they are ready 24/7 they could just
他们随时待命，24/7 全天候准备就绪。
go they they they need no emotional turn
他们去吧，他们，他们不需要任何情感上的转变
on in order to have sex they just get a
为了发生性关系，他们只需要……
hard on sat there hard on demand okay
坐在那里，硬着头皮，要求，好的
pretty
漂亮的
much whereas as women get older
然而，随着女性年龄的增长，情况就大不相同了。
typically they require responsive desire
通常它们需要积极的回应
what is responsive desire they want some
什么是回应性欲望，他们想要一些
emotional connection some emotional
情感联系，一些情感
currency they want some safety they want
他们想要的货币，他们想要的安全感
a conversation and not just one but they
一场对话，而且不止一场，而是他们
want to have a buildup of that emotional
想要积累那种情绪
currency in order for them to have a
货币，以便他们拥有
responsive desire to the sex in order to
对性行为产生积极的性欲
have sex so there's different desires
发生性行为是因为存在不同的欲望
when you talk about sex um and I think
当你谈到性的时候，嗯，我想
that more discussion needs to be had
还需要进行更多讨论。
around responsive desire and the
围绕着响应式欲望和
importance of building what Dr Karen
构建凯伦博士的理念的重要性
gurnie talks about is as emotional
格尼谈论的是情绪化的
currency to build up that connection
建立这种联系所需的资金
with your partner so it's almost
和你的伴侣一起，所以几乎
emotional currency is almost like
情感货币几乎就像
putting deposits in the bank account
将存款存入银行账户
right if you if you're if if there's an
对，如果你，如果你是，如果有一个
empty sexual bank account and you just
你性欲账户空空如也，而你却……
go to your partner and you say I want to
去找你的伴侣，然后说我想
have sex in other words I want to make a
换句话说，我想做爱。
withdrawal there's nothing there you're
提款，那里什么都没有，你什么都没有
getting nothing literally you're getting
你实际上什么也没得到。
nothing however if you are placing
但是，如果您要放置，则无需其他操作。
deposits in
存款
what is that that is just wanted to send
那是什么？就是想发给你的那个东西。
you a text to to tell you you know how
给你发条短信告诉你，你知道怎么做
much I do love you to I appreciate how
我非常爱你，也很感激你。
well you take care uh of the kids um uh
你负责照顾孩子们，嗯……
I can't wait for us to have date night
我迫不及待地想和你一起约会。
tonight uh you know just to watch the
今晚，你知道，就看看……
movie and have wine right these
看电影，喝葡萄酒，对吧？
deposits hugs kisses with no requirement
存款、拥抱、亲吻，无需任何要求
of of of sex you know I often talk about
性，你知道我经常谈论……
30 second hug and I gave you a 30 second
30秒的拥抱，我也给了你30秒
hug
拥抱
once why don't you look happy about
你为什么看起来不高兴？
that no it matters it's important deina
不，这不重要，这很重要，迪娜
does the same she's a really exceptional
她也一样，她真的非常出色。
hugger yes she's very good so the 30
拥抱者，是的，她非常好，所以是30
second hug I talk about the sixc kiss
第二次拥抱，我谈到了六度之吻
and so many people respond back well if
而且很多人对此反应良好
if I gave my husband a 30 second kiss
如果我给我丈夫一个30秒的吻
he'd think that se sex is at the end of
他会认为性爱是在最后。
that no we need to normalize these
不，我们需要将这些正常化。
things that's putting emotional dep
造成情感依赖的事情
deposits into our partner so then once
将存款存入我们的合作伙伴账户，然后一旦
it's built up then you can go make your
搭建好之后，你就可以去做你的了。
withdrawal right and and so um yeah sex
撤回对，所以嗯，是的，性
needs to be looked at it I think more
我觉得需要仔细研究一下。
and more from the standpoint of
以及从以下角度来看：
responsive in spontaneous
自发性反应
desire desire management term that I
欲望欲望管理术语我
talk about with my friends sometimes um
有时候会和朋友们聊聊，嗯。
should we spend more time apart in our
我们是否应该花更多时间分开居住？
relationships we we live in a society
我们生活在一个充满各种关系的社会中。
now as you said where we're becoming
正如你所说，我们正在走向何方
more and more individualistic which
越来越个人主义
means that there's more demands being
这意味着有更多的需求。
placed on our partner to be everything
我们把一切都托付给了我们的合作伙伴。
and if they're everything surely they're
如果它们就是一切，那它们肯定就是
less attractive because if they're our
吸引力降低，因为如果它们是我们的
counselor our therapist our accountant
咨询师、治疗师、会计师
or our best friend there's it seems like
或者我们最好的朋友似乎就在那里
logically then they wouldn't be as spicy
从逻辑上讲，那样的话它们就不会那么辣了。
yeah if if they are everything we set
是的，如果它们就是我们设定的一切。
ourselves up with a very high stakes
我们把自己置于非常高的风险之中
relationship because the moment that
因为那一刻的关系
they don't become everything they could
他们并没有成为他们能成为的一切。
be 99% of everything but the moment
占据一切的99%，唯独不占据那一刻。
they're not 100% we're disappointed but
他们并非百分之百满意，我们感到失望，但
also like if this person is
也喜欢这个人
like my emotional support in so many
就像我在很多方面给予我的情感支持一样
areas of my life they are my friend they
在我生活的方方面面，他们都是我的朋友。
are my uh co-founder of my company I
我的公司联合创始人
wonder if the the spice you know they
想知道你是否知道他们使用的香料
say absence makes the heart grow fond I
俗话说，小别胜新婚。
wonder if the spice is going to leave
不知道香料会不会散去
the
这
building the the spice can but there are
建造香料罐，但有
other I think more challenging issues
我认为其他更具挑战性的问题
that that can arise and I'll give you my
这种情况可能会发生，我会把我的
example because I fell into this right
举例来说，因为我掉进了这个陷阱
so I uh reached a point in my marriage
所以，我的婚姻到了一个阶段。
where my wife was everything to me she
妻子对我来说就是一切。
was my co-founder we were running a
是我的联合创始人，我们当时正在运营一家
matchmaking agency we spent nearly all
我们几乎把所有钱都花在了婚介机构上
of our time together we were co-parents
在我们共同生活的这段时间里，我们是共同抚养孩子的父母。
uh right we were uh if I had a a a a
嗯，对，我们当时是……如果我有一个……
business question a platonic question a
商业问题 柏拉图式问题
romantic question I would go to her uh
浪漫的问题，我会去找她……
it got to the point where I saw myself
到了后来，我看到了自己
disconnecting from my Social Circle I
与我的社交圈断绝关系
used to go uh to I had season tickets to
以前经常去，我有季票。
to to watch basketball I would stop
为了看篮球比赛，我会停下来
doing that stop watching my NFL football
那样做就别看我的NFL橄榄球比赛了
on the weekends because it was just
周末的时候，因为就是这样
spending time with with with you know
花时间和你在一起，你知道
with with Jill and the boys and I
和吉尔、孩子们还有我
realized very quickly that what was
我很快意识到那是什么
happening is I was investing everything
事情的经过是这样的，我当时把所有钱都投了出去。
into my wife and my family and the issue
这个问题牵扯到我的妻子、我的家人以及这个问题上。
is that and this is this is what happens
就是这样，这就是发生的事情。
with so many people is that I had had no
与这么多人在一起，我却从未有过这种感觉。
other confidence in my life I had
我生活中还有其他自信。
distanced myself from from almost
我几乎与所有人保持了距离
everyone and the issue from from that is
每个人以及由此产生的问题是
is then I'm bringing no value into the
那么我就没有为公司带来任何价值了。
relationship because I have no no other
因为我没有其他伴侣，所以这段关系对我来说很艰难。
relationships that's ultimately what
归根结底，人际关系才是最重要的。
that means is when you have other
这意味着当你有其他
relationships when you have other
当你有其他关系时，也会有其他关系。
friendship circles you're learning new
你正在了解新的友谊圈
things you're bringing novelty into your
你为你的事物带来了新意
relationship you are adding spice to
你正在为这段关系增添情趣
your relationship I wasn't doing any of
我当时并没有参与你们的关系。
that that continued for quite some time
这种情况持续了相当长一段时间。
this this is one of the reasons why I
这就是我这样做的原因之一
got involved with football here is that
在这里参与足球运动就是
being involved now with a with a with a
现在正与一个与一个与一个
football team in England has allowed me
英格兰的足球队让我有机会
an outlet outside of my family and even
除了家人之外，我还有一个情感出口，甚至
outside of my Social Circle that I was
在我的社交圈之外，我
building here that is entirely different
这里的建筑完全不同。
right it's it's it's a different group
对，是，是，是另一个群体。
of PE it's a group of people who I had
在体育教育方面，这是我曾经拥有的一群人。
not come across in my walks of of of
在我的散步中没有遇到
life who I love and adore and learn so
生命中我所爱、所敬仰、所学习的人
much from and I have a sense of
很多来自，我有一种感觉
enjoyment and because I have a sense of
享受，也因为我有一种……的感觉
enjoyment there I begin to have more
在那里，我开始享受更多。
purpose in my life I begin to have more
我开始拥有更多人生目标。
joy in my life and the more joyful I am
我生活中的快乐，以及我越来越快乐。
about my entire life I can bring that to
我一生中大部分时间都可以做到这一点
my relationship and help to boost that
我的关系以及帮助促进这一点
that that relationship and and so it's
那种关系，所以就是这样
almost like you know if if you think
就像你知道如果你这么想的话一样。
about uh if you're an electrical battery
呃，如果你是电池的话
right and you're charging and you are
对，你在充电，你是
the battery how wonderful would it be to
电池该有多棒啊
be able to get a charge from 8 sources
能够从 8 个来源获得电量
opposed to one right maybe the the one
与其中一个相反，也许是那个
is not working today and therefore you
今天无法使用，因此您
you you don't get charged up but if You'
你不会被充电，但如果你
have eight if you're getting charged
如果你被起诉，那就准备八块钱。
eight different sources right it hires
八个不同的招聘渠道
the likelihood of you being charged up
你被充电的可能性
um to uh you know to to to live your
嗯，你知道，为了活出你的
best life and I think this is where the
最好的生活，我认为这就是……
attachment Styles comes into to play
依恋风格开始发挥作用。
again because I think in my relationship
再次是因为我认为在我的关系中
I'm maybe a little bit more of on the
我可能更倾向于……
avoidant side and she's maybe a little
她有点回避型人格，可能有点
bit more on the anxious side so I think
有点焦虑，所以我觉得
there's a desire in me to like space
我内心深处渴望喜欢太空。
Freedom explore Wonder um she has that
自由探索奇迹，嗯，她有那种感觉。
too of course but I think I just I have
当然也有，但我认为我只是……我有
it a little bit more so it can sometimes
稍微多一点，所以有时可以
feel like she's pursuing yes the the
感觉她好像在追求是的
quality time and I'm maybe pursuing
高质量的陪伴，我或许正在追求
being on my own yes which causes this
是的，我独自一人导致了这种情况。
sort of dysfunction or this this
某种功能障碍或这种
imbalance I guess some couples who are
我猜有些夫妻是不平衡的
both anxious I don't know if they get on
他们俩都很焦虑，我不知道他们能不能相处融洽。
but no I mean what happens most of the
但我的意思是，大多数情况下会发生什么
time is
时间是
anxious find avoidance oh okay yeah so
焦虑的人会选择逃避，哦，好吧，是的。
th those are the two that that end up
最终，这两个人就成了
matching and it's very important to work
匹配非常重要，而且这项工作也至关重要。
for for you both to work on an earned
为了你们俩共同努力，挣到一份工作。
secure one of the best ways to do that
这是确保实现这一目标的最佳方法之一。
is to surround yourself with couples who
就是让自己身边围绕着这样的情侣：
are secure why is it that anxious
明明很安全，为什么还会这么焦虑
relationship attachment Styles go for
关系依恋类型
avoidance you'd think they'd go for
你可能会认为他们会选择回避
anxious right and and we should probably
焦虑是对的，我们可能应该
pause to Define what these attachment
暂停片刻，定义这些附件是什么
Styles mean sure sure so uh out of Mary
风格意味着肯定肯定，所以呃，玛丽
answorth and John bulby uh research uh
安斯沃思和约翰·布尔比呃研究呃
which you know buby from the UK answorth
你知道来自英国安斯沃思的布比吗？
from from Canada the whole idea is is uh
来自加拿大，整个想法是……
it was something called The Strange
它叫做《怪异》
situations test which examined the
情境测试考察了
relationship that we have with our first
我们与第一个人的关系
caregivers and those who had a secure
照顾者和那些拥有安全感的人
attachment is where your caregiver was
依恋是指你的照顾者与你之间的关系。
really always there for you so in your
真的会一直支持你，所以在你
time of need your caregiver was always
在你需要的时候，你的照护者总是
there to to to be of support anxious
在那里，焦虑的人会感到支持。
which a large percentage of the
其中很大一部分
population is is is anxious anxious is
人口焦虑是焦虑的
where your caregiver was there sometimes
你的照护者有时就在那里
other times they they weren't this is is
其他时候他们不是这样，这是
very prevalent in Immigration
在移民领域非常普遍
communities first second generation
社区第一代 第二代
especially second generation immigrants
尤其是第二代移民
where your uh parent was working you
你父母工作的地方
know they're out hustling multiple jobs
我知道他们同时在外奔波找好几份工作。
and they're there for you sometimes but
他们有时会在你身边，但是
they can't be there for for you all the
他们不可能一直陪着你们所有人
time and then you have avoidant avoidant
时间，然后你就会有回避型回避
is when the caregiver wasn't there so
就是当照护者不在的时候。
you had to learn to self Soo you end up
你必须学会​​自立，所以你最终……
seeing a large number of very successful
看到大量非常成功的案例
business people
商人
are avoidance why because they've
之所以回避，是因为他们有
learned to be
学会了
self-reliant
自力更生
anxious turn tend to be more of the what
焦虑的转向往往更倾向于什么
feels to be needy right secure I'm I'm
感觉自己很需要安全感，我……
okay you know I'm I'm okay about myself
好吧，你知道，我对自己挺满意的。
now why does to to do anxious and
现在，为什么会感到焦虑和不安呢？
avoidance end up matching because the
回避最终会匹配，因为
anxious feels comfortable in
焦虑的人感到舒适
Pursuit that's their that's our because
追求，那是他们的，那是我们的，因为
I'm that's our that's our disposition
这就是我们的……这就是我们的倾向
and I think I'm I'm earning more of a of
我觉得我赚的钱更多了。
a secure but our my natural inclination
安全，但我的自然倾向
is that I'm comfortable in
就是我感到自在
Pursuit and avoidant is comfortable
追逐和回避都让人感到舒适
being pursued
被追捕
because you have an opportunity to
因为你有机会
connect but then create the distance you
连接，但随后制造距离
know when you want to so you end up
知道何时该这样做，这样你最终就会
seeing many anxious and avoidance come
看到许多焦虑和回避行为
together and it's important to recognize
共同努力，这一点很重要，要认识到这一点。
that so you've already recognized this
所以你已经意识到这一点了。
which is half the battle is the
这已经成功了一半。
awareness now you can begin to develop
现在有了这种意识，你就可以开始发展了
the tools to become more secure that's
提升安全性的工具就是
difficult that's the work it's difficult
难，这就是工作，它很难。
isn't it I think Step One is obviously
难道不是吗？我认为第一步显然是
awareness because then you can start
提高意识，因为那样你就可以开始了
start to sort of catch yourself out and
开始有点发现自己的不足之处，
see yourself when you're exhibiting
想象一下自己参展时的样子
certain behaviors and really start to
某些行为，并真正开始
question them that's kind of what I do
质问他们，我就是这么做的。
now as an avoidant I when when my
现在我作为一个回避型人格障碍患者，当我的
partners like looking for attention and
伴侣喜欢寻求关注，
looking for you know making those bids
你知道，我正在寻找那些出价机会。
for attention as they call them I
为了博取关注，正如他们所说的那样。
observe what they're doing I observe how
观察他们在做什么，我观察他们如何
I feel about it I and I then rationalize
我对此有感觉，然后我会进行理性分析。
it um above both of those observations
嗯，以上两点观察结果都比较合理。
in a different way so I'll rationalize
换个角度来说，我会这样解释。
it as I love this person so much and if
因为我非常爱这个人，如果
they need some attention now just play
他们现在需要一些关注，就玩吧。
the game Steve just give them what they
游戏史蒂夫只是给了他们他们想要的
want whereas before I'd be like why are
想要，而以前我会想，为什么会这样
they annoying me
他们真烦人
mean yes but I have to do that every day
是的，但我每天都必须这样做。
like as many of these podcasts as I've
就像我听过的很多这类播客一样……
done as many times I've heard about
我听说过很多次这样的事
attachment Styles it's still an ongoing
附件样式仍在开发中
battle yes and I think this is important
是的，这场战斗很重要。
because sometimes we believe that we're
因为有时我们相信我们是
fixed or cured because we have
修复或治愈，因为我们有
information that we're going to act upon
我们将根据这些信息采取行动。
it at all times but the wiring is so
它一直都在，但是线路连接得非常糟糕。
deep it it is and it it is it is a
它很深，而且它很深。
Continuum it it never ends
连续体永无止境
and to your point is this is the work
正如你所说，这就是工作。
the work is that mental energy right
这项工作就是消耗精神能量。
that you had to go through uh you you're
你必须经历的，呃，你，你是
doing uh this uh uh thing Dr Julie Smith
做这个呃呃呃事，朱莉·史密斯博士
talks about it metacognition is really
谈到元认知，确实
what you're doing having the thought
你正在做什么，脑子里想着这件事
about the thought and
关于这个想法和
that is tiring Tire exhausting it's
真累人，真让人精疲力竭。
exhaust to do that all the time is
一直这样做会让人筋疲力尽。
exhausting but that's the
很累，但这就是……
price that you're paying to have the
你为拥有它所付出的代价
relationship that's the work yeah and
关系就是工作，是的。
she's worth it yeah people that listen
她值得，是的，那些听她说话的人。
to this podcast will know that like you
收听本播客的人都会知道，就像你一样。
know when I talk about marriage and
知道我何时谈论婚姻
stuff it's not um anything to do with
这东西跟……没什么关系
her in particular in fact she's the
尤其是她，事实上，她就是……
person that's made me want to get
这个人让我想要得到
married she's the person that's made me
结婚了，她就是成就我的人。
agnostic before I was against it now I'm
我以前是不可知论者，后来反对不可知论，现在我……
like it doesn't really matter if she
好像她是否真的无关紧要似的。
wants it then I I don't really care um
如果你想要，那我其实不在乎。嗯
so I'm saying all of this in spite of
所以我说这些话，尽管……
the fact that I believe I'm with the
我相信我和……在一起
perfect person yes and when I say
是的，我就是完美的人。
perfect I mean Perfectly Imperfect as
完美，我的意思是完美的不完美。
well yes as as I am to her but I just
是的，我对她来说确实如此，但我只是
couldn't imagine ever finding anyone
无法想象能找到任何人
better so I'm saying all of this in
更好，所以我才说这些
spite of that just in case anyone was
尽管如此，以防万一有人
wondering and I genuinely mean that like
我很好奇，我是真心这么想的。
I wouldn't say otherwise I'm not saying
我不会这么说，我不是这个意思。
that just for the sake of it I my
仅仅为了这样，我
friends know this too my friends all
我的朋友们也都知道这一点，我的朋友们。
believe and I believe that she is
我相信，而且我相信她是。
there's no one I'm ever going to find
我永远也找不到任何人。
that's better than her yes
那比她说的“是”要好。
um few more questions that I had that
嗯，我还有几个问题。
came emerged from reading your book
读完你的书后，我深受启发。
which by the way is superb thank you I
顺便说一句，这太棒了，谢谢你！
have to say it is published by flight
不得不说，它是通过航班发布的。
books and there's probably some kind of
书籍，而且可能还有一些其他的东西
disclaimer I have to give for the ASA
我必须就ASA做出免责声明
com for me but um so that's hasht ad but
对我来说是com，但是嗯，所以那是#广告，但是
um one of the ones that was quite
嗯，其中一个相当
provocative to me me is this
对我来说，这很具有挑衅性。
question should you keep secrets from
问题：你是否应该对……保守秘密
your
你的
partner this is big
伙伴，这很重要。
yes so many people are like well don't
是的，很多人都会说，那好吧，别这样。
say that this is crazy what you're
说这太疯狂了，你到底在干什么
saying there are quite a few studies on
据说有相当多的研究……
a concept called selective disclosure
一种称为选择性披露的概念
and a matter of fact one of I think the
事实上，我认为其中之一是
most provocative compelling studies on
最具争议性和说服力的研究
selective disclosure looked at uh you
选择性披露审视了呃你
know many many couples and one couple or
认识很多很多对夫妇，还有一对夫妇
one one group was told to be entirely
其中一组被告知要完全
transparent to your partner so tell them
对你的伴侣坦诚相告，所以要告诉他们。
everything every issue every concern
所有的一切，所有的问题，所有的一切担忧
that pops into your mind tell them right
想到什么就说什么，直接告诉他们。
that's full transparency then the other
那才是完全透明，然后呢？
was selective disclosure now what is
选择性披露现在是什么？
selective disclosure there rules to
选择性披露规则
selective disclosure one is is that you
选择性披露一是你的
share information that's relevant right
及时分享相关信息
you share information that considers
您分享的信息考虑了
their
他们的
emotions information that considers
考虑情绪信息
boundaries information that acknowledges
承认边界信息
the future of your relationship that is
你们关系的未来，就是
timely and the tone is very important
及时性以及语气都非常重要
how it's delivered that's selective
它的传递方式是选择性的。
disclosure so this group was told to do
披露信息，所以这个小组被告知要这样做
that what do you think happens at the
你觉得接下来会发生什么？
end of the result at the end of the
结果的结尾
experiment everyone in the transparent
在透明环境中对每个人进行实验
group they've killed each other no I'm I
他们这群人互相残杀了，不，我……
was going to say Jesus no no no they
本来想说耶稣不不不，他们
they haven't killed each other but the
他们没有互相残杀，但是
group that had selective disclosure has
存在选择性披露的群体
higher
更高
satisfaction less conflict more autonomy
满意度降低，冲突减少，自主性增强
in their relationship so it's very
在他们的关系中，所以非常
important to know that what I say secret
重要的是要知道，我说的话都是秘密。
is is I'm saying you have to
我的意思是，你必须
selectively decide and I think selective
有选择地决定，我认为是有选择的
disclosure is a concept we should spend
信息披露是一个我们应该花时间去理解的概念。
more time thinking about so give me an
再多花点时间思考，所以给我一个
example of something that I shouldn't
一个我不应该做的事情的例子
say to my partner okay so well once
对我的伴侣说，好的，那么一旦
again it depends what your partner's
这又取决于你伴侣的情况。
boundaries are right so so you discussed
界限是对的，所以你讨论过
these boundaries you know all these
这些界限，你都知道。
things but but but just generalizing
但是，但是，但是只是概括而言
I'll give an example so your partner
我举个例子，这样你的伴侣就能明白了。
always leaves the cap off the toothpaste
总是忘记盖上牙膏盖
always it annoys you it annoys you right
它总是让你恼火，对吧？
it annoys you
它让你感到恼火
however you know your partner is going
然而，你知道你的伴侣要去
through a lot of stress at work they're
由于工作压力巨大，他们
working on a new
正在开发新
project is it the right time to bring up
现在是提出这个项目的合适时机吗？
the fact that the cap annoys
帽子令人恼火的事实
you probably not probably not here's a
你可能不，可能不，这里有一个
juicier
多汁
one your
你的
ex slides into your
前任滑进了你的
DMs and wants to congratulate
私信并想祝贺
you and it's platonic it's
你和我是柏拉图式的关系。
congratulations you respond
恭喜你回复
back thank you that's it nothing
回去谢谢，就这些了，没什么。
more look at you speaking from
更多关注你说话的方式
experience was it on the new book what
这次经历是在新书上发生的吗？
was it on what did she congratulate was
她祝贺的是什么？
it the podcast congratulations on your
播客祝贺你
new
新的
podcast thank
播客感谢
you arive delet block right it's like
你到达删除块，对吧，就像这样
thank you right so
谢谢，好的。
boom you know your partner
砰！你知道你的伴侣
is working through a trauma around
正在努力克服创伤
jealousy is it do you run home and say
嫉妒就是嫉妒，你会跑回家说吗？
so and so sent me this message probably
某某人大概给我发了这条信息。
not right so selective disclosure means
选择性披露并非正确之举
that you're taking into consideration
您正在考虑的
the relevance of the information their
他们信息的关联性
boundaries their emotions Etc try to it
限制他们的情绪等等，试着去做
it truly is a concept that I believe
这确实是一个我认为值得考虑的理念。
will help to increase satisfaction and
将有助于提高满意度和
lower conflict in your relationship I
降低你们关系中的冲突
think that's super important uh because
我觉得这非常重要，因为
a lot a lot of the narrative has just
很多叙述都只是
never lied to your partner and it's it's
从未对伴侣撒谎，就是这样。
interesting cuz all of those things
有趣，因为所有这些都与此有关。
you've said have happened to me in my
你说这些事发生在我身上了
relationships before where an ex slides
恋爱关系之前，前任是如何溜进来的
into your DMs and I'm literally sat with
给你发私信，我简直就坐在那里
my girlfriend and my the ex is just
我的女朋友和我的前任只是
saying oh love this or something and you
说哦，我喜欢这个之类的，然后你
like almost panic because I'm like I
几乎要恐慌了，因为我感觉自己
don't want to lie yes but at the same
不想撒谎，是的，但同时
time what's the point in me stopping
时间，我停下来还有什么意义？
this moment to say something that's
现在正是说些什么的好时机
irrelevant and you know
无关紧要，你知道的
um interesting very very interesting
嗯，很有意思，非常非常有趣。
it's an important Insight you you're
这是你重要的洞察
talking there about diminishing conflict
在那里谈论减少冲突
and I am I was recording some stuff over
我当时正在录制一些东西。
the week weekend where I was thinking
那周的周末，我一直在想
about relationshipss and one of the
关于人际关系以及其中之一
things I've really come to believe over
我真正相信的事情
time is that the
时间就是……
the the best predictor of a long-term
长期发展的最佳预测指标
relationship is what how you are at
关系就是你如何看待自己
conflict resolution yes and there's this
冲突解决，是的，还有这个
quote that I love that I've never
我喜欢的一句话，我从未
forgotten that says You can predict the
忘记了那句话说你可以预测
long-term health of a relationship by
通过长期健康的关系
whether each cut heals to 99% or
无论每个伤口愈合到99%还是
101% does your conflict make you
101% 的冲突让你
stronger I love that and in the big
更强，我喜欢这一点，而且在大方面
thing that I noticed in this
我注意到这一点
relationship versus my previous
与我之前的关系相比
relationships is there was this in built
这种关系是与生俱来的。
natural conflict resolution system based
基于自然冲突解决系统的
on who we were as people okay and I say
关于我们作为人的身份，好吧，我说
that because like she doesn't want to
因为她好像不想
shout she doesn't want to scream she
她喊叫，但她不想尖叫。
wants to listen I don't want to shout I
想听，我不想喊叫。
don't want to scream I want to listen
我不想喊叫，我只想倾听
which meant that from the first moment
这意味着从一开始……
of conflict we were able to resolve it
我们能够解决冲突。
and move on yes whereas in previous
是的，继续前进，而之前
relationships it was like two people
这段关系就像两个人之间的关系
that were just broken records trying to
那只不过是不断重复的失败之作。
get their point across at the other
让他们的观点在另一边得到表达。
person yes almost trying to win yeah you
是的，那个人几乎是想赢，是的，你。
know so one is I love that quote I love
我知道其中之一是我喜欢那句名言。
that and what I found and I age our
那以及我发现的，还有我年龄的增长
ability to and I say you know I I I'm
有能力，我说你知道我我我是
careful with using the word management
谨慎使用“管理”一词。
now opposed to resolve given the
现在反对鉴于此的解决方案
research from the Gman around how uh 69%
Gman 的研究表明，大约 69%
of these issues won't be resolved but
这些问题都无法解决，但
but managing the conflict there's two
但要管理这种冲突，有两个方面：
ways that we typically try to manage it
我们通常尝试管理它的方法
one is we try to win the
一是我们努力赢得比赛
argument that is the route that is
论点是这条路
always going to lead to a low level of
总是会导致低水平的
satisfaction the other route is to try
另一种满足感的途径是尝试
to gain understanding about why your
为了了解为什么你的
partner thought
伙伴的想法
that so so so it's just simply I just
所以，所以，所以，我就是这么觉得。
want to understand right should you
想了解正确的做法是
apologize absolutely should you always
如果你总是道歉，那就绝对要道歉。
apologize all right so so here here's
道歉，好的，就是这样。
what the research shows this is well I
研究表明，这很好。
will say this I uh when I was writing
我会这么说，呃，当我写的时候
the
这
book I was writing a chapter on
我正在写其中一章的书
apologies and I go to Jill and I say
我道歉后去找吉尔，我说
Jill how many times a month do you think
吉尔，你觉得一个月几次？
I apologize to you and she's like
我向你道歉，她就像……
H you only apologize like every other
你只会像其他人一样道歉。
month so she's saying that I apologize
一个月后，她说我道歉。
about six times to her per year and I
我每年大约给她六次，而我
was thinking oh this is terrible because
我当时想，哦，这太糟糕了，因为
the data shows the most successful
数据显示最成功的
Partnerships there's an apology every
合作关系中，每件事都有道歉。
week on average once a week and what I
平均每周一次，而我
realized in the Trap that I fell into
我意识到自己落入了陷阱
and I think a lot of men fall into this
我认为很多男人都会陷入这种境地。
is the threshold in which we believe we
是我们认为我们达到的阈值
should be apologizing so something will
应该道歉，这样才能有所进展。
happen in the relationship and I'll
如果这段关系中发生了什么，我会
think what I need to apologize for for
想想我需要为什么道歉
that it's just like it it is what it is
就是这样，它就是这样。
you know so for example I mean the the
你知道，例如，我的意思是……
trash is is always a big issue in my
垃圾问题一直是我生活中的一个大问题。
household right so I'm supposed to take
家里对吧，所以我应该拿
the rubbish out or take the trash out
把垃圾拿出去或把垃圾扔掉
and sometimes I forget okay I forget I
有时候我会忘记，好吧，我会忘记我
don't think it's apology worthy to
我觉得这不值得道歉。
forget to take it out but but I realize
忘了把它拿出来，但我意识到
that's my threshold but to my wife that
那是我的底线，但对我妻子来说却是。
is a I mean there's World War III and
我的意思是，现在有第三次世界大战了，
there's not taking out the rubbish so
所以没人去倒垃圾。
that's a major issue so her threshold
这是一个重大问题，所以她的门槛很高。
level is different so part of what I
水平不同，所以一部分原因是我
learned in investigating this chapter is
本章研究过程中学到的是
for us to be so in tune with our partner
我们与合作伙伴如此默契
that we understand what their threshold
我们了解他们的门槛
is and we meet them at it I had an
是，我们在那里遇到了他们，我有一个
incident in my relationship a couple of
我与伴侣之间发生的一件事
weeks back maybe five six weeks ago
几周前，大概五六周前吧。
where I didn't want to apologize because
我不想道歉，因为
I wasn't sorry because I didn't think I
我并不感到抱歉，因为我并不认为我
did anything wrong okay and I'm I think
我做错什么了吗？好吧，我觉得
I am actually quite quick to apologize
我其实很容易就道歉。
to my partner I've I've apologized this
我已向我的伴侣道歉。
week I've probably apologized last week
我可能上周已经道歉了
for something but it was a really
虽然是为了某个目的，但这真的
interesting moment we're actually in um
我们现在所处的时刻很有意思。
like relationships counseling therapy or
例如人际关系咨询治疗或
whatever we've been for since the start
无论我们从一开始就为何而努力
of our relationship been doing this
我们之间的关系一直在这样做
we've been through like three different
我们已经经历过三种不同的情况了。
therapists and I looked at the situation
我和治疗师们一起审视了这种情况。
of effectively and arrived at the
有效地并最终达成目标
conclusion that in the future I would
结论是，将来我会
not have done anything different so I
我并没有做任何不同的事情，所以我
arrived at the conclusion that an
最终得出结论，
apology would actually be disingenuous
道歉实际上是虚伪的。
like I'm I would be apologizing for
就像我会为此道歉一样
something and probably setting a new
某种东西，而且可能是在建立一个新的……
standard in our relationship that I know
我知道，这是我们关系中的一个标准。
I can't me in the future so I I
我无法预知未来的自己，所以我……
explained that and said I don't I don't
解释之后，我说我不，我不
want to apologize because I wouldn't
我想道歉，因为我不会
mean it in this situation and I wondered
在这种情况下，我的意思是真心这么想的，我很好奇。
whether there's any Merit in that like
这其中是否有任何价值呢？
does your apology genuinely have to be
你的道歉真的必须是真诚的吗？
sincere or are you just doing it just to
你是真心实意的，还是只是为了……而做？
keep the peace you're you're doing it
保持和平，你正在这样做
only when it's sincere but how we're
只有当它是真诚的时候，但我们是如何做到的呢？
doing it is very important so in in the
这样做非常重要，所以……
research that I found only 50% of
我发现的研究只有50%
apologies are actually effective right
道歉其实很有效，对吧？
what constitutes an effective apology
什么才算是有效的道歉
there's a system that I I've created
我创建了一个系统
called Arc okay a acknowledge
名为 Arc 的确认
acknowledge what happened yeah so for
承认发生了什么，是的，所以
example I am sorry that I interrup
例如，很抱歉我打断了
interrupted you genuinely sorry right
打断你了，我真的非常抱歉，对吧？
that I'm sorry that I interrupted you
很抱歉打扰了你。
two is remorseful and I
二是懊悔，而我
apologize for the fact that you may feel
为你可能感到……而道歉
undervalued or not listen to as a result
因此被低估或不被重视。
that's the remorse and then the C is the
那就是悔恨，然后C是
commitment and in the future I'm going
承诺，未来我会去
to try to um you know pay more
想办法……你知道，多付点钱
attention when we're having these
当我们有这些事情时，请注意
conversations so that I'm not
对话，这样我就不会
interrupting you right so this is this
打断一下，所以是这样的
is the the kind of you know what I call
就是那种你知道我称之为……的
Arc method but the idea is to make it
弧形方法，但其理念是使其
effective is to acknowledge what
有效的方法是承认什么
happened be remorseful for the emotional
可能会对情绪感到懊悔
impact that's the key and that's where I
影响力是关键，也是我所在的地方。
wanted to come with with yours and then
想和你一起来，然后
see is what's your commitment for the
关键在于你对……的承诺是什么
future that makes it a comprehensive
使其成为一个全面的未来
apology so in your
所以，在你的道歉中
situation perhaps what you did
或许你当时的情况就是这样。
objectively you would do in the future
客观来说，你未来会怎么做？
but you are remorseful for how it made
但你对事情的经过感到后悔。
her feel so I'll give you some context I
她的感受，所以我给你一些背景信息。
was basically working on something very
基本上是在做一些非常
very important I was going through it
非常重要，我正在经历这件事
and I told her previously I'm going to
我之前告诉过她我要去
be going through this thing I need to be
经历这件事我需要……
working on this thing it's very very
做这件事非常非常
important she knew the every single
她知道每一件事都很重要
detail of this project I was working on
我正在做的这个项目的细节
okay she knew the the deadline she knew
好吧，她知道截止日期，她知道。
the significance of it profound and one
它的意义深远而重要。
thing I'd learned probably from doing
我可能是通过做某事学到的。
this podcast and speaking to you was
这次播客以及与你们的对话是
that assume people can't read your mind
那假设人们无法读懂你的心思
yes so brief them yes and like if you're
是的，所以简要地告诉他们，是的，如果你是
going to be a bit strange if you're
如果你是的话，那会有点奇怪。
going to be a bit focused let them know
我会稍微集中精力，让他们知道。
ahead of time so I'd sat her down and
我事先已经让她坐下了，
said listen for this period of time here
他说，请在这里听这段时间。
I'm going to be a bit weird and I'd
我可能会有点怪异，而且我会
asked her to lower her expectations on
要求她降低期望值
me okay which I think is a pretty like
我同意，我觉得这挺好的。
Forward Thinking thing to do and within
这是具有前瞻性的做法，而且是在
a short period of time we had had uh a
在很短的一段时间里，我们有过……
disagreement a moment of conflict
分歧，冲突时刻
because upon like while I was working on
因为就像我在工作的时候
this thing
这东西
on the third bid for attention I had
第三次试图引起注意时，我……
seemingly ignored it which caused a
似乎对此置之不理，这导致了
spiral and I hate when you ignore me and
螺旋式上升，我讨厌你无视我。
I'd said listen I told you I was I sat
我说过，听着，我告诉过你，我当时坐着。
you literally sat you down night before
你前一天晚上真的把你叫醒了
and in the morning and had a
早上起来，我……
conversation with you just to tell you
跟你聊天只是想告诉你
what was going on and how I needed to
发生了什么事，以及我需要怎么做
focus on this thing yes so I thought the
是的，我当时想，要专注于这件事。
reason why I didn't want to apologize
我不想道歉的原因
was because I thought I did everything I
是因为我以为我已经尽力了。
thought I was supposed to do like I
我以为我应该像我一样
thought I was like i' let the person
我当时想，我就像那样，让那个人……
know told them exactly what let them in
我知道告诉了他们确切的入场方式
on it let them know what was going on in
在上面让他们知道发生了什么事
my nervous system let them know what was
我的神经系统让他们知道了发生了什么。
going on in my mind and we still ended
我脑子里一直在想这件事，但我们最终还是结束了。
up in this like situation where there
在这种情况下，
was a bid for attention and I wasn't
这是博取关注的举动，而我并没有。
quite there but I literally said I'm not
确实如此，但我确实说过我不是
I'm probably not going to be very
我可能不会非常
present right now yes so I thought well
我现在就在现场，是的，所以我想，嗯
what could I have done in
我本可以做些什么？
future like what more could I have done
未来，我还能做些什么？
Y in that situation so I thought maybe I
当时是Y，所以我想也许我
shouldn't be apologizing here because I
我不应该在这里道歉，因为我
actually don't know what commitment I
其实我不知道我做出了什么承诺
can make
可以制作
to so then do you just not apologize
那你为什么不道歉呢？
then you just didn't apologize so we
然后你就没有道歉，所以我们
were in theer we were in like a the
我们当时在那里，就像在……
coup's therapy thing okay so I was
政变疗法那件事好吧，所以我是
telling the therapists this to see what
告诉治疗师这件事，看看他们会说什么。
they their perspective was and they
他们的观点是，他们
didn't they I think they kind of sided
难道他们没有吗？我觉得他们有点偏袒一方。
with me really I think they started with
对我来说，我觉得他们一开始就是
me and then my partner ended up
我和我的伴侣最终……
apologizing which is quite rare because
道歉的情况相当罕见，因为
I typically think that I should
我通常认为我应该
apologize oh my gosh okay well so I may
道歉，我的天哪，好吧，那我可能
have a different take then okay please
如果您有不同的看法，好的，请告诉我。
one
一
is you have you're clear that your
你很清楚你的
partner is anxious yeah she knows she's
伴侣很焦虑，是的，她知道自己很焦虑。
anxious so you're aware that as a result
焦虑让你意识到这一点
of her being anxious there's a higher
她焦虑的程度更高
level of reassurance that she is going
她即将出发，这让我感到非常安心。
to need while she is working on healing
她正在努力康复，需要有人在她康复期间提供帮助。
and becoming earn earn detached but
并变得挣钱挣钱脱离了现实，但
people never really heal you never I
人们永远不会真正治愈你，永远不会。
never heal you well you know what
你知道吗，你永远不会真正痊愈。
healing is continual yeah the question
是的，疗愈是一个持续的过程。
though is can she get to a place of
不过，她能到达某个地方吗？
being secure absolutely happens to many
安全感对很多人来说都是绝对存在的。
people so she's in the process of
所以她正在经历这个过程
evolving into secure so while she's
逐渐变得自信，所以当她……
evolving into secure you have to give
演变成安全，你必须付出
her that benefit of the doubt that she's
给她那份信任，相信她……
going to need a little bit more on the
还需要再多一点关于……
reassurance front that's one secondly is
其次是安抚人心的前线。
if you did sit her down you explain all
如果你让她坐下来，你就把一切都解释清楚。
these things what also could be the case
这些事情也可能是这种情况。
I'm not saying this is but what also
我不是说这就是，但还有什么呢？
could be the case is that there's not
有可能的情况是，根本没有这种情况。
enough emotional deposits that she
她积累了足够的感情。
currently has in the account I think
我认为账户里目前有这些。
that's fact so as a result of there not
这是事实，所以结果是没有
being enough she's checking in for for
她觉得足够了，所以就来报个平安。
the for the uh re Assurance so being
为了呃，关于保证，所以是
aware of those two things the fact that
意识到这两件事，即
she has an anxious attachment she's
她患有焦虑型依恋障碍。
developing secure but she has anxious so
她正在逐渐建立安全感，但她也有焦虑。
she'll her threshold is is is higher for
她的阈值更高。
the need or lower for the need and you
需求或降低需求，而你
may not have given enough emotional
可能没有给予足够的情感
currency early on it makes sense to me
早期使用货币对我来说是有意义的。
that she would kind of check in and and
她会来报个平安，然后……
and there would be a bid now given the
鉴于此，现在应该会有人出价。
fact that you're head down you're
你低着头的事实是
focused you acknowledge the bid and you
你集中精力确认了出价，并且你
specifically said you chose to
明确表示是你选择的
ignore the bid the third one it was the
忽略第三个出价，那就是它。
third bid it was the third it wasn't it
第三次出价，是第三次，不是的。
was I actually didn't feel like I not it
其实我并没有觉得我不是那样。
I looked up and smiled but she was 100
我抬头看了看她，笑了笑，但她已经100岁了。
meters away from me okay and she and
离我几米远，好吧，她和
then I okay I'm GNA be completely honest
那好吧，我承认我是GNA，说实话。
okay because I'm there's no point me
好吧，因为我在这里没有意义。
bullshitting this is good this is okay
胡扯，这很好，这没问题
okay so I I looked up I smiled and then
好吧，我抬起头，笑了笑，然后
I got up and walked across and I picked
我起身走过来，然后我拿起
up my headphones and I came back and
我戴上耳机，然后回来了。
s [__] up when I say I know I [__]
我说我知道我搞砸了，这感觉糟透了。
up no I
不，我没有
know it's worse than I thought I thought
我知道情况比我想象的还要糟糕。
the two I thought there were two
我以为有两个
separate incidents I thought it was the
我认为这是几起独立的事件。
smile and then I thought maybe if I put
微笑，然后我想，也许如果我放
my headphones on I could focus no no you
戴着耳机，我能集中注意力，不，不，是你。
you need immediately after this you need
之后你需要立即……
to go apologize [__] yeah you you know I
去道歉，去他妈的，你知道的，我
I thought there were two separate
我以为是两个独立的。
incidents I thought look up smile H and
我想到的事件是抬头微笑H和
then I need to go get them headphones
那我得去拿耳机了。
because because I need to focus on
因为因为我需要专注于
writing this thing no no when when a bid
写这个东西的时候，不不，什么时候出价
comes through when a bid comes through
当投标成功时，一切就绪。
we know Goins talk about this all the
我们知道戈因斯一直在谈论这件事。
time when the bid comes through is it's
投标结果出来的时候就是……
important to affirm the bid but this is
确认投标很重要，但这
a great opportunity to discuss what
这是一个讨论以下内容的绝佳机会
affirming a bid is you know what would
确认投标就是你知道的
in that moment what would have been
那一刻，原本会是……
enough for her to feel reassured have
足以让她感到安心。
that conversation maybe it she would
那次谈话或许她会
have said if when you right before you
有人说过，如果你就在你面前的时候
picked up the
拿起
headphones a hug or a kiss on the cheek
耳机、拥抱或脸颊上的吻
would have been great I would be good
那就太好了，我会很棒的。
right and so to be aware of what it
对，所以要意识到它是什么。
means to be reaffirmed is is is is so
意味着要再次确认，是，是，是，所以
important or should I say affirmed is so
重要，或者应该说，已得到肯定，这一点如此
important so in this case I would a if I
很重要，所以在这种情况下，如果我
were you I I would
如果你是我，我会
apologize and do that investigation
道歉并展开调查
around what affirming means because
围绕着肯定意味着什么，因为
everyone needs to be affirmed you know
每个人都需要得到肯定，你知道的。
differently I'll apologize to her
我会以另一种方式向她道歉。
promise but no it's a good I'll actually
答应了，但其实没关系，我会的。
I'm seeing her tonight so I'll just let
我今晚要见她，所以我就不多说了。
her know that I've got a slight
她知道我有点
different perspective on it now I love
现在我对它有了不同的看法，我爱它。
it um let's go for one more myth okay
嗯，我们再来讲一个神话故事吧，好吗？
okay let's go for two more all right um
好的，我们再来两个，好的，嗯
because this one's a prevailing one that
因为这是目前普遍存在的一种情况。
I've been exposed to in my relationships
我在人际关系中接触到的
should you go to bed angry at your
你应该带着怒气入睡吗？
partner this is perhaps the most
合作伙伴，这或许是最
believed
相信
myth period we always hear
我们总是听到神话时期
this just apologize and it's not just in
这只是道歉，不仅仅是……
romantic relationships you know I
你知道，恋爱关系
noticed this all the time when I was in
我在……的时候一直注意到这一点。
school when I was when I was younger is
我小时候上学的时候是
if there was a disagreement or an
如果出现分歧或
argument the teacher would say just
老师会说，这种争论仅仅是
apologize right I I played football uh
道歉，对吧？我踢过足球……呃
American football and you know the coach
美式橄榄球，还有教练，你也知道。
would say just just just you know just
会说，你知道，就是
just swipe it like Ju Just make up like
就像 Ju 那样轻轻一抹，就像化妆一样
and you think about that and what we're
你想想这件事，想想我们到底在做什么
saying is that if you appear to be in
意思是说，如果你看起来像是在
Harmony you have a great relationship
和谐，你们关系很好
but we know that's a falsehood in
但我们知道那是谎言。
actuality the key is that if you are
实际上，关键在于，如果你是
able to fully manage what is happening
能够全面掌控正在发生的事情
be aware acknowledge make adjustments
意识到这一点，并做出调整。
around the conflict then at that point
冲突爆发前后
you are living in a true harmonious
你生活在一个真正和谐的环境中
relationship in a healthy relationship
健康关系中的关系
so whenever people say oh we got into
所以每当人们说“哦，我们陷入了……”
disagreement just make up before bed I
睡前和好，就算有分歧也好。
think that is some of the most
我认为这是最……
disastrous advice you can have why
你可能会得到一些灾难性的建议，原因何在？
because you're going to be dist like you
因为你会像你一样疏远你
just get into an argument you're going
只要跟人争论起来，你就会……
to be entirely distressed entirely
完全痛苦
distressed and then what kind of
感到痛苦，然后是什么样的？
response are you going to give you're
你打算如何回应？
going to give the worst qualitative
将会给出最差的定性评价
response that you can will you reconcile
你的回应是，你能和解吗？
what's happening absolutely not a
绝对不是这样。
profound study around this researchers
围绕这项研究的深入研究
divided two groups of people one group
将人分成两组，一组
they showed distressing images to
他们展示了令人不安的画面
terrible images terrible right and the
可怕的画面，可怕的权利，以及
other group they say they showed the
他们说另一组人展示了
same image
同一张图片
however the second group was allowed to
然而，第二组被允许……
sleep for 8 hours at the end of 8 hours
8 小时后睡 8 小时
so what group one can't sleep group two
所以，第一组睡不着觉的是哪一组？第二组呢？
saw the distressing images they can
他们看到了那些令人痛心的画面
sleep at the end of the eight hours they
八小时工作结束后，他们会睡觉。
then track the reaction to the images
然后追踪人们对这些图片的反应。
what do you think happens the group that
你认为这群人会发生什么事？
didn't sleep that didn't rest that
没睡，没休息
didn't get regulated they report a much
没有受到监管，他们报告说……
higher level of distress around the
周围人群的焦虑程度较高
images the group group that is reporting
图片显示的是正在报告的小组。
back that had sleep they're regulated
睡眠充足后，它们的神经就会恢复正常。
they're able to look at the images
他们可以查看这些图像。
differently they're not it's the same
虽然不一样，但它们是一样的。
image but they're not as distressed the
画面显示，但他们并没有那么沮丧。
point here is that the best thing that
重点是，最好的事情是
we can do to give ourselves regulation
我们可以采取哪些措施来规范自身。
is a cooling off period sleep on it so
冷静期需要睡一觉，所以
you should go to bed angry you should go
你应该带着怒气入睡，你应该离开
to bed angry and when you wake
带着怒气入睡，醒来后……
up resolve it the brain does wonderful
解决这个问题，大脑真是太棒了。
things in in your sleep doesn't it it
你睡觉的时候会做些事情，对吧？
really helps to sort of pack things and
这对于打包东西真的很有帮助，
and make sense of things and rationalize
理解事物并使其合理化
things better but also obviously it's
情况有所好转，但显然也是
regulating hormones and the and the
调节激素和以及
Brain in a way which I guess will make
大脑以某种方式，我想这会……
you make more rational decisions the
你会做出更理性的决定。
next morning not from the amydala but
第二天早上，并非来自杏仁核，而是
from the logic centers of your brain
来自你大脑的逻辑中心
exactly exact rest is is a superpower
完全精确的其余部分是一种超能力
and we don't use it enough last myth
而我们对它的利用还不够充分，这是最后一个误区。
then if someone cheats on you okay is
如果有人背叛你，那又怎样呢？
that the end of the relationship
这段关系的结束
no or at least it doesn't have to be it
不，或者至少不一定非得是这样。
doesn't have to be uh I I I've referred
不必是呃，我，我，我已经提到了
to the Gman a lot and I think the reason
经常和Gman联系，我认为这是原因。
why is because you know they really did
为什么呢？因为你知道他们真的这么做了。
starting in the 1970s
从20世纪70年代开始
change couples therapy right where
改变伴侣治疗的现状
couples therapy primarily between like
夫妻治疗主要针对类似情况的人。
the 1950s and 70s was about these
20世纪50年代和70年代大致是这样的
interventions when your relationship was
当你的关系处于……时，干预措施
doomed and and and it was about to be
注定要失败，而且即将失败
over so it was a last ditch effort was
结束了，所以这是最后的努力。
to go to these therapists but the Gans
去看这些治疗师，但甘斯
came along and said no you could build
有人过来表示不行，你可以建造
these skills you could build these these
你可以培养这些技能
these these tools to help you all the
这些工具可以帮助你们所有人
way through your relationship no matter
无论你们的关系如何发展
at what stage you're in but they also
无论你处于哪个阶段，他们也
spend a lot of time in what I call these
我花了很多时间在这些我称之为……的地方。
these these these these existential um
这些这些这些这些存在主义的嗯
um issues like cheating and from their
嗯，诸如作弊之类的问题，以及他们的
research they show that 70% of people
研究表明，70%的人
who go through uh their process can end
那些经历过这个过程的人可能会结束
up having a higher level of satisfaction
满意度更高
the key though is around the ability to
关键在于能否……
truly forgive your partner and what I
真正原谅你的伴侣，以及我
say all the time with infidelity whether
总是说有婚外情
it may be emotional infidelity or
这可能是精神出轨，或者
physical
身体的
infidelity is go see a professional
婚外情应该去看专业人士
first especially if you've
首先，尤其如果你有
built what you consider to be something
建造了你认为的某种东西
profound and special with your partner
与伴侣之间深刻而特别的情感
they believe it's profound and special
他们认为这意义深远，非常特别。
and in particular they want to fight and
他们尤其想要战斗，
you have an awareness for how special it
你意识到它有多么特别。
is go see a professional because seeing
去看专业人士是因为看到
a professional literally can put you
专业人士确实可以让你……
back on track to have a phenomenal
重回正轨，有望取得辉煌成就。
relationship question I didn't think I
关于关系问题，我没想到我
was going to ask you but I probably
本来想问你的，但我可能
should ask you based on that because
应该基于此问你，因为
we're talking about infidelity what
我们正在讨论婚外情，什么？
about digital
关于数字
infidelity only fans only F well so I
不忠只有粉丝才有 F 好吧，所以我
mean is that infidelity does that count
意思是说，婚外情算不算婚外情？
does pornography count as infidelity
看色情片算不算出轨？
well long story short is it depends on
简而言之，这取决于
who you ask most people that I talk to
你问我跟我交谈最多的人是谁
qualify that as infidelity if you're not
如果你不……，就把这定义为不忠。
disclosing to your partner that you're
向你的伴侣透露你是
doing it so if you were out here on only
这样做是为了让你能够独自一人来到这里。
fans or or a a full pornographic site
粉丝或完整的色情网站
and you do not disclose to your partner
你没有向你的伴侣透露。
that this is something that you do
这是你做的事
that's infidelity that's cheating right
那就是不忠，那就是出轨，对吧？
if it's something that you disclose you
如果你透露了这件事……
have a conversation about then then
然后就此展开对话
clearly it's not right so for some
显然这样做不对，所以对某些人来说
people they will say that's still it is
人们会说，情况依然如此。
in my opinion if you were not disclosing
我认为，如果你没有披露……
that to your partner it is I'm reading
我正在读，你的伴侣是这么认为的。
some stats here and it says that about
这里有一些统计数据，上面说大约
80% of men view porn on their
80%的男性在手机上观看色情片
own um and roughly
自己的嗯，大致如此
35% of women reported to watching
35%的女性表示她们会观看
pornography on their
他们身上的色情内容
own so watching on your own
自己观看
without your partner having any
无需你的伴侣有任何
awareness of
意识
that for for many people that would be
对很多人来说，那将是
or or or I I believe many people would
或者或者或者我相信很多人会
consider that
请考虑这一点
infidelity with a quarter of men
四分之一的男性有婚外情
reporting that they conceal their
报道称他们隐瞒了他们的
pornography consumption from their
他们消费色情制品
partner and nearly a third of women
伴侣和近三分之一的女性
Express concerns about their partner's
表达对伴侣的担忧
pornography use
色情制品的使用
yeah yeah you know this is why I I think
是啊，你知道，这就是为什么我觉得
it's so important
这太重要了
we have to normalize it almost goes back
我们必须让它正常化，几乎回到原点。
to
到
normalizing being
正常化存在
attracted to people we have to normalize
被我们需要正常化的人所吸引
this because with the attraction there's
这是因为，有这个景点……
emotional there's physical and there's
情感上的，有生理上的，还有心理上的。
sexual attraction and we have to
性吸引力，我们必须
understand that this is a part of Being
要明白，这是存在的一部分。
Human this is what we've been given and
人类啊，这就是我们所拥有的。
the reason why one reason why that we
其中一个原因是我们这样做的原因
hide it is because Society likes to
隐藏它是因为社会喜欢……
shame us and say oh no once found your
羞愧地告诉我们，一旦发现你的
partner you should never have eyes for
你永远不应该对之动心的伴侣
anyone else and part of that is what the
其他人，其中一部分就是
script that's been handed to us and we
我们拿到了剧本，我们
talked about religion having impact on
谈到宗教对……的影响
this and we have we have to normalize
这一点，我们必须使其正常化。
these conversations because when we do
这些对话是因为当我们这样做的时候
we'll have higher satisfaction because
我们将获得更高的满意度，因为
we'll realize that you know like you
我们会意识到你和你一样了解你
turn around and say oh my God like my
转身说“哦我的天哪”，就像我的
partner does this too you know what I
你知道吗，我的伴侣也会这样做。
mean um so it's incredibly important for
我的意思是，嗯，所以这非常重要
us to normalize this concept around
使我们能够将这一概念正常化
having an a level of attra raction
具有一定程度的吸引力
outside of our
在我们之外
partner when it comes to food I trust my
在食物方面，我信任我的伴侣。
gut and I trust Zoe a business I'm an
直觉告诉我，我相信佐伊，我是一个生意人。
investor in and today's sponsor of this
投资者和今天的赞助商
podcast all the nutritionists I've
我录制了所有营养学家的播客节目
spoken to have highlighted just how
谈话中强调了这一点
misleading information is out there when
当误导性信息流传开来时，就会出现这种情况。
it comes to food take healthy Halos the
说到食物，要选择健康的Halos。
claims you see on packaging that say
包装上看到的声明是：
things like low sugar and nothing
比如低糖之类的
artificial are often a sign of foods to
人工成分往往是食品质量的标志。
avoid have you ever noticed a health
避免你是否注意到过健康问题
claim on fresh fruit you probably get my
关于新鲜水果的索赔，你可能会得到我的
point understandably there's loads of
这一点可以理解，有很多
distrust out there who should you turn
在如今这个充满不信任的世界里，你应该向谁求助？
to for accurate information I use Zoe
为了获取准确信息，我使用 Zoe。
which is backed by one of the world's
它背后有世界领先的……
largest microbiome databases and most
最大的微生物组数据库和大多数
scientifically Advanced atome gut health
科学先进的原子肠道健康
tests Zoe gives you proven science
Zoe提供的测试结果经科学验证
whenever you need it as a Zoe member
作为 Zoe 会员，您随时都可以使用我们的服务。
you'll get an atome test kit and
你会得到一套原子测试盒，
personalized nutrition program to help
个性化营养计划，以帮助
you make smarter food choices that
你会做出更明智的食物选择。
support your gut to sign up visit
相信你的直觉，注册访问
zoe.com and use my code steven1 for 10%
访问 zoe.com 并使用我的优惠码 steven1 可享 10% 折扣
off your membership that's zoe.com code
使用 zoe.com 优惠码即可取消您的会员资格。
steven10 trust your gut
steven10 相信你的直觉
so I've invested more than a million
所以我投资了超过一百万美元。
pounds into this company Perfect Ted and
向这家公司投入了巨额资金，完美泰德
they're also a sponsor of this podcast I
他们也是这个播客的赞助商。
switched over to using matcha is my
我开始改用抹茶了
dominant energy source and that's where
主要能源来源，那就是
perfect Ted comes in they have the
完美的泰德进来了，他们有
matcha powders they have the matcha
他们有抹茶粉
drinks they have the pods and all of
他们有各种饮料，包括胶囊饮料等等。
this keeps me Focus throughout a very
这让我能够全程保持专注。
very long recording day no matter what's
无论如何，录音日都非常漫长。
going on and their team is obsessed with
正在进行中，他们的团队对此非常着迷
quality which is why they Source their
质量是他们采购原材料的原因，所以他们注重品质。
ceremonial grade matcha from Japan so
来自日本的仪式级抹茶
when people say to me that they don't
当人们对我说他们不
like the taste of matcha I'm guessing
我猜是喜欢抹茶的味道吧。
that they haven't tried perfect Ted
他们还没试过完美的泰德
unlike lowquality matcher that has a
与低质量匹配器不同，它具有
bitter grassy taste perfect Ted is
苦涩的草味，完美的泰德
smooth and naturally sweet and without
口感顺滑，天然香甜，且不含
knowing it you're probably a perfect T
知道这一点，你可能就是个完美的T
customer already if you're getting your
如果您已经是客户，那么您就拥有了您的
match at places like blank Street or Joe
在像布兰克街或乔这样的地方进行比赛
in the juice but now you can make it
果汁里，但现在你可以自己做了
yourself at home so give it a try and
你自己在家就能做，所以不妨试一试。
we'll see if you still don't like
我们看看你是否仍然不喜欢
matcher so here's what I'm going to do
匹配器，所以我接下来要这样做
I'm going to give you 40% off our
我将给你40%的折扣
matcher if you try it today head to
如果您今天尝试匹配器，请前往
perfect head.com and use code Steven 40
perfect head.com 并使用代码 Steven 40
or if you're in a supermarket you can
或者如果你在超市里，你可以
get it at tesos or Holland and Barrett
去 Tesos 或 Holland &amp; Barrett 买吧
or in the Netherlands at Albert Heine
或在荷兰的阿尔伯特·海涅
and those of you in the US you can get
而身在美国的你们可以得到
it on
在上面
Amazon is it ever productive in a
亚马逊一直都很高效吗？
relationship to be overtly jealous like
关系中表现出明显的嫉妒心
to be babe where are you texting when
宝贝，你什么时候在发短信？
are you coming home like that kind of
你就是这样回家的吗？
jealousy where you're like expressing
嫉妒就像你在表达……
the jealousy so so so that level of
嫉妒的程度真是……
overtness in your jealousy I would say
我觉得你表现出的嫉妒心太明显了。
is is is dangerous and it speaks to your
这很危险，它反映了你的问题。
insecurities and this is why I always
缺乏安全感，这就是我总是
say like because that goes to doubts in
比如说，因为这会引发怀疑
the relationship and you know there are
你知道，这种关系是有的。
healthy doubts if if the question is
如果问题是……，那么健康的怀疑是……
around growth of the
围绕增长
relationship that's healthy if it is
如果一段关系是健康的，那就是健康的。
about a fear based on an
关于基于恐惧的
insecurity that's
那是一种不安全感。
unhealthy Paul this is a exceptional
保罗身体不好，这真是个例外。
book this is an exceptional book um
这本书非常出色。
really it's exceptional because it
它确实很特别，因为……
confronts some of the biggest myths that
直面一些最大的误解
I think hold us all back from being able
我认为这会阻碍我们所有人。
to keep love and in many respects find
保持爱，并在许多方面找到
love in our relationships so I highly
在我们的关系中，爱至关重要，所以我非常
recommend everybody who's listening
推荐给所有正在收听的人
right now check out the link in the
现在就点击链接查看。
description you can get a copy of this
您可以获得此描述的副本。
book on pre-order it'll be out a week
预购这本书，一周后就能买到。
from now roughly on the 6th of February
从现在大约2月6日开始
I believe it comes out the 6th of
我相信它会在第六天发布。
February
二月
2025 and it is the book probably the
2025年，这本书很可能是
only book you'll need um in order to
你只需要这本书就能……
increase the probability drastically
大幅提高概率
that once you find that person you will
一旦你找到了那个人，你就会
do the very difficult maybe even more
去做非常困难的事情，甚至可能更难。
difficult thing of being able to keep
能够保持下去是一件难事
that person um because I like many
那个人，嗯，因为我喜欢很多人。
people listening Once Upon a Time
人们正在听《从前》
thought the game was to find them and
我以为游戏的目标是找到他们，
now I've been in a relationship for some
现在我已经谈恋爱一段时间了。
time I realized that that's actually
我意识到那其实是……
when the work begins and that's what
当工作开始时，那就是……
these 20 this this book that debunks
这20本书揭穿了……
these 25 myths really helps us to do in
这25个误区确实能帮助我们……
a way that is so accessible so um
一种如此便捷的方式，所以……
actionable um and really strikes at the
可操作的，而且确实打击了……
heart of a lot of society's BS to be
社会上很多荒谬现象的核心在于……
quite Frank um it's published by flight
相当弗兰克，嗯，它是通过航班发布的。
books which I probably have to say for
我可能不得不说，这些书
legal reasons which is our publisher as
出于法律原因，我们的出版商是
well um but nonetheless I read this book
嗯，不过我还是读了这本书。
and you're this is the reason why I
而你，这就是我……的原因
wanted to speak you today cuz it's
今天想跟你谈谈，因为……
really essential book and there's a lot
这本书非常重要，内容也很丰富。
of mass media social media propagated
大众媒体社交媒体的传播
myths that I think are really standing
我认为真正站得住脚的神话
in the way of most of us Paul we have a
保罗，就我们大多数人而言，我们有
closing tradition on this podcast where
本播客的结尾传统是……
the last guest leaves a question for the
最后一位客人留下了一个问题。
next guest not knowing who they're
下一位客人不知道自己是谁
leaving it for and the question that's
留待以后再讨论，问题是……
been left for you is what experience did
留给你的，是经历带给你的感受。
you have around age 10 to 13 where you
大约在10到13岁之间，你
discovered your own power to get things
发现了你自身获得事物的能力
done without your parents being involved
无需父母参与即可完成
I know right away
我立刻就知道了。
right away when you said 10 to 13 I
你一说10到13，我就立刻答应了。
zeroed in to me in New York in Long
在纽约的朗，我被锁定了。
Island on a bus on a school bus getting
岛上的公交车，校车上的巴士，到达
my head smashed in to that school bus so
我的头撞到校车上了，所以
I was uh our family was one of the first
我当时……呃，我们家是最早一批……
black families to move into this all
黑人家庭搬进这里
Italian neighborhood um in Long Island
长岛的意大利社区
New York and uh there were a lot of
纽约，还有很多
people who you would put into the to the
你会把这些人放进……
bully category and there was one person
霸凌类别中，只有一个人
in particular that
尤其是
really was was was was trying to get to
真的就是想要达到
me and time after time he would taunt me
他一次又一次地嘲讽我
he would say certain things uh he had
他会说一些话，嗯，他有
control he was like the bully of the bus
他控制了一切，就像公交车上的恶霸一样。
and I had no friends on this bus and he
我在车上没有朋友，而他
would literally sometimes like smash my
有时候真的会像砸碎我的一样
head into the the the glass as he was
他把头伸进玻璃里，就像他当时那样
walking out and the bus driver would
走出去，公交车司机就会
look and never stop never say anything
看着，永远不要停下来，永远不要说话
and I remember that but you know what
我记得这件事，但是你知道吗？
every day I got back out on that bus and
我每天都坐上那辆公交车出去玩。
a lot of the times that he was smashing
很多时候他都在猛击
my head it was because I would say
我当时脑子一片混乱，因为我会说
something to him as he was walking out
他走出去的时候，心里想着什么。
or he would be outside and I never
否则他就会在外面，而我永远不会
forget like he would walk off the bus
他会像下车一样忘记这件事
and I would still flick him off right
我还是会朝他竖中指。
and he would get back on the bus smash
然后他会重新坐上巴士，撞毁
my head in the next day
第二天我的头就乱了。
I I hit him again and I learned how
我又打了他一下，然后我学会了怎么做
resilient I am I'm a resilient guy
我是个坚韧的人。
resilient right I keep you you you push
坚韧的我，我让你，你，你推动
me down I get right back up Maybe not
我跌倒了，但我马上又站起来了，也许不是。
immediately but I'm definitely getting
马上就能收到，但我肯定会收到的。
back up and so that was what I learned
回去，这就是我学到的。
and that was without having uh you know
而且那还是在没有……的情况下。
my parents involved that was just me
我父母也牵涉其中，那只是我。
it's crazy how you can remember that so
真不可思议，你居然能记住这个。
quickly I I love how uh that question
我很快地……我喜欢这个问题
was posed because you know it it focused
之所以摆出这个姿势，是因为你知道它很专注。
on the lesson yeah you know know from
关于这节课，你知道的，从
from um from from that moment and it's
从那一刻起，就是
interesting because I've thought about
很有意思，因为我一直在思考这个问题。
that moment many times but I've never
那一刻我经历过很多次，但我从未……
thought about the lesson until this
我一直思考着这个教训，直到……
question you know and so it's empowering
你知道这个问题，所以它能增强你的力量。
to look at it from that perspective but
从这个角度来看，但是
it's interesting because you chose an
这很有趣，因为你选择了一个
empowering lesson oh do you know what I
令人振奋的教训，哦，你知道我
mean so that's like the choice you made
所以，这就是你做出的选择。
there I was reading this book called the
当时我正在读一本书，书名叫……
courage to be disliked I don't know if
我不知道是否有勇气被人讨厌。
you've read that book no but it
你读过那本书吗？没有，但是
basically says that what happened the
基本上是说发生了什么事
first chapter in it anyway says that
第一章就提到了这一点。
what happened to us in our past doesn't
我们过去的经历并不能改变什么。
determine our future in fact we choose
事实上，我们的未来是由我们自己决定的。
how to take what happened in our past to
如何将我们过去发生的事情转化为
serve a current goal so that thing that
服务于当前目标，因此该事物
happened to you on the bus you've chosen
这件事发生在你选择的那辆公交车上。
to take the goal of like it's going to
把目标看作是即将实现的
make you resilient today and you've said
今天，你要让自己变得坚韧不拔，你已经说过
to yourself now I'm a resilient person
现在对自己说，我是一个坚韧的人。
because I get back up now someone else
因为我现在重新振作起来，换了别人。
could have
可能
said they could have chosen today to
他们说他们今天本来可以选择……
adopt a like a victim mentality and they
他们抱持着一种受害者心态。
could have said I'm always the one that
我本可以说我总是那个人
gets picked on yes and that's just my
是的，我经常被欺负，这只是我的个人感受。
luck yes and that would serve a current
是的，运气好，而且这会对当前有利。
goal of an image that you want to
你想要的图像的目标
maintain and construct today now the
维护和建设当今的
image you want to construct is you
你想构建的形象就是你
you're the type of person that gets back
你是那种会反击的人。
up so anyway the power is within you no
总之，力量就在你心中。
that's brilliant it really is Paul thank
太棒了，真是太棒了，保罗，谢谢。
you everybody please go get this book
请大家去买这本书。
it's an incredible book and it's
这是一本非常棒的书，而且
probably the definitive book on this
这或许是这方面的权威著作。
subject and that pulls on so many
主题，它牵涉到很多方面。
different reference points from PS
来自PS的不同参考点
experience as a Matchmaker to a lot of
拥有为许多人牵线搭桥的经验
the science to the interviews you've now
你现在采访中提到的科学知识
done it's an Incredible Book keep Love
完成了，这是一本很棒的书，请继续支持它！
by Paul C brunon 21 Truth for a
保罗·C·布鲁农著《21条真理》
longlasting relationship thank you
谢谢您维系长久的友谊
brother thank you thank
兄弟，谢谢你，谢谢
you do you know that 80% of New Year's
你知道吗，80%的新年
resolutions fail by February it's
到二月份，所有决议都失败了。
because we focus too much on the end
因为我们太关注结局了。
goal and we forget the small daily
我们追求目标，却忘记了日常琐事。
actions that actually move us forward
真正推动我们前进的行动
those actions that are easy to do are
那些容易做到的行动是
also easy not to do in life it's easy to
生活中也很容易不这样做，很容易……
save a dollar so it's also easy not to
省下一美元，所以也很容易不……
making one small Improvement each day
每天做出一个小小的改进
one tiny step in the right direction has
朝着正确方向迈出的一小步已经
a big difference over time and that is
随着时间的推移，情况会发生很大的变化，那就是
the 1% mindset which is why we created
这就是我们创立的初衷——秉持1%的心态
the 1% diary a 90day journal designed to
《1%日记》是一本为期90天的日记本，旨在……
help you stay consistent and focus on
帮助你保持一致性并专注于
the small wins and make real progress
取得小胜利，并取得真正的进步
over time it also gives you access to
随着时间的推移，它还能让你获得以下权限：
the 1% Community a space where you can
1%社区，一个你可以……的空间
stay accountable motivated inspired
保持责任感和动力，充满灵感
along with many others on the same
以及其他许多人
Journey we launched the 1% diary in
Journey 我们推出了 1% 日记
November and it sold out so now we're
11月份就售罄了，所以现在我们是
doing a second drop head Toth diary.com
第二次甩头 Toth diary.com
to grab yours before it sells out again
赶紧下手，免得再次售罄
I'll put the link below
我会把链接放在下面。
[Music]
[音乐]